<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f112a80c-6c10-4dda-8256-43a221ed047b" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2R2:1461927204</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2R2:1461927204</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T102408Z_1461927204_L5N26G2R2_RTRMADT_0_VOLKSWAGEN-EMISSIONS-TRIAL-PIX.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>VW workers applaud chairman despite indictment</title><summary>VOLKSWAGEN-EMISSIONS/TRIAL (PIX):VW workers applaud chairman despite indictment</summary><xmlText><p>VW workers applaud chairman despite indictment</p><p>HAMBURG, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Volkswagen workers applauded Chairman Hans Dieter Poetsch at a mass meeting of employees at its headquarters on Wednesday, according to a participant, as staff appeared to close ranks behind its senior managers, three of whom have been indicted.</p><p>German prosecutors have accused Poetsch as well as the carmaker's current Chief Executive Herbert Diess and former CEO Martin Winterkorn of holding back market-moving information on rigged emissions tests four years ago, raising the prospect of more upheaval at the company just as it tries to reinvent itself as a champion of clean driving.</p><p>The VW supervisory board was due to meet on Wednesday following the indictments.</p><p>The mass staff meeting at the company's Wolfsburg base had been long scheduled and is part Volkswagen's normal agenda where such meetings usually take place every three months.</p><p>The charges show how the German company, which in September 2015 admitted using illegal software to cheat U.S. diesel engine tests, is struggling to move on from a scandal which has cost it more than $30 billion in vehicle refits, fines and provisions. (Reporting by Jan Schwartz Writing by Arno Schuetze Editing by Kathrin Jones and Keith Weir)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>