<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5a8c6153-ecf2-1777-1b2c-f4a736ab42fe" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Karen Pearlman</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-HOMELESS-FEED:SD — national, itop (500 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — The city of El Cajon, Calif., which found itself under an international spotlight because of its ban on feeding the homeless, lifted the temporary order on Tuesday.City officials enacted the ban on sharing food in city parks in...</summary><sourceId>3549e627-5cc8-1873-8738-21ba5c6b62ef</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K6776%kniht%r%BC-HOMELESS-FEED:SD — national, itop (500 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">California town ends ban on feeding homeless</h2><byline xmlns="">By Karen Pearlman</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — The city of El Cajon, Calif., which found itself under an international spotlight because of its ban on feeding the homeless, lifted the temporary order on Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">City officials enacted the ban on sharing food in city parks in October as a safety measure after the San Diego County Board of Supervisors declared the region’s growing hepatitis A outbreak a public health emergency.</p><p xmlns="">On Tuesday, the county ended its health emergency declaration and the city of El Cajon followed suit.</p><p xmlns="">“We’re happy that the hep A emergency is over,” said El Cajon Mayor Bill Wells. “As we always said, the ban was lifted the moment we were aware of that.”</p><p xmlns="">Critics called El Cajon’s ban a punitive measure meant to dehumanize and criminalize the homeless and in protest staged several food-sharing events at one of the city’s most popular parks, Wells Park near the downtown hub.</p><p xmlns="">International media, including the BBC, picked up on the ban after volunteers distributing food earlier this month were arrested. It also attracted plenty of national attention, much of it unflattering, to the East County city of nearly 100,000.</p><p xmlns="">Activist Mark Lane, who organized a group called “Break the Ban,” was one of dozens of people who shared food in Wells Park several times with the homeless in spite of the ban. Lane and 10 others were cited with misdemeanor charges for violating city code.</p><p xmlns="">Lane said lifting the ban is good news for the homeless and for the groups that want to share food in the city’s parks with those in need.</p><p xmlns="">“The groups that had been sharing food regularly with the homeless will be able to go back and do that again and that’s a great thing,” Lane said.</p><p xmlns="">Lane reiterated, however, that “the ban was unconstitutional and one of four in a series of criminalizing ordinances in El Cajon.”</p><p xmlns="">Lane said he and other protesters believe that El Cajon “very clearly has a plan to move the homeless out of their city in order to not have to give services to them.”</p><p xmlns="">Shane Parmely, another advocate for the homeless, said she felt the ban was the latest in “a series of ordinances that criminalize homeless residents of El Cajon. It’s still illegal for a homeless person to lay down and try to sleep.”</p><p xmlns="">She said the move by Wells and the City Council was “a completely discriminatory, unconstitutional and unscientifically justifiable ban on sharing food with homeless people.”</p><p xmlns="">Wells said the issue of homelessness is “the most important issue that our region faces.”</p><p xmlns="">While El Cajon being in the spotlight because of the ban has been “an uncomfortable situation,” he said, the topic of food sharing in the city’s parks was beneficial.</p><p xmlns="">“It got people talking about it,” he said.</p><p xmlns="">Wells said he was still having a difficult time understanding the controversial nature of the city’s ban.</p><p xmlns="">“This has always been about preventing the spread of hepatitis,” Wells said. “Ironically, it’s the homeless that are most likely the ones who were most protected by this ban.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000027855,t000027882,t000157567,t000041223,t000030742,g000065627,g000362661,g000066164,g000221226,g000065558</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>