<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="05341e70-8380-415b-a2e4-03080b88e4f7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0860</summary><sourceId>d8be1ada-584f-40e5-0e5b-cc609cb64ec5</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7644%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0860</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BOSTON RED SOX — Agreed to terms with 2B Ivan De Jesus Jr. and Cs Oscar Hernandez and Dan Butler on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Named Tom Wiedenbauer special assistant to the general manager; Anthony Medrano assistant player development field coordinator; Anna Bolton player development education and language coordinator; Jeremy Harris player development physical therapist; L.A. Hasani Torres player development performance coordinator; Teddy Blackwell player development medical administrator; Johnny Narron manager and Bobby Magallanes bench coach of Columbus (IL); Tony Mansolino manager, Rigo Beltran pitching coach, Kevin Howard hitting coach and Dennis Malave bench coach of Akron (EL); Rouglas Odor manager, Tony Arnold pitching coach, Justijn Toole hitting coach, Grant Fink bench coach and Eric Ortego strength and conditioning coach of Lynchburg (Carolina); Luke Carlin manager, Joe Torres pitching coach, Pete Lauritson hitting coach, Kyle Hudson bench coach, Juan Acevedo strength and conditioning coach and Jake Legan trainer of Lake County (MWL); Jim Pankovits manager, Jason Blanton pitching coach, Omir Santos bench coach, Moises Cuevas strength and conditioning coach and Gabriel Garcia trainer of Mahoning Valley (NYP); Larry Day academy coordinator, Joel Mangrum pitching coach, Jason Esposito hitting coach and Kai Correa bench/bullpen coach of the AZL Indians 1; Jerry Owens manager, Owen Dew pitching coach, Junior Betances hitting coach, Max Weiner bench coach, Chris Giacchino strength and conditioning coach and Matt Beauregard trainer of the AZL Indians 2; and Luis Jimenez strength and conditioning coach, Mike Merganthaler hitting coach and Juan DelaCruz bench coach of the DSL Indians.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Named Justin Morneau special assistant to baseball operations.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Agreed to terms with C Jesus Moreno on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">SIOUX CITY EXPLORERS — Released LHP Cody Forsythe.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed C John Nester.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Sold the contract of INF Wes Darvill to the L.A. Dodgers.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA CHAMPIONS — Signed RHPs Austin Chrismon and Jordan Kurokawa and OF Steve Brown.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BILLS — Signed S Kelcie McCray to a reserve/future contract.</p><p xmlns="">GREEN BAY PACKERS — Promoted Ed Policy to chief operating officer and general counsel.</p><p xmlns="">NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS — Placed DB Jonathan Jones on injured reserve. Signed WR Bernard Reedy.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH STEELERS — Announced the contract of offensive coordinator Todd Haley will not be renewed.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Assigned G Sean Maguire from Fort Wayne (ECHL) to Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned G Ken Appleby to Binghamton (AHL). Recalled D Steven Santini from Binghamton.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ROCHESTER AMERICANS — Recalled D Eric Knodel from Cincinnati (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE BARRACUDA — Assigned Fs Spencer Asuchak and Colby McAuley to Allen (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TUCSON ROADRUNNERS — Assigned F Trevor Cheek to Fort Wayne (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">WILKES-BARRE/SCRANTON PENGUINS — Recalled F Cody Wydo.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Claimed F Gary Steffes off waivers from Allen.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY MAVERICKS — Signed Fs Nick Miglio, John Schiavo and Dan Smith.</p><p xmlns="">QUAD CITY MALLARDS — Signed F Chris Izmirlian.</p><p xmlns="">UTAH GRIZZLIES — Released G Jay Stevens as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">LACROSSE</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Lacrosse League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BANDITS — Placed T Mark Steenhuis and D Matthew Bennett on injured reserve. Activated D Ryan Wagner from injured reserve and T Liam Patten from the practice squad. Signed F Zach Heereweyers and D Bill O'Brien to the practice squad.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES FC — Signed M Calum Mallace.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA UNION — Agreed to terms with G Andre Blake on a multi-year contract. Named Pat Noonan assistant coach and Tim Hanley goalkeeping coach.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Acquired W Andy Polo on loan from Monarcas Morelia (La Liga-Mexico).</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Signed F Zach Wright.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">NCAA — Named Oregon athletic director Rob Mullens chairman of the College Football Playoff selection committee, beginning next season. Named Florida athletic director Scott Stricklin, Georgia Tech athletic director Todd Stansbury, Oklahoma athletic director Joe Castiglione, former Clemson and Rice coach Ken Hatfield, former player Ronnie Lott and former Arizona Republic sports columnist Paola Boivin to the selection committee.</p><p xmlns="">ALBANY (N.Y.) — Named Brian Gordon assistant women's soccer coach.</p><p xmlns="">ALMA — Promoted assistant women's soccer coach Meghan Gorsuch to head coach.</p><p xmlns="">AUBURN — Named JB Grimes offensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">DAVIS &amp; ELKINS — Added women's golf as a varsity sport to begin play in the 2018-19 academic year.</p><p xmlns="">EAST CAROLINA — Named Don Mahoney offensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS — Named Herb Hand offensive line coach and co-offensive coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>