<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f6f2ae13-9653-464c-a4b3-ff07c09f368a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0443</summary><sourceId>63e1cabf-7af3-4936-9369-4c0e25097b85</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8520%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0443</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">DETROIT TIGERS — Agreed to terms with RHP Matt West, LHPs James Russell and Caleb Thielbar and INF Alexi Amarista on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Agreed to terms with INF Ryan Goins on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — LHP Glen Perkins announced his retirement.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Named Juan Leonel Garciga director/youth academy and youth baseball/softball programs.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO GIANTS — Designated SS Engelb Vielma for assignment.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">JOLIET SLAMMERS — Signed OF Alex Krupa and SS Chaz Meadows.</p><p xmlns="">SCHAUMBURG BOOMERS — Signed catcher Nick Oddo to a contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND BROWNS — Named Todd Haley offensive coordinator, Amos Jones special teams coordinator and Freddie Kitchens running backs/associate head coach.</p><p xmlns="">GREEN BAY PACKERS — Named Joe Philbin offensive coordinator, Mike Pettine defensive coordinator, James Campen run game coordinator/offensive line coach, Jim Hostler pass game coordinator, Patrick Graham defensive run game coordinator/inside linebackers coach, Joe Whitt Jr. defensive pass game coordinator, Frank Cignetti Jr. quarterbacks coach, Ryan Downard defensive quality control coach, Maurice Drayton assistant special teams coach, Scott McCurley defensive assistant coach, Jerry Montgomery defensive line coach, David Raih wide receivers coach and Jason Simmons secondary coach.</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES RAMS — Named Jedd Fisch senior offensive assistant coach.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK JETS — Fired offensive line coach Steve Marshall.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Signed DBs Brendan Morgan and Steven Clarke and WR Tylor Henry.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NHL — Suspended Boston F Brad Marchand five games without pay for elbowing New Jersey's Marcus Johansson in the head during the Bruins' win over the Devils.</p><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS BLUE JACKETS — Signed F Nathan Gerbe to a two-way, one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Assigned LW David Booth to Grand Rapids (AHL). Recalled C Dominic Turgeon from Grand Rapids.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Reassigned F Michael Joly to Colorado (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES FC — Signed D Steven Beitashour and G Luis Lopez.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Signed M Andres Flores and D Modou Jadama. Re-signed D/M Bill Tuiloma.</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE EARTHQUAKES — Named Alex de Crook assistant coach and Jyri Nieminen goalkeeper coach.</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED 2 — Signed Ds AJ Cochran and Jack Metcalf, F Diego Lopez and M/D Yosef Samuel.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALBANY — Announced the resignation of John Battaglino women's lacrosse coach. Named Jessica Davos as interim coach.</p><p xmlns="">BROWN — Promoted Kevin Decker to offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach. Named Chris Zarkoskie offensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS STATE — Promoted wide receivers coach Andre Coleman to offensive coordinator, offensive line coach Charlie Dickey to co-offensive coordinator/offensive line coach/running game coordinator and quarterbacks coach Collin Klein to co-offensive coordinator/quarterbacks coach/passing game coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN STATE — Announced the resignation of Lou Anna Simon, president.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>