<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6eda6508-12ad-481f-23f1-f0d1be62941c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Bryce Miller</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBO-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (950 words)</title><summary>ESCONDIDO, Calif. — Hanging in the home of former Cy Young Award winner Randy Jones is a game-worn jersey from 1975, the season he piled up 20 wins and paced the National League with a 2.24 earned-run average.Above the cursive “a” and “d” in...</summary><sourceId>9fcfa71f-8a7f-4714-714f-623292416927</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K2246%kniht%r%BC-BBO-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (950 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Bryce Miller: Resilient, cancer-free Randy Jones ‘not close to being done’ on road back</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Bryce Miller</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">ESCONDIDO, Calif. — Hanging in the home of former Cy Young Award winner Randy Jones is a game-worn jersey from 1975, the season he piled up 20 wins and paced the National League with a 2.24 earned-run average.</p><p xmlns="">Above the cursive “a” and “d” in Padres rest a collection of brown smudges more than four decades old. The jersey reminds Jones of his exceptional athletic past, along with his stubbornly unaccommodating medical present.</p><p xmlns="">Those stains prod memories of what he tucked inside his lip before each of his 285 career starts.</p><p xmlns="">“That’s chewin’ tobacco, yeah,” said Jones, newly 68, surveying the speckled memento of his playing youth. “I used to spit all over myself. You’d have tobacco juice in your throat all the time. That can’t be good for you. That’s where it started.”</p><p xmlns="">The throat-cancer diagnosis Jones kicked to the curb last May caused him to shed nearly 45 pounds. Radiation treatments essentially robbed him of his taste buds, leaving him unsure if he’ll ever savor a full meal again. A “super virus” he’s still unable to shake caused him to undergo a vocal cord biopsy the day after Christmas and makes every swallow painful.</p><p xmlns="">Jones remains cancer-free, but knows he’s battling through one of life’s 10-pitch at-bats.</p><p xmlns="">“You’ve got to deal with what life gives you,” Jones said this week, overlooking the orchard he lovingly tends that pumps out plums, apricots, pears, oranges, limes and enough other backyard bounty to stock a small grocery store.</p><p xmlns="">“I’m still going through it. You can hear it in my voice. I’m not close to being done.”</p><p xmlns="">That’s the pitcher in Jones, staring down an opponent until the job is done. Health roadblocks make the challenge thornier, but he refuses to back away from projects that include the Randy Jones Run/Walk for Independence on Feb. 17 in Crown Point Park.</p><p xmlns="">The event raises money for Home of Guiding Hands, an El Cajon-based organization that benefits those who are developmentally disabled in the San Diego area.</p><p xmlns="">Jones worked with the group all the way back to the days when he debuted permed hair and a perplexing sinkerball. One time, kids at the home tackled a project selling red apple ice plants for landscaping. He was working on a new home near Poway and needed something to anchor a hillside and thwart erosion.</p><p xmlns="">Soon, a truck arrived at the home. They had 300 flats to sell. Jones bought them all. They pulled together 300 more. He bought those, too.</p><p xmlns="">“I needed something like that and wanted to help them,” he said. “I just thought it was overwhelming, what they did. They find someone a job at McDonald’s, you learn how to ride a bus and all of that.</p><p xmlns="">“They find you what you can do, not what you can’t. You live a life.”</p><p xmlns="">That last thought resonates with Jones. Cancer causes perspective to sneak into the cracks and crevices of the everyday. Fruit dangling from the trees suddenly smells a little sweeter, the sun feels a little warmer, the grandkids’ smiles shine a little brighter. The heart cuts through the haze.</p><p xmlns="">Jones remembers the contrasting feelings while driving back from a central California trip with his hunting spaniel, R.J., in November 2016. It’s wasn’t unusual for his tonsils to swell up from time to time, but antibiotics always did the trick. Until this time.</p><p xmlns="">When Jones reached Los Angeles on the way back, he began to worry. Something wasn’t right. He walked into his doctor’s office on Monday. A CT scan followed.</p><p xmlns="">“I wasn’t in my truck 10 minutes and my doctor called and said, ‘Turn around. I need to see you right now,’ ” Jones recalled. “That’s when I knew I had cancer. I remember, I was on the 15 (freeway), I got off on Miramar Way, did a U-turn and said, ‘OK, here we go.’ ”</p><p xmlns="">The radiation treatments battered his immune system. In October, “the cold from hell” took hold as he lost his voice for six weeks. It frustratingly lingers, still.</p><p xmlns="">Jones peeked at the chew-stained jersey. Any regrets?</p><p xmlns="">“Sure,” he said. “But hindsight, what are you going to do?”</p><p xmlns="">These days, Jones gnaws on an herbal concoction he nicknamed “ground-up asparagus,” a no-tobacco, no-nicotine substitute. He works with a trainer at the gym a couple of times a week. His throat can’t tolerate something cold, like ice cream — and eating without the benefit of taste aggravates.</p><p xmlns="">“Every once in a while I’ll taste a bite out of nowhere, then it’s gone,” Jones said. “I might have the first two bites of a steak and think, man that tastes good. Then everything’s gone. I’d say 95 percent of what I eat, I can’t taste.</p><p xmlns="">“If that’s what you need to be to be cancer-free, so be it.”</p><p xmlns="">The weight tumbled off, dropping to a low of 162. Now, Jones hovers around 170 — a familiar benchmark.</p><p xmlns="">“That’s my old pitching weight,” he said. “I always bragged that one of these days I could get down to my old playing weight, but I didn’t know I was going to do all of this. I got a whole new wardrobe.”</p><p xmlns="">Hopefully, that new wardrobe will include a Padres jersey as a special instructor at spring training in Peoria, Ariz.</p><p xmlns="">“That’s the plan,” he said. “We’ll see, though. You don’t want to take any steps back.”</p><p xmlns="">Don’t count him out. He’s helping Home for Guiding Hands. He’s running his charity golf tournament. He’s tending the orchard. He’s chasing around the grandkids.</p><p xmlns="">Toeing the rubber. Again.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002832,t000002828,t000002827,t000412858,g000065558,g000362661,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>