<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="06fb24b9-08b2-de9c-2c95-c1c4c0dde8c2" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kristina Davis</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-LASVEGAS-SHOOTING:SD — national (300 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Last May 18 — about four months before the deadliest mass shootings in modern U.S. history unfolded on the Las Vegas Strip — gunman Stephen Paddock was thinking about San Diego.On a laptop computer seized from one of his Mandalay Bay...</summary><sourceId>03e59938-bdfb-78e4-8e4f-38b3ba418975</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1956%kniht%r%BC-LASVEGAS-SHOOTING:SD — national (300 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Las Vegas shooter researched San Diego before mass shooting</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Kristina Davis</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Last May 18 — about four months before the deadliest mass shootings in modern U.S. history unfolded on the Las Vegas Strip — gunman Stephen Paddock was thinking about San Diego.</p><p xmlns="">On a laptop computer seized from one of his Mandalay Bay hotel rooms after the massacre, authorities found a web search from that Thursday in May for “La Jolla Beach,” as well as evidence that he had visited Sandiego.org, the region’s tourism website.</p><p xmlns="">The findings were released by the Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department Friday in a report on the shootings.</p><p xmlns="">From his perch on the 32nd floor of the hotel, Paddock sprayed gunfire for more than 10 minutes down on concertgoers attending the Route 91 Harvest Music Festival on Oct. 1. Fifty-eight people were killed and more than 700 were injured.</p><p xmlns="">The search through Paddock’s computers reveals queries into several areas around the country, although it is not clear whether he was considering those places as targets.</p><p xmlns="">On the same day as the San Diego searches, he searched Google Maps for locales in Southern California, including hotels in Santa Monica and a Venice Beach gastropub, and places in Boston, including Fenway Park and Boston University Questrom School of Business.</p><p xmlns="">The Google search for “La Jolla Beach” was made alongside queries for “biggest bear,” “grant park functions,” “open air concert venues,” “biggest open air concert venues in USA,” “summer concerts 2017” and “how crowded does Santa Monica Beach get.”</p><p xmlns="">Ticketmaster’s website and the site for the Grant Park Music Festival — a summer-long classical music concert series in Chicago — were visited about a half-hour before sandiego.org was accessed at 5:05 a.m. that day in May.</p><p xmlns="">The search history grows more focused on Las Vegas in September as Paddock finalized his plans, the report shows.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194): Stephen Paddock</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000027855,t000002537,t000050801,t000394143,t000040350,t000002664,t000002675,c000214761</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>