<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="047e4c1f-4f93-41a1-a619-984dd63f128b" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4 p.m.Stock indexes ended slightly higher on Wall Street after overcoming a brief stumble in the afternoon.The dip Wednesday came after the Federal Reserve released...</summary><sourceId>874f8234-30d9-4ddd-ddd9-317fd73e3ed9</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:a1154%-----%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: After a stumble, stocks end a bit higher</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates with close of US trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stock indexes ended slightly higher on Wall Street after overcoming a brief stumble in the afternoon.</p><p xmlns="">The dip Wednesday came after the Federal Reserve released its latest statement on interest rate policy and the economy. The Fed, as expected, held off on raising interest rates.</p><p xmlns="">Losses in health care stocks were offset by gains in technology companies and other sectors.</p><p xmlns="">Boeing jumped 4.9 percent after reporting sharply higher profits in its latest quarter.</p><p xmlns="">The market was coming off a two-day losing streak and its biggest drop since August.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 1 point, or 0.1 percent, to 2,823.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average rose 72 points, or 0.3 percent, to 26,149. The Nasdaq climbed 9 points, or 0.1 percent, to 7,411.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks moved higher in midday trading after several big U.S. companies reported strong quarterly results.</p><p xmlns="">Boeing jumped 6 percent Wednesday. The aerospace giant has been the biggest gainer in the Dow Jones industrial average over the past year.</p><p xmlns="">Technology companies accounted for much of the gain, outweighing losses in health care and other sectors.</p><p xmlns="">Chipmaker Advanced Micro Devices rose 5.1 percent and Electronic Arts rose 7.6 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The market was coming off a two-day losing streak and its biggest drop since August.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 4 points, or 0.1 percent, to 2,826.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow rose 134 points, or 0.5 percent, to 26,209. The Nasdaq climbed 14 points, or 0.2 percent, to 7,416.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.74 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are opening solidly higher on Wall Street after a number of big U.S. companies reported strong quarterly earnings.</p><p xmlns="">Boeing jumped 6 percent in early trading Wednesday. The aerospace giant has been the biggest gainer in the Dow Jones industrial average over the past year.</p><p xmlns="">Xerox rose 10.5 percent after reporting a strong quarter of its own. Chipmaker Advanced Micro Devices rose 4.7 percent and Electronic Arts rose 8.6 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The early gains recovered some of the ground the market lost a day earlier, when it had its biggest drop since August.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 15 points, or 0.6 percent, to 2,837.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow rose 238 points, or 0.9 percent, to 26,318. The Nasdaq climbed 48 points, or 0.7 percent, to 7,451.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>