<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="39edb2d9-0908-4240-8c8a-12e0daee59f5" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L2N26G087:388785665</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L2N26G087:388785665</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T095843Z_388785665_L2N26G087_RTRMADT_0_USA-EDUCATION-CHEATING-UPDATE-1.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UPDATE 1-Second parent gets 4-month sentence in U.S. college scandal</title><summary>USA-EDUCATION/CHEATING (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Second parent gets 4-month sentence in U.S. college scandal</summary><xmlText><p>UPDATE 1-Second parent gets 4-month sentence in U.S. college scandal</p><p>(Updates to change attribution to court files)</p><p>Sept 24 (Reuters) - A California businessman was sentenced to four months in prison on Tuesday for paying bribes to get his son into a prestigious university, court records said, the second parent jailed in a U.S. college admissions cheating scandal.</p><p>A Boston judge also ordered Devin Sloane, 53, to pay a $95,000 fine and perform 500 hours of community service for his role in the fraud scheme court records said.</p><p>"There are no words to justify my behavior," Sloane said in a brief statement to the court, the New York Times reported, adding that he said he wanted to do what was best for his son.</p><p>His attorney was not available for comment early on Wednesday.</p><p>Sloane pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit mail fraud and honest services mail fraud, court files online show.</p><p>To secure his son's admission to the University of Southern California, Sloane paid $250,000 in a scheme to pass his son off as a water polo player, media reported.</p><p>His sentence was more severe than the 14-day prison term given to Emmy-award winning actress Felicity Huffman this month for paying to rig her daughter's entrance exam.</p><p>Huffman, the first parent sentenced in the scandal, was also fined $30,000 and ordered to perform 250 hours of community service.</p><p>More than 50 people have been charged in a vast scheme in which wealthy parents were accused of conspiring to use bribery and other forms of fraud to secure for their children admission to prominent U.S. universities.</p><p>The schools included Yale, Stanford, Georgetown, the University of Southern California, the University of Texas and Wake Forest.</p><p>William "Rick" Singer, a California college admissions consultant, pleaded guilty in March to charges that he facilitated the cheating and helped bribe university sports coaches to present clients' children as fake athletic recruits.</p><p>Fifteen parents have pleaded guilty in the bribery scandal that FBI investigators call Operation Varsity Blues.</p><p>Sloane remained free on bond, but is ordered to report to a facility designated by the Bureau of Prisons on Dec. 3. (Reporting by Rich McKay in Atlanta; editing by Darren Schuettler)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>