<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5849cda3-ba96-4aeb-b0b5-217510ab5b5f" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDW5ISYF01T:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDW5ISYF01T:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYDW5ISYF01T00000_DNMLENf-20190925110979.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Credit Suisse Spy Probe Set to Decide Fate of Top Executives</title><authors>Patrick Winters</authors><summary>PYDW5ISYF01T(Bloomberg) -- Credit Suisse Group AG plans to finish its probe into a corporate spying case this week, and the findings have the potential to bring down Chief Executive Officer Tidjane Thiam or other senior executives.Investigators are reporting directly into Chairman Urs Rohner, who will move swiftly to either exonerate or take punitive action against top executives, according to a person familiar with the situation, who asked not to be identified because of the sensitivity of...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Credit Suisse Group AG plans to finish its probe into a corporate spying case this week, and the findings have the potential to bring down Chief Executive Officer Tidjane Thiam or other senior executives.</p><p>Investigators are reporting directly into Chairman Urs Rohner, who will move swiftly to either exonerate or take punitive action against top executives, according to a person familiar with the situation, who asked not to be identified because of the sensitivity of the matter. The bank announced on Monday that its board of directors was starting a detailed investigation into the surveillance of former wealth management head Iqbal Khan.</p><p>Credit Suisse is scrambling to contain a crisis that escalated this week as further details emerge on the case. The scandal focuses on the hiring of private investigators to shadow Khan after his resignation to join rival UBS Group AG as co-head of wealth management, giving further insight into the intense rivalry and competition in Switzerland’s outwardly calm financial center. </p><p>According to people familiar with the matter, the operation was ordered to prevent Khan from poaching private bankers from Credit Suisse. It’s unclear who ordered the operation, which culminated in an altercation last week in the center of Zurich between Khan and representatives of the investigative firm following him.</p><p>Rohner and Thiam said that they’re confident that the “truth will emerge” during the probe, according to an internal memo seen by Bloomberg. The lender said media coverage of the recent incidents contained inaccuracies and “sensationalized both facts and events,” before issuing a follow up release which said that Rohner would be in charge of the investigation.</p><p>A spokesman for Credit Suisse declined to comment. The shares fell as much as 3.5% and were trading 2.8% lower as of 12:23 p.m. in Zurich.</p><p>It’s the latest extraordinary twist in a tale that burst into the open earlier this summer with Khan’s abrupt exit from Credit Suisse after a rift with Thiam. Khan, a rising star at the bank’s key wealth-management business, abruptly left in July. Seen as a potential successor to the CEO, he’d enjoyed a rapid ascent to the highest echelons of the bank.</p><p>The case is also making its way into the legal system. Zurich prosecutor said on Friday it had launched criminal proceedings in response to a complaint from Khan, who said he was threatened. The prosecutor declined further comment, citing ongoing investigations.</p><p>The scandal risks shattering a period of relative calm for Credit Suisse -- and Thiam -- after the bank recently completed a three-year restructuring. The lender had enjoyed better results at the volatile global markets business and seen revenue from securities trading rise recently even as peers posted declines, giving a filip to Thiam amid the acrimony. </p><p>The relationship between Khan and Thiam had soured in the months before his exit, according to people with knowledge of the matter. When a corporate reorganization came in February, Khan’s brief stayed the same, even as two colleagues were elevated to the executive committee. Tensions mounted as Khan’s name surfaced in media reports as a candidate to replace Bernhard Hodler as head of Julius Baer. That job eventually went to Philipp Rickenbacher, a little-known internal candidate.</p><p>(Adds Khan’s departure from Credit Suisse in sixth paragraph.)</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Patrick Winters in Zurich at pwinters3@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Dale Crofts at dcrofts@bloomberg.net, Ross Larsen</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>