<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c0d2fbbf-761f-2c08-f408-d4f9eb2602b4" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Josh Shaffer</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-NC-FIFTHGRADER-GOVERNOR:RA — lifestyle (400 words)</title><summary>CARY, N.C. — Last month, fifth-grader and budding reporter Grace Loflin caught a cold on the unluckiest Tuesday: the afternoon North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper toured Penny Road Elementary, meeting her young news team.Her mother, Katherine, prodded...</summary><sourceId>59c06454-0697-4f1c-f1cc-f00c25699c80</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K2628%knihr%w%BC-NC-FIFTHGRADER-GOVERNOR:RA — lifestyle (400 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">How a stuffy nose got a fifth-grader an interview with the governor</h2><byline xmlns="">By Josh Shaffer</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">CARY, N.C. — Last month, fifth-grader and budding reporter Grace Loflin caught a cold on the unluckiest Tuesday: the afternoon North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper toured Penny Road Elementary, meeting her young news team.</p><p xmlns="">Her mother, Katherine, prodded Grace toward school. “You don’t have a fever,” she said. “It isn’t the flu. How often do you get to meet the governor?”</p><p xmlns="">But the 11-year-old answered with red eyes and stuffed-up nose: “I can’t risk getting the governor sick. He has to run the state.”</p><p xmlns="">For her germ-free thoughtfulness, the governor rewarded Grace this week with a one-on-one interview inside the Capitol, where she quizzed him for 11 minutes, jotting notes with a Sharpie.</p><p xmlns="">“You’re a lefty,” noted Cooper. “Like my daddy.”</p><p xmlns="">Grace may have suffered through Cooper’s January visit at home sniffling, but on Tuesday, she faced him in a red leather chair, notebook in her lap, gas logs waiting in a marble fireplace.</p><p xmlns="">“Almost overnight,” her mother said, “she’s seeing her future.”</p><p xmlns="">Before the interview began, she presented a picture she had drawn of a cardinal – the state bird – and gave a shout-out to her colleagues back at the Penny Road News – PNN for short. Then she dove in.</p><p xmlns="">What do you do when you put out a new law and people don’t agree with you? (Lead even when it’s unpopular.)</p><p xmlns="">How do you promote yourself without it sounding like bragging? (Be yourself.)</p><p xmlns="">Are there parts of the job you don’t like? (Disagreements with the legislature.)</p><p xmlns="">Midway through, Grace managed to coax some revealing thoughts from Cooper.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t tell this publicly very much,” Cooper said, “but I’m actually an introverted person. A lot of people who are in office are natural extroverts, and they find it just second nature to be with people. But I’m more of an introvert, so I have to work at going to people, talking to people. I’ve gotten pretty good over the years, but it’s something that doesn’t come easily to me.”</p><p xmlns="">Afterward, Cooper offered these thoughts, having been grilled by a courteous fifth-grader.</p><p xmlns="">“Grace could be our flu-season ambassador for why it’s important to stay home when you’re sick to not spread germs,” he said. “It was no easy interview, and I know Grace is destined for great things.”</p><p xmlns="">So often, sickness leads to missed chances: birthday parties on the day of a fever, sleepovers foiled by pinkeye. But in Grace’s case, placing courtesy over a journalism coup led to a notebook full of quotes – keepers every one.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>