<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e04039d2-6d72-43d5-aafc-12e87f2fd46e" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G26H:1343765608</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G26H:1343765608</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T090135Z_1343765608_L3N26G26H_RTRMADT_0_TANZANIA-TELECOMS-PIX.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Tanzania's mobile phone subscriptions rise to nearly 44 million</title><summary>TANZANIA-TELECOMS/ (PIX):Tanzania's mobile phone subscriptions rise to nearly 44 million</summary><xmlText><p>Tanzania's mobile phone subscriptions rise to nearly 44 million</p><p>By Fumbuka Ng'wanakilala</p><p>DAR ES SALAAM, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Tanzania's mobile phone subscriptions rose to 43.67 million in the three months ending in June, a 4.7% increase from a year earlier, an official report showed on Wednesday.</p><p>Vodacom Tanzania, a subsidiary of South Africa's Vodacom Group, remained the market leader for both mobile phone subscribers and mobile money transfers.</p><p>As in many other African countries, mobile phone use has surged in Tanzania over the past decade, underpinned by the availability of cheaper smartphones.</p><p>The number of internet users in the East African country rose to 23.14 million in June, up from 22.99 million a year ago, the state-run Tanzania Communications Regulatory Authority (TCRA) said in a report.</p><p>The number of people using mobile money transfers rose to 22.9 million in second quarter from 20.8 million previously.</p><p>Vodacom Tanzania increased its share of the mobile phone subscription market share slightly to 33% from 32%.</p><p>Other major mobile operators in Tanzania include Tigo, part of Sweden's Millicom with a 27% market share, Airtel, a unit of India's Bharti Airtel on 26% and Halotel, owned by Vietnam's Viettel, with 10%.</p><p>Vodacom Tanzania also holds a 41% share of the country's thriving mobile money business, which handled transactions worth 8.3 trillion Tanzanian shillings ($3.6 billion) in June, according to TCRA. ($1 = 2,293.0000 Tanzanian shillings) (Reporting by Fumbuka Ng'wanakilala; editing by Hereward Holland and David Clarke)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>