<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8fb9c1ac-c0fb-4c45-883e-0eec8a8c1477" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2OY:949955538</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2OY:949955538</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T100000Z_949955538_L5N26G2OY_RTRMADT_0_BRITAIN-ECONOMY-RETAIL.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UK retail sales fall less fast in September - CBI</title><summary>BRITAIN-ECONOMY/RETAIL:UK retail sales fall less fast in September - CBI</summary><xmlText><p>UK retail sales fall less fast in September - CBI</p><p>LONDON, Sept 25 (Reuters) - British retailers reported that sales fell less rapidly in September than the month before, when they declined at their sharpest rate in more than a decade, the Confederation of British Industry said on Wednesday.</p><p>The CBI's monthly index of reported sales rose to -16 in September from -49 in August, a somewhat bigger rebound than economists had forecast on average in a Reuters poll.</p><p>The gauge of orders placed with suppliers rose to -9 from -59, but stores still judged that sales were poor for the time of year, with this measure dropping to -11 from -6.</p><p>Retailers remained under pressure from a weaker currency, as well as concerns about tariffs and delays to imports if Britain leaves the European Union without a deal on Oct. 31, the CBI said.</p><p>"Five successive months of falling volumes tells its own story about the tough conditions retailers are having to operate in," the CBI's chief economist, Rain Newton-Smith, said.</p><p></p><p>(Reporting by David Milliken, editing by Andy Bruce)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>