<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8e694059-495e-497b-855d-19c5143447bb" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Chelsea Manning-Maryland Senate,CORRECTIVE</title><summary>BETHESDA, Md. (AP) — In a story Jan. 18 about Chelsea Manning running for the U.S. Senate in Maryland, The Associated Press reported erroneously that Manning filed in Montgomery County. She filed at the Maryland State Board of Elections in...</summary><sourceId>f5c3dd51-1afe-45a0-5a08-87f776298d0c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL0523%limit%r%BC-US--Chelsea Manning-Maryland Senate,CORRECTIVE;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Correction: Chelsea Manning-Maryland Senate story</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Editors who used BC-US--Chelsea Manning-Maryland Senate, sent Jan. 18 and datelined in Bethesda, Md., are asked to use the following story.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">BETHESDA, Md. (AP) — In a story Jan. 18 about Chelsea Manning running for the U.S. Senate in Maryland, The Associated Press reported erroneously that Manning filed in Montgomery County. She filed at the Maryland State Board of Elections in Annapolis.</p><p xmlns="">A corrected version of the story is below:</p><p xmlns="">Chelsea Manning officially files for US Senate race</p><p xmlns="">Chelsea Manning has officially filed to run for U.S. Senate in the 2018 Maryland Democratic primary</p><p xmlns="">BETHESDA, Md. (AP) — Chelsea Manning has officially filed to run for the U.S. Senate in the 2018 Maryland Democratic primary.</p><p xmlns="">The state elections board website says Manning filed Thursday. Manning also tweeted a photo Thursday evening saying she is officially on the ballot.</p><p xmlns="">The transgender woman, known as Bradley Manning when she was convicted in 2013 of leaking more than 700,000 classified documents, was released from military prison in May after a 35-year sentence was commuted. President Barack Obama commuted her sentence to time served plus 120 days in the final days of his administration.</p><p xmlns="">U.S. Sen. Ben Cardin told The Associated Press on Tuesday that he looks forward to a "strong campaign" against Manning or any other contenders. Cardin won his seat in an open race in 2006.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>