<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="141da8f0-3063-44c5-a124-3bd1c44486f2" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV27</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV27,5431</summary><sourceId>659149a7-80ec-4849-849a-16db8f995f43</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9208%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV27;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV27</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV27,5431</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv27</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend, Jan. 27-28</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 28</hl2><p xmlns="">1901 — The American League is founded. The league plans for a 140-game schedule, set player rosters at 14 and recognizes the Players Protective Association, the players' union.</p><p xmlns="">1943 — Max Bentley of the Chicago Black Hawks has four goals and three assists in a 10-1 rout of the New York Rangers. Bentley scored all four goals and an assist in the third period. Max's brother, Doug, has four assists in the third period.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Monte Irvin and Ford Smith are signed by the New York Giants. They are the first black players to sign with the club.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Wayne Gretzky's record 51-game scoring streak is halted as the Angeles Kings post a 4-2 victory. Over the 51 games, Gretzky scored 61 goals and 92 assists.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — The San Francisco 49ers beat the Denver Broncos 55-10 in the most lopsided Super Bowl. The 49ers are the first repeat NFL champion in a decade and tie the Pittsburgh Steelers with four Super Bowl wins.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Brett Hull becomes the second player in NHL history to score 50 goals in 50 games more than once in a career when the St. Louis Blues tie the Los Angeles Kings 3-3.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Baltimore's brazen defense backs up its bragging by beating the New York Giants 34-7 in the Super Bowl. The Ravens intercept Kerry Collins four times, the final pick returned 49 yards for a touchdown by Duane Starks.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Amelie Mauresmo wins her first Grand Slam singles title when Justine Henin-Hardenne retires in the second set of their Australian Open final because of stomach pain. Mauresmo led 6-1, 2-0.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Roger Federer captures his 10th Grand Slam singles title without dropping a set at the Australian Open, beating Fernando Gonzalez 7-6 (2), 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Towson ends its NCAA record 41-game losing streak with a 66-61 victory over North Carolina Wilmington. The victory is the first career win at Towson for coach Pat Skerry and the Tigers' first win since a win at La Salle on Dec. 29, 2010.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Calling the NCAA a dictatorship, Northwestern quarterback Kain Colter and the United Steelworkers announce plans to form the first labor union for college athletes. Colter details the College Athletes Players Association at a news conference in Chicago, flanked by leaders of Steelworkers union that agree to pay legal bills for the effort.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Serena Williams wins her record 23rd Grand Slam singles title with a 6-4, 6-4 victory over her older sister Venus in the Australian Open final.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Arrogate beats California Chrome again, winning the $12 million Pegasus World Cup in his rival's last race before retirement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 29</hl2><p xmlns="">1950 — In an Associated Press poll of sports writers and broadcasters, Jack Dempsey is voted the greatest fighter of the past 50 years. Dempsey received 251 votes to 104 for Joe Louis.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — The St. Louis Cardinals give Stan Musial a contract for $100,000, making him the highest paid player in the National League.</p><p xmlns="">1963 — Eleven players and six officials are elected to the Pro Football Hall of Fame. Jim Thorpe, Red Grange, Bronco Nagurski, Sammy Baugh, Dutch Clark, Johnny McNally, Ernie Nevers, Mel Hein, Pete Henry, Cal Hubbard and Don Hutson are the players. The six officials are Bert Bell, Joe Carr, George Halas, Curly Lambeau, Tim Mara and George Preston.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Hal Greer of Philadelphia becomes the sixth player in NBA history to score 20,000 points as the 76ers lose to Milwaukee 142-118.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Bryan Trottier of the New York Islanders scores his 1,000th point with a goal in a 4-4 tie with the Minnesota North Stars.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Julio Cesar Chavez suffers his first loss in 91 fights when Frankie Randall knocks him down in the 11th round and wins the WBC super lightweight championship on a split decision.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Brian Himmler rolls two perfect games to take the lead after the first two rounds of qualifying at the PBA's Columbia 300 Open.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Utah's Karl Malone becomes the third player in NBA history to score 30,000 points when he makes a layup with 8:53 left in the third quarter of a 96-94 loss to Minnesota.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Serena Williams fends off six break points in the fifth game of the second set, then wills herself to overcome an aching back in a 2-6, 6-3, 6-0 victory over Lindsay Davenport in the Australian Open final.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Irina Slutskaya joins the elite company of Katarina Witt and Sonja Henie by winning a sixth title at the European Figure Skating Championships.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Roger Federer wins his seventh Grand Slam title, overcoming an early challenge from unseeded Marcos Baghdatis to win the Australian Open 5-7, 7-5, 6-0, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Bernard Lagat wins his eighth Wanamaker Mile at 103rd Millrose Games in New York. Lagat, who finishes in 3:56.34, had shared the record with Irish great Eamonn Coghlan.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Lydia Ko becomes the youngest person ever to win a professional golf tour event by winning the Bing Lee/Samsung Women's NSW Open on the ALPG Tour. She is 14 and 8 months, one year younger than the previous youngest person ever to win a professional golf tour event, Japan's Ryo Ishikawa.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Novak Djokovic outlasts Rafael Nadal to defend his Australian Open title in the longest ever Grand Slam final and becomes the fifth man to win three straight majors in the Open Era. Djokovic completes a 5-hour, 53-minute 5-7, 6-4, 6-2, 6-7 (5), 7-5 victory over Nadal at 1:37 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Ben Scrivens sets an NHL record for saves in a regular-season shutout with 59 in a spectacular performance that help the Edmonton Oilers beat the San Jose Sharks 3-0.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Roger Federer wins his 18th major title by beating Rafael Nadal 6-4, 3-6, 6-1, 3-6, 6-3 to capture the Australian Open.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 30</hl2><p xmlns="">1926 — The major league rules committee mandates that pitchers must have access to a rosin bag.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — UCLA starts its 88-game winning streak with a 74-61 win over UC Santa Barbara.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — John Riggins rushes for a Super Bowl-record 166 yards on 38 carries to spark the Washington Redskins to a come-from-behind, 27-17 victory over the Miami Dolphins. For Riggins, the game's MVP, it's his fourth consecutive 100-yard rushing game during the playoffs, also a record.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Jockey Mike Smith wins six races in one day at Aqueduct Racetrack for the second time in the month. His first six-winner day at Aqueduct was on Jan. 13.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Monica Seles beats Steffi Graf 4-6, 6-3, 6-2 to capture her third straight Australian Open.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — The Dallas Cowboys, behind MVP Emmitt Smith and safety James Washington, beats Buffalo 30-13 for their second straight NFL title while giving the Bills four straight Super Bowl losses.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Magic Johnson finishes with 19 points, 10 assists and eight rebounds in the Los Angeles Lakers' 128-118 victory over Golden State. It Johnson's first regular-season game back from a 4 1/2-season retirement.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Martina Hingis wins her fifth Grand Slam title and third-straight Australian Open with a 6-2, 6-3 victory over France's Amelie Mauresmo.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Daron Rahlves wins the super giant slalom, the first American to capture the event at the world championships.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Teemu Selanne scores two goals for his 1,000th career point in Anaheim's 4-3 overtime victory against Los Angeles.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Serena Williams puts an end to Justine Henin's hopes of a Grand Slam title in her return from retirement with a 6-4, 3-6, 6-2 victory in the Australian Open final.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — MVP DeAngelo Hall has one of his team's five interceptions and returns a fumble 34 yards for a touchdown to help the NFC match a Pro Bowl scoring record in a 55-41 victory over the AFC. AFC quarterbacks Philip Rivers, Peyton Manning and Matt Cassel each throw first-half interceptions to help the NFC blow open a 42-0 lead.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Loui Eriksson's second goal, an empty-netter at 18:49 of the third period, helps seal an 11-10 victory for Team Lidstrom against Team Staal in the NHL All-Star Game.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — The Phoenix Open continues without Tiger Woods and Phil Mickelson. The biggest shock is Woods, who bogeys on his last hole for an 82, the worst score in his two decades as a pro. Mickelson shoots 76 and misses the cut by two shots.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Angelique Kerber upsets Serena Williams 6-4, 3-6, 6-4 to win the Australian Open title, ending the six-time champion's unbeaten streak in finals at Melbourne Park.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 31</hl2><p xmlns="">1920 — Joe Malone of the Quebec Bulldogs scores an NHL record seven goals in a 10-6 victory over the Toronto St. Patricks.</p><p xmlns="">1941 — Joe Louis knocks out Red Burman in the fifth round at Madison Square Garden to retain the world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1950 — High school pitcher Paul Pettit signs with the Pirates for a record $100,000. To do so, Pittsburgh has to purchase his contract from a film producer who had signed Pettit to an exclusive contract as an athlete/actor.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — The Washington Redskins score 35 points in the second quarter to overcome a 10-0 deficit and beat the Denver Broncos 42-10 in the Super Bowl. MVP Doug Williams passes for four touchdowns and a record 340 yards. Timmy Smith rushes for a record 204 yards.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Michael Adams of the Denver Nuggets scores a career-high 45 points, hands out 12 assists and grabs 11 rebounds in a 123-119 win over New Jersey. The 5-foot-11 guard becomes the shortest player in the NBA to get a triple-double.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — The Dallas Cowboys win the Super Bowl, beating Buffalo 52-17 and giving the Bills their third straight loss in the title game, a league record.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Martina Hingis, 17, becomes the youngest player in the Open era to defend a Grand Slam title, capturing her second Australian Open with a 6-3, 6-3 victory over Conchita Martinez.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — John Elway gets his second straight Super Bowl ring, weaving his magic for the final time during the Denver Broncos' 34-19 win over the Atlanta Falcons.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Justine Henin-Hardenne wins her third Grand Slam title and extends her dominance in major finals against countrywoman Kim Clijsters with a 6-3, 4-6, 6-3 win in the Australian Open women's title match.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Serena Williams routs Dinara Safina 6-0, 6-3 to win the Australian Open — her 10th Grand Slam title — and return to the No. 1 ranking.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Roger Federer easily beats Andy Murray 6-3, 6-4, 7-6 (11) for a fourth Australian Open championship and his 16th Grand Slam title overall.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — For the first time since the inception of the WTA rankings in 1975, the top 10 players hail from 10 different countries. With Danish player Caroline Wozniacki remaining at No. 1, the top 11 women are from 11 different countries.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Serena Williams wins her 19th Grand Slam title and extendeds her decade-long domination of Maria Sharapova with a commanding 6-3, 7-6 (5) win.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Teen star Lydia Ko becomes the youngest golfer of either gender to reach No. 1 in the world ranking. The 17-year-old shares a second place finish at the LPGA Tour's season opener, where she finishes a shot behind Na Yeon Choi in the Coates Golf Championship.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 1</hl2><p xmlns="">1913 — Jim Thorpe, star of the 1912 Olympics, signs to play baseball with the New York Giants.</p><p xmlns="">1914 — The Chicago White Sox and New York Giants play an exhibition game to promote baseball in Egypt. The game ends in a 3-3 tie.</p><p xmlns="">1956 — Hayes Alan Jenkins leads the United States in a sweep of Olympic men's figure skating in Cortina d'Ampezzo, Italy. The silver goes to Ronald Robertson, and Jenkins' younger brother, David, wins the bronze.</p><p xmlns="">1964 — Bobby Rousseau of the Montreal Canadiens scores five goals in a 9-3 victory over the Detroit Red Wings.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Utah guard John Stockton becomes the NBA's career assist leader, setting up Karl Malone with 6:30 left in the first half of the Jazz's 129-88 victory over Denver. Stockton's 9,922nd assist moves him ahead of Magic Johnson.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — David Graham wins the longest playoff in Senior PGA Tour history, beating Dave Stockton with a birdie on the 10th extra hole in the Royal Caribbean Classic.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Regina Jacobs becomes the first woman to break four minutes in the indoor 1,500 meters at the Boston Indoor Games. Jacobs finishes in 3:59.98 to break the world record of 4:00.27 set by Romanian Doina Melinte in 1990.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — The New England Patriots win their second Super Bowl in three seasons after Adam Vinatieri kicks a field goal with 4 seconds left to lift his team to a 32-29 victory over the Carolina Panthers.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — New York's Epiphanny Prince scores 113 points for Murry Bergtraum High School in a 137-32 win over Brandeis High School, breaking a girls' national prep record previously held by Hall of Famer Cheryl Miller.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Jockey Russell Baze is the first to win 10,000th races in North America when he leads Two Step Cat to victory in the third race at Golden Gate Fields.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Ben Roethlisberger and the Pittsburgh offense end a Super Bowl of incredible swings with a final-minute touchdown for a historic victory, 27-23 over the Arizona Cardinals. Santonio Holmes makes a brilliant 6-yard catch deep in the right corner of the end zone with 35 seconds remaining, lifting the Steelers to a record-setting sixth Super Bowl win.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Ray Guy becomes the first punter elected to the Pro Football Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Oregon Institute of Technology men's basketball coach Danny Miles becomes the second men's coach at a four-year program to reach 1,000 career wins with a 71-51 victory over Corban.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Tom Brady throws for four touchdowns and Malcolm Butler intercepts Russell Wilson's pass in the end zone with 20 seconds left, helping New England hold on to beat Seattle 28-24 for their fourth Super Bowl title.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — For the first time in more than eight years, Duke is not in The Associated Press men's basketball Top 25. The Blue Devils (15-6) had lost four of five, including two home games. They had been in every men's poll since the preseason rankings of 2007-08.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 2</hl2><p xmlns="">1876 — The National League forms, consisting of teams in Philadelphia, Hartford, Boston, Chicago, Cincinnati, Louisville, St. Louis and New York.</p><p xmlns="">1936 — Ty Cobb, Babe Ruth, Honus Wagner, Christy Mathewson, and Walter Johnson are the first members elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1954 — Bevo Francis of Rio Grande College scores 113 points in a 134-91 victory over Hillsdale. Francis breaks his own record for small colleges (84), set two weeks earlier against Alliance College.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Using a fiberglass pole, John Uelses becomes the first man to vault more than 16 feet, indoors or out. Uelses, a Marine Corps corporal, clears 16¼ during the Millrose Games at Madison Square Garden in New York.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — The American Basketball Association begins operation with George Mikan as commissioner. The league has 10 teams in two divisions, with franchises in New York, Pittsburgh, Indianapolis, New Orleans, Dallas, Houston, Kansas City, Oakland and Anaheim.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Toronto's Ian Turnbull scores five goals to set an NHL record for defensemen as the Maple Leafs beat the Detroit Red Wings 9-1.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — New Hampshire's men's basketball team snaps its 32-game losing streak at home with a 72-56 win over Holy Cross. The NCAA-record streak started on Feb. 9, 1988.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Lenny Wilkens gets his 900th NBA victory as the Atlanta Hawks beat the Orlando Magic 118-99. Wilkens runs his regular-season mark to 900-760, trailing only Red Auerbach's 938 in NBA regular-season victories.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Austria's Hermann Maier and Norway's Lasse Kjus ski to an unprecedented tie in the men's super-G as the World Alpine Ski Championships get off to a roaring start.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Stacy Dragila takes center stage at the Millrose Games in New York, breaking her world indoor pole vault record by half-an-inch with a 15-2 1/4 vault.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Kobe Bryant breaks the current Madison Square Garden record with 61 points to lead the Los Angeles Lakers to a 126-117 victory over New York. Bryant is 19-for-31 from the field, including 3-of-6 from beyond the arc, and hits all 20 of his free throw attempts to eclipse the previous visitor record of 55 held by Michael Jordan and the overall record of 60 set by Bernard King.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Sam Gagner has four goals and four assists in the NHL's first eight-point game in 23 years, and the Edmonton Oilers beat the Chicago Blackhawks 8-4.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — California Institute of Technology's baseball team ends a 228-game losing streak with a 9-7 victory against Pacifica, the Beavers' first win in nearly 10 years. Caltech hadn't won since Feb. 15, 2003, 5-4 against Cal State-Monterey Bay.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The Seattle Seahawks win their first Super Bowl title, crushing the favored Denver Broncos 43-8. The Seahawks led 36-0 before Denver finally scored on the last play of the third quarter.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Patrick Marleau scores his 500th career goal, Chris Tierney tallies twice and San Jose beat Vancouver 4-1. Marleau becomes the 45th player in NHL history to reach 500 goals, scoring in the first period on a power play.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 3</hl2><p xmlns="">1944 — Syd Howe of the Detroit Red Wings scores six goals in a 12-6 victory over the New York Rangers.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — Larry Bird hits the first 3-point shot in the history of the NBA All-Star Game. Bird' 3 came in overtime as the East team outscores the West 16-8 in the overtime for a 144-136 win.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Skier Steve Mahre, twin brother of overall champion Phil Mahre, becomes the first American man to win a gold medal in Olympic or World Championship competition when he edges Sweden's Ingemar Stenmark by 0.51 seconds in the giant slalom.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Bill Shoemaker, the world's winningest jockey, finishes fourth on Patchy Groundfog in his final ride at Santa Anita. The 58-year-old Shoemaker finishes his 40-year career with $123,375,524 in earnings, a record 8,833 wins, 6,136 seconds and 4,987 thirds in 40,350 starts.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Visiting teams are 7-0, marking the first time in NBA history road clubs go undefeated on a day with more than five games. Expansion Toronto beats the Los Angeles Clippers 119-113 in overtime, Seattle defeats Houston 104-103 in overtime, Boston downs Miami 100-99, Portland tops Philadelphia 96-85, Sacramento defeats Detroit 94-85, Cleveland tops Milwaukee 111-88 and Minnesota downs Dallas 105-96.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — World Wrestling Federation mastermind Vince McMahon unveils his latest creation: the XFL, a new pro football league.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — One year later, the XFL muscles its way onto the national sports scene with its first two games. With exuberant cheerleaders and trash-talking players sharing center stage, the Las Vegas Outlaws beat the New York/New Jersey Hitmen 19-0, while the Orlando Rage beat the Chicago Enforcers 33-29 before a crowd of 35,603 in Orlando.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Martin Brodeur becomes the third goaltender in NHL history to reach 100 shutouts as New Jersey blanks Carolina 3-0. Brodeur joins Terry Sawchuk (115) and George Hainsworth (102).</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The Baltimore Ravens survive a power outage at the Super Bowl to edge the San Francisco 49ers 34-31. Jacoby Jones returns the second-half kickoff 108 yards, a Super Bowl record, to give Baltimore a 28-6 lead. Moments later, lights lining the Superdome fade. When action resumes 34 minutes later, Colin Kaepernick and the 49ers score 17 consecutive points, getting as close as 31-29. Baltimore stops San Francisco on fourth-and-goal from the 5 with under 2 minutes left when Kaepernick's pass sails beyond Michael Crabtree in the end zone.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Tara VanDerveer becomes the second NCAA women's coach to reach 1,000 career victories, when No. 8 Stanford beats Southern Cal 58-42 to give the Hall of Famer a major milestone in front of the home crowd at Maples Pavilion. VanDerveer joins the late Pat Summitt, with 1,098 wins to her name, as the only other women's coach in the elite club. Duke's Mike Krzyzewski is the only Division I men's coach with 1,000.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Boston's Isaiah Thomas scores 17 of his 38 points in the fourth quarter, and the Celtics beat the Los Angeles Lakers 113-107. Boston and Los Angeles began the night with 3,252 wins, tied for the most in NBA history. Before their loss, the Lakers held at least a share of the league's victories mark since 2001.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>