<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="989747c5-7d9b-401c-9d6d-8df90325c043" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T120652Z:TX-PAR-EJM37:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T120652Z:TX-PAR-EJM37:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T120652Z-TX-PAR-EJM37.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Tennis</item><item>ATP</item><item>CHN</item><item>Zhuhai</item><item>Nick Kyrgios</item><item>Andreas Seppi</item><item>Rafael Nadal</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Kyrgios blames 'clicking shoulder' for first-round exit</title><authors></authors><summary>Nick Kyrgios fears he could face several weeks out after struggling with what he said was a "clicking" shoulder in a limp first-round exit at the Zhuhai Championships on Wednesday.The 24-year-old Australian, who has been accused of tanking matches in the past, served underarm on one occasion and led the veteran Italian Andreas Seppi 4-1 in the first set.But the unpredictable firebrand went down 7-6 (7/5), 6-1 in southern China after his game spectacularly fell apart.Kyrgios, who has had...</summary><city>Zhuhai</city><country>CHN</country><xmlText><p>Nick Kyrgios fears he could face several weeks out after struggling with what he said was a "clicking" shoulder in a limp first-round exit at the Zhuhai Championships on Wednesday.</p><p>The 24-year-old Australian, who has been accused of tanking matches in the past, served underarm on one occasion and led the veteran Italian Andreas Seppi 4-1 in the first set.</p><p>But the unpredictable firebrand went down 7-6 (7/5), 6-1 in southern China after his game spectacularly fell apart.</p><p>Kyrgios, who has had numerous run-ins with tennis authorities down the years, said that he was "struggling a lot" -- but he still played doubles soon after.</p><p>"I was battling with a bit of a shoulder/collar bone injury," said the 27th-ranked Kyrgios, a colourful but controversial figure.</p><p>"At this rate I'm not thinking about playing until my shoulder's -- or I don't even know what it is -- but until my front of my shoulder feels better and I can serve," he added, saying his right shoulder had been "clicking".</p><p>"I mean the reason I lost today was because I couldn't serve. </p><p>"If I could serve, it would have been a pretty routine win for me, to be honest."</p><p>Asked if he could sit out the next few weeks or even the rest of the season, Kyrgios replied: "For sure, I mean at this rate I wouldn't be surprised. </p><p>"I wasn't able to even serve at a reasonable pace.</p><p>"I'm probably not going to bother playing until I can get it right again," he added.</p><p>Kyrgios elicited a few giggles from a sparse crowd in Zhuhai with an underarm serve in the first set.</p><p>Coasting 3-1 and 40-0 up, Kyrgios served weakly into the net, before surging into a 4-1 lead.</p><p>But the Australian faded alarmingly from there and his previously dominant serve collapsed.</p><p>Kyrgios, who appears to revel as the "bad boy" of men's tennis, repeatedly felt his shoulder and his game disintegrated as lost the first-set tie break.</p><p>The second set was a non-contest as Seppi, 35, ranked 74th in the world, strolled into round two in 65 minutes.</p><p>Kyrgios said that he still hopes to play for Australia in the Davis Cup in November.</p><p>"So until now and then I've got a lot of time, I can rest, recover, get my shoulder right," he said.</p><p>Kyrgios has long divided tennis fans.</p><p>He is an undoubted talent but has a long list of misdemeanours including rowing with umpires and spectators, and throwing an on-court chair.</p><p>The Australian says he deploys underarm serves for tactical reasons, but Spanish player Rafael Nadal accused him of "lacking respect".</p><p>pst/rbu</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>