<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="53ca2a81-9305-4240-8d16-8a8d0ce2c93f" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_S8N1QP03K:2132067437</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_S8N1QP03K:2132067437</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T072515Z_2132067437_S8N1QP03K_RTRMADT_0_BRITAIN-EU-CORBYN-URGENT.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UK Labour leader Corbyn says priority is preventing no-deal Brexit</title><summary>BRITAIN-EU/CORBYN (URGENT):UK Labour leader Corbyn says priority is preventing no-deal Brexit</summary><xmlText><p>UK Labour leader Corbyn says priority is preventing no-deal Brexit</p><p>LONDON, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Britain's opposition Labour Party leader Jeremy Corbyn said on Wednesday that it would be appropriate to trigger a vote of no confidence in Prime Minister Boris Johnson only when a no-deal Brexit has clearly been averted.</p><p>Corbyn said his priority was averting a no-deal Brexit with legislation and only when that was clear would he be ready to trigger a vote of no confidence. He said he would be happy to have an election once no-deal Brexit had been averted.</p><p>"Quite simply our first priority is to prevent a no-deal exit from the EU," Corbyn told BBC Radio 4.</p><p>"At that poing it would be appropriate to move a vote of no confidence to force the prime minister to resign."</p><p>He said Johnson should apologise to Queen Elizabeth and to the British people after the Supreme Court ruled he had acted unlawfully by suspending parliament for five weeks in the run-up to Brexit. (Reporting by Estelle Shirbon; writing by Guy Faulconbridge)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>