<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b777a69b-d90e-4b76-bff2-68eff01b6ef1" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T085641Z:TX-PAR-EJH30:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T085641Z:TX-PAR-EJH30:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T085641Z-TX-PAR-EJH30.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>AFP</item><item>news</item><item>agenda</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>International 7-Day News Agenda</title><authors></authors><summary>Go to https://agenda.afp.com to consult AFP AgendaContact us on contact-agenda@afp.comAFP International 7-Day News AgendaPlease note that all times are in GMT. For full details of our coverage of top stories, please see our regularly updated News Advisory(+) : Event added in the last 24 hours.(*) : Event updated in the last 24 hours.WEDNESDAY, SEPTEMBER 25, 2019Asia-PacificHONG KONG (China) - Activists charged with rioting appear at court, protesters rally outside (0630 GMT) LIVE VIDEO....</summary><city>Hong Kong</city><country>CHN</country><xmlText><p>Go to https://agenda.afp.com to consult AFP Agenda</p><p>Contact us on contact-agenda@afp.com</p><p>Please note that all times are in GMT. For full details of our coverage of top stories, please see our regularly updated News Advisory</p><p>(+) : Event added in the last 24 hours.</p><p>(*) : Event updated in the last 24 hours.</p><p></p><p>WEDNESDAY, SEPTEMBER 25, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>HONG KONG (China) - Activists charged with rioting appear at court, protesters rally outside (0630 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO.</p><p>TELUK BAHANG (Malaysia) - World's longest tube water slide to be unveiled at Escape theme park VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>Europe</p><p>(*) MONACO (Principality of Monaco) - IPCC press conference to present special report on the ocean and cryosphere (0900 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>(+) LONDON (United Kingdom) - Parliament reopens after Supreme Court strikes down suspension (1030 GMT) VIDEO. PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) MOSCOW (Russia) - Venezuela's Maduro visits, meets Putin PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) STOCKHOLM (Sweden) - Rights Livelihood Prize winner announced</p><p>(*) BERLIN (Germany) - National forest summit (1130 GMT)</p><p>PARIS (France) - Verdict in defamation case filed against French #MeToo founder (1300 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO.</p><p>BRIGHTON (United Kingdom) - Labour Party annual conference VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>BAIKONUR (Kazakhstan) - Astronauts from US, Russia, UAE blast off for ISS PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>MONACO (Principality of Monaco) - Monaco Yacht Show (0800 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>(+) BRUSSELS (Belgium) - EU Parliament Brexit steering committee meets (1300 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO.</p><p>TARBES (France) - Verdict in trial of performance artist Deborah de Robertis over nude pose in Lourdes sanctuary (2200 GMT)</p><p>MADRID (Spain) - Ryanair pilots go on strike (To 29)</p><p>PARIS (France) - Paris Fashion Week Womenswear (To October 1)</p><p>North America</p><p>UNITED NATIONS (United States) - UN General Assembly general debate PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO. (To 30)</p><p>UNITED NATIONS (United States) - Iranian President Rouhani addresses UN General Assembly PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>VANCOUVER (Canada) - New extradition hearing of Huawei top official Meng Wanzhou, accused in the US of violating Iran sanctions PICTURE. VIDEO. (To October 4)</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Bloomberg Global Business Forum PICTURE.</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Day two of the UN General Assembly general debate PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) NEW YORK (United States) - Foreign ministers from signatory countries to the Iran nuclear deal JCPOA meet PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) UNITED NATIONS (United States) - Trump meets Japan PM Abe on sidelines of UNGA PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) UNITED NATIONS (United States) - Trump meets his Ukrainian counterpart Volodymyr Zelensky PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) UNITED NATIONS (United States) - Trump holds presser on sidelines of UNGA PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(+) WASHINGTON (United States) - Expected publication of Trump call with Ukrainian President Zelensky amid whistleblower scandal VIDEO.</p><p>LOS ANGELES (United States) - Darth Vader's mask among Hollywood artefacts being auctioned (To 26)</p><p>SEATTLE (United States) - Amazon unveils new Alexa and Echo products VIDEO.</p><p>LOS ANGELES (United States) - Annual AirWorks conference on drones PICTURE. VIDEO. (To 26)</p><p>Middle East and North Africa</p><p>(+) ALGIERS (Algeria) - Algeria court sentences Bouteflika brother to 15 years</p><p>DUBAI (United Arab Emirates) - Cityscape Global property exhibition (0430 GMT) VIDEO. PICTURE. (To 27)</p><p>(+) DOHA (Qatar) - Students march against climate change in rare protest (0930 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>(*) DUBAI (United Arab Emirates) - Takeoff of the UAE's first astronaut into space (1200 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>RABAT (Morocco) - Contemporary Art Biennale (To December 18)</p><p>(+) TUNIS (Tunisia) - Court rules on request to release jailed presidential contender Nabil Karoui VIDEO.</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>SOUTH AFRICA - Prince Harry, Meghan on southern Africa regional tour PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO. (To October 2)</p><p>(+) LILONGWE (Malawi) - Fresh post-election protests against President Mutharika's rule (To 27)</p><p>LUANDA (Angola) - Corruption, money laundering trial of son of ex-president Dos Santos begins (To October 2)</p><p>Latin America</p><p>LIMA (Peru) - Constitutional court rules on opposition leader Keiko Fujimori's request for release from jail VIDEO.</p><p>(+) BRASÍLIA (Brazil) - Supreme Court hearing on case that could lead to Lula's conviction being overturned VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - Protest ahead of fifth anniversary of disappearance of 43 students in southern Mexico PICTURE.</p><p>(+) MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - Oscar-winning director Alejandro Gonzalez Inarritu gives a master class in his native Mexico</p><p>Sports</p><p>(*) DOHA (Qatar) - Sebastian Coe set to be re-elected IAAF president, as only candidate VIDEO.</p><p>JAPAN - Rugby World Cup, with New Zealand going for third straight title LIVE VIDEO. GRAPHIC. VIDEOGRAPHICS. (To November 2)</p><p>THURSDAY, SEPTEMBER 26, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>SEOUL (South Korea) - Bulgaria's PM Boyko Borissov visits PICTURE.</p><p>SHENZHEN (China) - Huawei founder Ren Zhengfei headlines panel discussion, answers reporter questions (0700 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO.</p><p>(*) HONG KONG (China) - Leader Carrie Lam holds first 'dialogue session' (1130 GMT) LIVE VIDEO. PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>Europe</p><p>MONACO (Principality of Monaco) - Monte Carlo Gala for the Global Ocean, with Robert Redford as guest of honour (1700 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>(*) BRUSSELS (Belgium) - Japanese PM Shinzo Abe visits for talks with the EU PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO. (To 27)</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia) - Moscow City Court considers appeal of actor jailed in protest crackdown (0700 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>(+) LUXEMBOURG (Luxembourg) - Opinion of EU Court's Advocate General on case involving a hot coffee tipped over on a flight (0730 GMT)</p><p>BERGEN (Norway) - Rafto Prize for human rights awarded (0800 GMT)</p><p>GENEVA (Switzerland) - Libra cryptocurrency association director holds presser on new digital training programme (0830 GMT) VIDEO.</p><p>MARGATE (United Kingdom) - Press preview of Turner Prize 2019 shortlist (1000 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>FRANKFURT AM MAIN (Germany) - Merkel attends conference marking 70th anniversary of Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung daily (1115 GMT) LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>FRANKFURT AM MAIN (Germany) - ECB head Draghi speech on risks faced by eurozone (1330 GMT)</p><p>GENEVA (Switzerland) - Geneva switches off street lighting to raise awareness about impact of light pollution (1830 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>North America</p><p>WASHINGTON (United States) - Acting Director of National Intelligence Joseph Maguire due to testify in US Congress (1300 GMT)</p><p>SAN FRANCISCO (United States) - New Uber products launch VIDEO.</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Iranian President Rouhani set to hold press conference PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>CHOBE (Botswana) - Prince Harry visits Chobe National park PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>JOHANNESBURG (South Africa) - UN expert on albinism holds press conference (1000 GMT)</p><p>(+) BANJUL (Gambia) - Gambia fear the worst after the collapse of travel firm Thomas Cook, (1500 GMT)</p><p>Latin America</p><p>(+) MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - Oscar-winning director Alejandro Gonzalez Inarritu receives an honorary degree in his native Mexico</p><p>MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - Protest to mark five years since disappearance of 43 students in southern Mexico VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>Sports</p><p>BRAZIL - Football: Copa Sudamericana 2019 - Semi final Second Leg (To 27)</p><p>BEIJING (China) - Press conference by former NBA star Jeremy Lin who has signed with Beijing Shougang Ducks (0700 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>FRIDAY, SEPTEMBER 27, 2019</p><p>Europe</p><p>(+) THE HAGUE (Netherlands) - March to demand action against climate change (1100 GMT) GRAPHIC. VIDEOGRAPHICS. VIDEO. PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>PORTUGAL - Ryanair cabin crew strike</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - Banksy's 'Devolved Parliament' auctioned ahead of Brexit deadline VIDEO.</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - Brexit Party holds final rally after national tour (1800 GMT) PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO. VIDEO.</p><p>North America</p><p>MONTREAL (Canada) - Activist Greta Thunberg attends climate march (1600 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - New York Film Festival (To October 13)</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - 'The Irishman', new film by Martin Scorsese with Robert De Niro and Al Pacino, premieres (1900 GMT)</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Release of 'Blue World', a lost John Coltrane album</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Sentencing hearing for Ali Kourani, American of Lebanese descent and Hezbollah member convicted for planning attacks</p><p>OTTAWA (Canada) - RCMP intelligence officer accused of stealing sensitive documents to appear in court by video link for a bail hearing</p><p>Middle East and North Africa</p><p>RIYADH (Saudi Arabia) - S&amp;P issues its updated rating for Saudi Arabia</p><p>EGYPT - Businessman Mohamed Aly calls for million-man anti-Sisi protests PICTURE. VIDEO. (To 28)</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>(+) SOUTH AFRICA - Banking sector employees hold strikes over job cuts</p><p>HUAMBO (Angola) - Prince Harry meets mine clearers in southern Angola PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>DAKAR (Senegal) - Inauguration of new Massalikoul Djinane mosque, said to be West Africa's largest VIDEO.</p><p>Sports</p><p>DOHA (Qatar) - World Athletics Championships VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO. GRAPHIC. (To October 6)</p><p>BARCELONA (Spain) - Court hearing in case brought by Neymar against FC Barcelona (0800 GMT) VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>SATURDAY, SEPTEMBER 28, 2019</p><p>Worldwide</p><p>WORLD - International Safe Abortion Day</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>AFGHANISTAN - Presidential election PICTURE. GRAPHIC. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>HONG KONG (China) - Fifth anniversary of pro-democracy Umbrella Movement PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>(*) PALU (Indonesia) - Anniversary of Sulawesi island quake-tsunami disaster that killed more than 4,000 people PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>Europe</p><p>GERMANY - Countrywide protests to defend women's right to safe abortion</p><p>(*) STOCKHOLM (Sweden) - 25 years since sinking of MS Estonia in Baltic Sea, leaving 852 people dead (0900 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>North America</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Queen + Adam Lambert headline Global Citizen festival</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>HARARE (Zimbabwe) - Opposition MDC holds 20th anniversary celebrations at stadium PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>Latin America</p><p>BUENOS AIRES (Argentina) - President Macri begins 30-day nationwide campaign tour ahead of October vote (2000 GMT) VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>(*) MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - Rally for International Safe Abortion Day VIDEO.</p><p>Sports</p><p>(+) HARROGATE (United Kingdom) - Road cycling World Championships PICTURE.</p><p>SOCHI (Russia) - F2 racing championship, round 11, with Mick Schumacher (To 29)</p><p>SUNDAY, SEPTEMBER 29, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>TAIPEI (Taiwan) - Civil society groups rally in support of Hong Kong protests (0700 GMT)</p><p>Europe</p><p>AUSTRIA - General election (0500 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO. GRAPHIC. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>MANCHESTER (United Kingdom) - Conservative Party holds annual conference VIDEO. (To October 2)</p><p>CHÉSEREX (Switzerland) - Auction of Equatorial Guinea leader's son's luxury car collection</p><p>VATICAN CITY (Holy See) - Pope Francis celebrates mass on Catholic Church's World Day of Migrants and Refugees (0830 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>MUNICH (Germany) - Barack Obama delivers speech at Bits &amp; Pretzels start-ups festival (0900 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>(*) MANCHESTER (United Kingdom) - Leftwing People's Assembly Against Austerity protest (1100 GMT)</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia) - Rally in support of political prisoners (1200 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>Middle East and North Africa</p><p>DUBAI (United Arab Emirates) - Dubai Investment Week (0600 GMT) (To October 3)</p><p>Sports</p><p>BERLIN (Germany) - Berlin Marathon, a race which traditionally produces world records (0700 GMT)</p><p>SOCHI (Russia) - Russian Grand Prix, the 16th race of the Formula One season (1110 GMT) PICTURE. GRAPHIC. VIDEOGRAPHICS.</p><p>MONDAY, SEPTEMBER 30, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>BEIJING (China) - Massive new international airport begins operations VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>BEIJING (China) - Wreath laying ceremony in front of the Monument to the People's Heroes at Tiananmen Square VIDEO. GRAPHIC. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>BEIJING (China) - September PMI data (0100 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>KUALA LUMPUR (Malaysia) - Pre-trial hearing for three Goldman Sachs units over 1MDB scandal (0100 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>HONG KONG (China) - Secondary students plan one-day class boycott (0100 GMT)</p><p>BEIJING (China) - Caixin releases independent survey of China's September manufacturing PMI (0145 GMT)</p><p>TOKYO (Japan) - Bank of Japan releases quarterly Tankan survey of business confidence (2350 GMT)</p><p>Europe</p><p>BRAUNSCHWEIG (Germany) - First 'dieselgate' mass court case pitting drivers against Volkswagen opens (0800 GMT) GRAPHIC. PICTURE.</p><p>DRESDEN (Germany) - Trial opens of far-right group Chemnitz Revolution, which planned attacks in Germany (0800 GMT) VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>(+) SOCHI (Russia) - Putin hosts foreign leaders for Valdai Discussion Club PICTURE. VIDEO. (To October 3)</p><p>PARIS (France) - Parliamentary debate on migration GRAPHIC.</p><p>STRASBOURG (France) - Plenary of European Council's parliamentary assembly (To October 4)</p><p>STRASBOURG (France) - European Council's parliamentary assembly awards Vaclav Havel prize for the defence of human rights (1030 GMT)</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - GDP Q2, 2nd estimate (0830 GMT)</p><p>LUXEMBOURG (Luxembourg) - Eurozone unemployment data for August (0900 GMT)</p><p>BRUSSELS (Belgium) - European Parliament holds hearings with EU commissioners-designate (1230 GMT) (To October 8)</p><p>Middle East and North Africa</p><p>(+) RABAT (Morocco) - Trial resumes of journalist Hajar Raissouni for abortion, extra-marital relations</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>LIWONDE NATIONAL PARK (Malawi) - Prince Harry, Meghan pay tribute to UK soldier who died during anti-poaching operation PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>YAOUNDÉ (Cameroon) - 'Major national dialogue' called by President Biya over anglophone regions violence VIDEO. (To October 4)</p><p>Latin America</p><p>BUENOS AIRES (Argentina) - Q1 2019 poverty index (1900 GMT)</p><p>TUESDAY, OCTOBER 1, 2019</p><p>Worldwide</p><p>WORLD - World Cocoa Day</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>BEIJING (China) - Military parade to celebrate 70th anniversary of People's Republic of China VIDEO. GRAPHIC. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>HONG KONG (China) - Government unveils new lightshow to celebrate 70th anniversary of the PRC (1200 GMT)</p><p>HONG KONG (China) - Protesters plan 'dress in black' rallies as communist China marks 70th anniversary (0000 GMT) VIDEO. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>TAIPEI (Taiwan) - Golden Horse Film awards organisers announce nomination list after China's boycott (0600 GMT)</p><p>Europe</p><p>DAX (France) - Duck owner to appear in court over disruptive quacking (1200 GMT) VIDEO. PICTURE.</p><p>GROZNY (Russia) - 20 years since Russian forces launched second Chechen war</p><p>COPENHAGEN (Denmark) - 30th anniversary of world's first gay marriages</p><p>SOCHI (Russia) - Serbia signs free trade deal with Eurasian Economic Union</p><p>SKOPJE (Republic of North Macedonia) - The Economist conference on Balkan EU integration, with Greek ex-PM Tsipras among participants</p><p>LUXEMBOURG (Luxembourg) - Eurozone inflation data for September (0900 GMT)</p><p>PARIS (France) - Court ruling on whether ex-president Sarkozy should face trial in 'Bygmalion' campaign finance case (1200 GMT)</p><p>STRASBOURG (France) - Macron addresses Parliamentary Assembly of Council of Europe (1300 GMT)</p><p>North America</p><p>NEW YORK (United States) - Automakers report quarterly US sales</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>JOHANNESBURG (South Africa) - Nigerian President Buhari visits following wave of xenophobic violence PICTURE. (To 31)</p><p>TANZANIA - Expulsion of Burundian refugees begins</p><p>WEDNESDAY, OCTOBER 2, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>CHRISTCHURCH (New Zealand) - Christchurch mosque shooting accused Brenton Tarrant's case in court for procedural mention</p><p>Europe</p><p>ISTANBUL (Turkey) - US consulate staffer arrested over 2016 coup bid appears in court</p><p>(*) ISTANBUL (Turkey) - Vigil outside Saudi consulate on anniversary of dissident journalist Khashoggi's murder PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>WARSAW (Poland) - Annual Warsaw Security Forum (To 3)</p><p>LÁNY (Czech Republic) - Visegrad Group presidents meet (To 3)</p><p>COURNON-D'AUVERGNE (France) - European Livestock Trade Fair (To 4)</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - London Film Festival 2019 PICTURE. VIDEO. (To 13)</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - Tesco posts half-year results (0600 GMT)</p><p>PARIS (France) - Fijian rugby player Josaia Raisuqe in court on sexual assault charge (0700 GMT)</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia) - Russian Energy Forum (1100 GMT) PICTURE. VIDEO. (To 5)</p><p>North America</p><p>WASHINGTON (United States) - Trump hosts Finland's President Niinisto PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>Middle East and North Africa</p><p>JERUSALEM - Netanyahu appears before Attorney General Avichai Mandelblit for hearing ahead of possible charges on corruption affairs. (To 3)</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa</p><p>JOHANNESBURG (South Africa) - Prince Harry, Meghan visit township PICTURE. LIVE VIDEO.</p><p>Latin America</p><p>MEXICO CITY (Mexico) - March to mark 51st anniversary of Tlatelolco student massacre (2100 GMT) VIDEO.</p><p>Sports</p><p>ARGENTINA - Football: Copa Libertadores 2019 - Semi final First Leg PICTURE. (To 3)</p><p>OITA (Japan) - Rugby: World Cup, 1st round: Pool B New Zealand v Canada (1015 GMT) PICTURE.</p><p>THURSDAY, OCTOBER 3, 2019</p><p>Asia-Pacific</p><p>PHNOM PENH (Cambodia) - Verdict in espionage trial of two Cambodian journalists who worked for Radio Free Asia</p><p>Europe</p><p>DZHEZKAZGAN (Kazakhstan) - US, UAE astronauts, Russian cosmonaut return to earth from ISS PICTURE. VIDEO.</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom) - Hearing for teen accused of throwing French boy from Tate Modern viewing platform</p><p>(+) COUR DE JUSTICE EUROPÉENNE À LUXEMBOURG (Luxembourg) - Top EU court rules on legality of Swiss Franc mortgages in Poland</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia) - Russia jailed over tweet to appeal sentence (0700 GMT) VIDEO.</p><p>North America</p><p>MONTREAL (Canada) - PM Trudeau in French-language debate with main election opponents (0000 GMT)</p><p>Sports</p><p>PARIS (France) - 100th anniversary of Prix de l'Arc de Triomphe, France's premier horse race</p><p></p><p>afp</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>