<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9c7c95b4-cf5d-4fb4-a9e1-e07e2a11df5d" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190924:PYCERL6S9728:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190924:PYCERL6S9728:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYCERL6S972800000_DNMLENf-20190925090995.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>EU Pork Exports to China Are Booming on Deadly Pig Virus</title><authors>Megan Durisin</authors><summary>PYCERL6S9728(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars.  Sign up here. The European Union is shipping pork to China at a breakneck pace, as the Asian country grapples to contain a deadly swine virus that’s led to millions of pig deaths. Exports jumped 45% in the first seven months of the year, approaching the total for all of 2018, EU data show. But there’s a question over how long sales can keep rising -- even with increased demand,...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars.  Sign up here. </p><p>The European Union is shipping pork to China at a breakneck pace, as the Asian country grapples to contain a deadly swine virus that’s led to millions of pig deaths. Exports jumped 45% in the first seven months of the year, approaching the total for all of 2018, EU data show. But there’s a question over how long sales can keep rising -- even with increased demand, Europe’s pork output is seen largely steady this year.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Megan Durisin in London at mdurisin1@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Lynn Thomasson at lthomasson@bloomberg.net, Nicholas Larkin, Dylan Griffiths</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>