<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f48ca93f-b3c0-4bbe-8472-746de84a3f04" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T105716Z:TX-PAR-EJK41:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T105716Z:TX-PAR-EJK41:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T105716Z-TX-PAR-EJK41.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>SAfrica</item><item>Britain</item><item>royals</item><item>Desmond Tutu</item><item>Prince Harry</item><item>Meghan, Duchess of Sussex</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Royal baby Archie meets S.Africa's Archbishop Tutu</title><authors></authors><summary>The Duke and Duchess of Sussex on Wednesday took their four-month-old son Archie to meet Desmond Tutu in Cape Town, the royal baby's first public outing since his birth in May.To the delight of royal-watchers, Prince Harry and his wife Meghan walked into the Desmond &amp; Leah Tutu Legacy Foundation carrying a smiley Archie in blue dungarees.The family touched down in Cape Town on Monday for a 10-day trip in South Africa and other countries in the region.Both parents have hit the ground running...</summary><city>Cape Town</city><country>ZAF</country><xmlText><p>The Duke and Duchess of Sussex on Wednesday took their four-month-old son Archie to meet Desmond Tutu in Cape Town, the royal baby's first public outing since his birth in May.</p><p>To the delight of royal-watchers, Prince Harry and his wife Meghan walked into the Desmond &amp; Leah Tutu Legacy Foundation carrying a smiley Archie in blue dungarees.</p><p>The family touched down in Cape Town on Monday for a 10-day trip in South Africa and other countries in the region.</p><p>Both parents have hit the ground running -- speaking up for victims of gender violence, delving into local history and visiting charities that support poor children and disadvantaged youth.</p><p>But little Archie had yet to make an appearance, until he was taken for tea with one of South Africa's iconic anti-apartheid figures.</p><p>Archbishop Tutu and his wife Leah came out to greet the trio as they arrived, and Tutu kissed the baby's forehead.   </p><p>In a video posted on Twitter by journalists attending the event, Meghan bounced Archie on her lap as he made faces at the elderly couple.</p><p>They all laughed at Archie's expressions.</p><p>"You like the ladies better," joked Leah.</p><p>"I think he knows exactly what's going on," said Harry.</p><p>The adults shared an assortment of pastries decorated with the words "peace", "freedom" and "enough is enough" in reference to protests against gender violence that took place this month.</p><p>Archie had a special heart-shaped biscuit with his name written on it.</p><p>Tutu told the couple they were "adored" by South Africans.</p><p>"It's heartwarming," Meghan replied.</p><p>Harry last met Tutu in 2015, when he presented the archbishop with an honour in recognition for his services to UK communities and international peace.</p><p>Tutu was awarded a Nobel prize in 1984 for his unflinching opposition to the policies of apartheid -- a white-supremacist regime that dominated South Africa until 1994.    </p><p>The foundation, launched in 2013, focuses on youth leadership and social justice.</p><p>The prince will separate from his family later in Wednesday to travel to Botswana, Angola and Malawi.</p><p>He will visit conservation and HIV prevention projects, and a cleared minefield in Angola through which his late mother Princess Diana famously crossed in 1997.</p><p>Meanwhile the duchess and Archie will remain in South Africa, reuniting with Harry in Johannesburg next week to complete the tour as a family, flying back on October 2.</p><p>str-sch/ri </p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>