<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d9bb4680-8705-4f66-8ac3-4f254258bae0" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE2ZU6JTSE8:15</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE2ZU6JTSE8:15</followId><sourceFileName>PYE2ZU6JTSE800000_DNMLENf-20190925130933.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Dollar Rises, Stocks Steady Amid Political Drama: Markets Wrap</title><authors>Todd White and Jeremy Herron</authors><summary>PYE2ZU6JTSE8(Bloomberg) -- The dollar advanced and U.S. stocks were steady following the biggest drop in a month as political drama swirled in Washington and the U.K. Oil fell.The S&amp;P 500 was little changed as investors assessed the risks posed by a impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump. Trade tensions appeared to cool, with Bloomberg reporting that China will buy more U.S. pork, though chipmakers led losses. Philip Morris and Altria both rose after ending merger talks, while...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- The dollar advanced and U.S. stocks were steady following the biggest drop in a month as political drama swirled in Washington and the U.K. Oil fell.</p><p>The S&amp;P 500 was little changed as investors assessed the risks posed by a impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump. Trade tensions appeared to cool, with Bloomberg reporting that China will buy more U.S. pork, though chipmakers led losses. Philip Morris and Altria both rose after ending merger talks, while Marathon surged on activist intervention. Nike Inc. rose to a record after strong results. The dollar headed for its biggest advance since July.</p><p>In Europe, the mood was more dour. The Stoxx Europe 600 Index headed for its largest drop in six weeks amid rising concern that growth is flagging. U.K. shares fell as parliament reconvened amid Brexit turmoil. Asian benchmarks retreated, with losses of more than 1% in Hong Kong, South Korea, mainland China and India. Crude futures declined after Saudi Aramco said it was ahead of schedule in restoring output. </p><p>Markets have seemed to gyrate on the twists and turns of the protectionist battle between the two largest economies, with this year’s epic bond rally recovering from a pullback and U.S. stocks lingering within sight of a record high. The sudden escalation of political risk in Washington comes as economic signals deteriorate globally, adding a fresh complication for investors trying to decide whether central banks will be able to shore up growth.</p><p>Elsewhere, the pound slumped as Britain’s attorney general said a motion for a general election will be brought to Parliament “shortly.” In Japan, five-year government bond yields fell to a record low following comments from central bank Governor Haruhiko Kuroda that added to speculation of an interest-rate cut in October.</p><p>These are some key events coming up this week:</p><p>Here are the main moves in markets:</p><p>Stocks</p><p>Currencies</p><p>Bonds</p><p>Commodities</p><p>--With assistance from Sarah Ponczek, Vildana Hajric and Adam Haigh.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Todd White in Madrid at twhite2@bloomberg.net;Jeremy Herron in New York at jherron8@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editor responsible for this story: Samuel Potter at spotter33@bloomberg.net</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>