<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5a1ca8cb-8c55-49a5-b911-7d13bbb5991f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0546</summary><sourceId>183bd517-bef9-4ade-ade8-f04598ec0476</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9206%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0546</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 26</hl2><p xmlns="">1913 — Jim Thorpe gives up his track medals from the 1912 Olympic games as a result of his having been a professional. He had been paid $25 for playing in a semipro baseball game.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Jimmie Foxx and Mel Ott are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1955 — Joe DiMaggio is elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Pete Rozelle is chosen the new commissioner of the National Football League.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Edmonton's Wayne Gretzky scores his 50th goal in the 49th game of the season, a 6-3 victory over the Pittsburgh Penguins.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — The Chicago Bears win their first NFL championship since 1963 by setting a Super Bowl-record for points scored in defeating the New England Patriots 46-10.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Houston guard Vernon Maxwell joins Wilt Chamberlain, David Thompson and George Gervin as the only players in NBA history to score 30 points or more in a quarter. Maxwell scores 30 of his career-high 51 points in the fourth period to help Houston beat Cleveland 103-97.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — The Washington Redskins win their third Super Bowl in 10 years, beating the Buffalo Bills 37-24, putting the game away with 24 straight points after a scoreless first quarter.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — The Green Bay Packers, behind big plays, beat the New England Patriots 35-21 in the Super Bowl. Brett Favre finds Andre Rison for a 54-yard touchdown on the Packers' second offensive play, then throws an 81-yard TD pass to Antonio Freeman in the second quarter. Desmond Howard, the first special teams MVP, scores on a 99-yard kickoff return to put away the Patriots.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Jennifer Capriati produces the greatest comeback in a Grand Slam final to overcome Martina Hingis and defend her Australian Open title. Capriati saved four match points before clinching a 4-6, 7-6 (7), 6-2 victory over Hingis.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Mark Recchi scores two goals, including the 500th of his career, in Pittsburgh's 4-3 shootout win over Dallas.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Martin Brodeur makes 28 saves, extending his NHL record for consecutive 30-win seasons to 11, as the New Jersey Devils beat the Tampa Bay Lightning 2-0.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Mirai Nagasu becomes the second-youngest woman to win the title at the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. The 4-foot-11 14-year-old falls on her opening jump, a double axel, but lands six triple jumps, three in combination, in her program.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Victoria Azarenka wins her second consecutive Australian Open title, beating Li Na 4-6, 6-4, 6-3. Mike and Bob Bryan become the most decorated doubles team in Grand Slam history by winning their 13th major title, beating Robin Haase and Igor Sijsling 6-3, 6-4 in 53 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Ashley Wagner became the first woman since Michelle Kwan in 2005 to win back-to-back titles in the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. Earlier, Olympic silver medalists and 2011 world champions Meryl Davis and Charlie White win their fifth straight dance title, matching a U.S. record.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Stan Wawrinka holds off an injured Rafael Nadal to win his first Grand Slam title with a 6-3, 6-2, 3-6, 6-3 victory in the Australian Open final.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>