<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5b531dbd-9e14-b277-0e5c-89b3ccc16328" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Paul Muschick</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-NEWS2USE-CONSUMERS:AA — business, lifestyle (950 words)</title><summary>The brief shutdown is over and the federal government is back in business. Let’s hope that’s not business as usual.Congressional leaders say their goal now is to work on a long-term responsible budget, but it’s hard to take them seriously because...</summary><sourceId>9768186d-2d26-3dba-dba0-55acb36774e3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3119%ksign%w%BC-NEWS2USE-CONSUMERS:AA — business, lifestyle (950 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">The latest examples of the government wasting your money</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(NOT INCLUDED IN YOUR TRIBUNE NEWS SERVICE SUBSCRIPTION. To subscribe to News2Use, see purchase information below.)</p><byline xmlns="">By Paul Muschick</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">The brief shutdown is over and the federal government is back in business. Let’s hope that’s not business as usual.</p><p xmlns="">Congressional leaders say their goal now is to work on a long-term responsible budget, but it’s hard to take them seriously because of all the foolish spending that occurs. Government is too far out of touch with the real world when it comes to spending.</p><p xmlns="">You and I wince when gas goes up a few cents or our cable bill goes up a few bucks. Some federal agencies are so nonchalant about how they spend taxpayer dollars that they paid $38 million to dead people, $690,000 for unused parking spaces and $550,000 for questionable employee travel costs. And that’s nothing compared to the amount that may have been blown in Afghanistan, where America’s rebuilding efforts after the war on terror were terrible.</p><p xmlns="">Those are only a few examples of poor government financial stewardship revealed during recent audits.</p><p xmlns="">The $690,000 for unused parking spaces in 2015 and 2016 was courtesy of the Environmental Protection Agency. Its offices in Washington and Atlanta paid for the spaces as part of its subsidized employee parking program, which itself is a questionable expense. But the fact the agency wasn’t tracking whether it needed all the spaces it paid for is an insult to taxpayers.</p><p xmlns="">Federal regulations required the agency to monitor parking space usage, according to an audit published in November by the EPA inspector general. If anyone had been watching, they would have seen that an estimated 103 spaces were unoccupied over those two years.</p><p xmlns="">The inspector general questioned why those two EPA locations even were subsidizing employee parking. While it’s allowable, other agencies no longer pay for that, except for employees who are disabled, and the EPA doesn’t do it except at those two offices, according to the inspector general’s report.</p><p xmlns="">“In an age of dwindling federal resources, the EPA’s use of taxpayer money — over $840,000 in a two-year period — to fund employee parking may not be an effective use of federal resources and may take funds away from mission-critical public health and environmental initiatives,” the report said.</p><p xmlns="">The inspector general’s report, though, paid off. EPA headquarters stopped offering reduced-rate parking and reduced its parking allotment by 53 spaces.</p><p xmlns="">The government also could have saved a few bucks — $38 million to be exact, which is a few bucks in relation to the size of the federal budget — by not paying Social Security benefits to dead people.</p><p xmlns="">Benefits were paid to an estimated 746 veterans after they died, according to an August report by the Social Security Administration’s inspector general. Most payments were blamed on the failure of the Department of Veterans Affairs to include veterans’ death information in data it shared with Social Security, according to the audit.</p><p xmlns="">Social Security told auditors it would work with the VA to ensure future data it receives is complete.</p><p xmlns="">Another audit questioned $550,000 in travel expenses by employees at the Department of Housing and Urban Development. That agency’s inspector general said it found 3,160 charges on agency travel charge cards in fiscal year 2016 for dates outside employees’ approved travel periods.</p><p xmlns="">The audit also raised concerns about some charges on approved trips. One HUD employee paid to travel by train and rental car when flying would have been more efficient and saved at least two days of travel time, according to the audit. The unnecessary time on the road resulted in “avoidable” hotel stays and additional meal and other costs.</p><p xmlns="">HUD said it researched card transactions for anomalies and sent the results to its offices for review and action. It also conducted refresher training for cardholders and established mandatory annual training. It acknowledged “there is room for improvement” but disputed that there is a “significant deficiency” in the travel card program.</p><p xmlns="">There definitely is room for improvement the next time the U.S. government tries to help another war-torn country rebuild its economy.</p><p xmlns="">More than $316 million spent in Afghanistan from 2010 to 2014 achieved limited measurable results, according an investigation released two weeks ago. The money went to projects such as an industrial park, mining operations, natural gas pipelines, storage facilities, educational and vocational training, and banking and financial infrastructure.</p><p xmlns="">Only $70 million was spent on programs that fully accomplished their intended goal.</p><p xmlns="">The remaining $246 million was spent on projects that failed or only partially achieved their goal, according to an audit by the special inspector general for Afghanistan reconstruction.</p><p xmlns="">The audit cited poor planning, poor coordination with other agencies and poor oversight of work, which was done through the Task Force for Business and Stability Operations, part of the Defense Department. For example, while contract records said a $435,000 cold-storage pomegranate facility had been built, the inspector general visited the site and found no building, the audit said.</p><p xmlns="">This type of waste drives taxpayers out of their minds. I think most of us agree taxes are necessary to support necessary services. But when our money is wasted, we lose faith in the system. Unfortunately, there’s no reason to believe that will change anytime soon.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">Paul Muschick of The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) helps consumers fight errors, incompetence and arrogance by businesses, governments and institutions.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) at www.mcall.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">TO SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS2USE</p><p xmlns="">This column/content is for subscribers only. It is sold separately and is not included in your Tribune News Service subscription. To subscribe, please contact Rick DeChantal at Tribune Content Agency, (866) 280-5210 or rdechantal@tribpub.com, or you can purchase individual columns a la carte at www.tribunenewsservice.com.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002899,t000165520,t000002953,t000181590,t000003007,t000156697,t000138311,t000047682,t000138309,t000047680</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>