<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b95764ea-b3a8-4145-91c4-4798895fa816" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T092601Z:TX-PAR-EJI43:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T092601Z:TX-PAR-EJI43:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T092601Z-TX-PAR-EJI43.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Prévisions</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>AFPTV Advisory 1000 GMT</title><authors></authors><summary>Go to https://agenda.afp.com to consult AFP AgendaContact us on contact-agenda@afp.comLONDON (AFPTV) - We plan to file the following videos:TBA indicates that times are to be announced, but coverage is confirmed. TBC indicates that coverage is to be confirmed.For all editorial requests, email afptv@afp.com or contact the appropriate regional video desk.WEDNESDAY, SEPTEMBER 25, 2019+ HIGHLIGHTSLONDON (United Kingdom): Parliament reconvenes following Supreme Court decision WASHINGTON (United...</summary><city>London</city><country>GBR</country><xmlText><p>Go to https://agenda.afp.com to consult AFP Agenda</p><p>Contact us on contact-agenda@afp.com</p><p></p><p>LONDON (AFPTV) - We plan to file the following videos:</p><p>TBA indicates that times are to be announced, but coverage is confirmed. TBC indicates that coverage is to be confirmed.</p><p>For all editorial requests, email afptv@afp.com or contact the appropriate regional video desk.</p><p></p><p>WEDNESDAY, SEPTEMBER 25, 2019</p><p>+ HIGHLIGHTS</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom): Parliament reconvenes following Supreme Court decision </p><p>WASHINGTON (United States): Democrats launch impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump</p><p>BAIKONUR (Kazakhstan): First astronaut from UAE blasts off for ISS alongside astronauts from US, Russia</p><p>+ EUROPE</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom): .Boris Johnson arrives at Downing Street - LIVE TBC</p><p>LONDON (United Kingdom): Parliament reconvenes following Supreme Court decision - TBC</p><p>.Scene outside Houses of Parliament - LIVE 1000 GMT</p><p>.Inside House of Commons as it reconvenes - LIVE 1030 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia): Venezuela's Maduro visits, meets Putin TAPE TURN - EDIT TO FOLLOW - LIVE 0900 GMT</p><p>MONACO (Principality of Monaco): IPCC press conference to present special report on the ocean and cryosphere - EDIT TO FOLLOW - LIVE 0900 GMT</p><p>BAIKONUR (Kazakhstan): Astronauts from US, Russia, UAE blast off for ISS - LIVE 1300 GMT</p><p>.Docking at ISS - LIVE 1900 GMT</p><p>.Astronauts from US, Russia, UAE blast off for ISS: Hatch opening and welcome ceremony - LIVE 2100 GMT</p><p>BAIKONUR (Kazakhstan): First UAE astronaut, along with astronauts from US and Russia, gives a press conference ahead of launch for ISS - TBC </p><p>PARIS (France): French #MeToo founder holds presser after verdict in defamation case. - LIVE 1330 GMT</p><p>BERLIN (Germany): Demonstration of forestry staff, while the German Ministry of agriculture holds a summit on forests - EDIT 1400 GMT</p><p>+ MIDDLE EAST AND NORTH AFRICA</p><p>YAFOUR (Syria): Russian 'advisers' train new Syrian battalion - EDIT TBA</p><p>SALÉ (Morocco): Hearing in appeal trial of IS supporters sentenced for killing Scandinavian hikers - EDIT 1400 GMT</p><p>MORNAGUIA: Court rules on request to release jailed presidential contender Nabil Karoui - EDIT 1400 GMT</p><p>DOHA (Qatar): Qatari students march against climate change in a rare protest - EDIT 1400 GMT</p><p>DUBAI (United Arab Emirates): Cityscape Global opens, a property exhibition where hundreds of developers are expected to unveil new projects in a highly oversupplied market - EDIT 1400 GMT</p><p>JERUSALEM (Undefined): Israeli President Rivlin meets with Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and his main rival Benny Gantz. - LIVE 1500 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>RAMALLAH (Palestinian territories) Israeli security forces carry out raids in Ramallah - EDIT 1200 GMT </p><p>DUBAI (United Arab Emirates): Emiratis watch the launch of the first Emirati astronaut to the International Space Station - EDIT 1600 GMT</p><p>+ SUB SAHARAN AFRICA</p><p>DAKAR (Senegal): Senegal's powerful Mourides build 'biggest mosque in West Africa' - EDIT 1000 GMT </p><p>CAPE TOWN (South Africa): Prince Harry, Meghan meet archbishop Desmond Tutu - LIVE 0900 GMT</p><p>CAPE TOWN (South Africa): Duchess of Sussex visits HIV NGO Mothers 2 Mothers - LIVE 1230 GMT</p><p>+ ASIA PACIFIC</p><p>HONG KONG (China): Live outside a court where activists charged with rioting are expected to appear: Departures and potential statements - LIVE TBA</p><p>+ NORTH AMERICA</p><p>WASHINGTON (United States): Expected publication of Trump call with Ukrainian President Zelensky amid whistleblower scandal - EDIT TBA</p><p>NEW YORK (United States): Monitoring protests as Iranian President Rohani addresses UN General Assembly - EDIT TBA</p><p>.Beauty shot outside the UN - LIVE 1155 GMT</p><p>.World leaders arrive at the UN - LIVE 1200 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>.Day two of the UN General Assembly general debate with speeches including Iran, Ukraine, Libya - LIVE 1300 GMT</p><p>.Afternoon session - LIVE 1900 GMT</p><p>.Japanese PM Shinzo Abe holds presser - LIVE 2200 GMT TBC</p><p>.Iranian President Rouhani addresses UN General Assembly. Timings may change due to UN program - LIVE 1400 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p></p><p>.Trump meets Japan PM Abe on sidelines of UNGA - EDIT 1700 GMT</p><p></p><p></p><p>.Trump meets his Ukrainian counterpart Volodymyr Zelensky - EDIT 1830 GMT</p><p>.Trump holds presser on sidelines of UNGA - LIVE 2000 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p></p><p>UNITED NATIONS (United States): Foreign ministers from signatory countries to the Iran nuclear deal JCPOA meet - LIVE 1230 GMT</p><p>.Foreign ministers from signatory countries to the Iran nuclear deal JCPOA meet. TAPE TURN - EDIT 1300 GMT</p><p>SEATTLE (United States): Amazon unveils new Alexa and Echo products - EDIT 2200 GMT</p><p>+ LATIN AMERICA &amp; CARIBBEAN</p><p>MEXICO CITY (Mexico): Mexico Foreign Minister Marcelo Ebrard and undersecretary of Human Rights Alejandro Encinas take part in President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador press conference - Encinas will likely discuss the investigation on the 43 students who disappeared in 2014 - EDIT TBC</p><p>LIMA (Peru): Peruvian constitutional court rules on his request for release of Peru's imprisoned opposition leader Keiko Fujimori - EDIT TBA</p><p>BRASÍLIA (Brazil): Supreme Court hearing on Oderbrecht Lava Jato case that could lead to Lula's conviction being overturned - LIVE 1700 GMT TBC - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>MEXICO CITY (Mexico): Relatives of the 43 students who disappeared in Mexico in 2014 protest in front of the office of Mexico's Attorney General - EDIT 1800 GMT</p><p>BRASÍLIA (Brazil): Senators debate and vote on the nomination of Augusto Aras, elected by Jair Bolsonaro to serve as attorney general of Brazil in the next two years - EDIT 2200 GMT</p><p>+ SPORT</p><p>ABUJA (Nigeria): Graft case resumes against Nigeria Football Federation bosses - EDIT TBA</p><p>KUMAMOTO (Japan): Rugby/World Cup. France press conference - EDIT 1030 GMT</p><p>DOHA (Qatar): IAAF Congress Press Conference to announce re-election of president Sebastian Coe - EDIT 1400 GMT TBC</p><p>DOHA (Qatar): Team USA gives a press conference ahead of World Athletics Championships - EDIT 1600 GMT</p><p>PARIS (France): Football/Ligue 1. PSG-Reims post-match mixed zone - EDIT 2345 GMT</p><p>+ FEATURES</p><p>PARIS (France): Presentation of the "Ethiquette" collection, a haute couture label that produces its pieces exclusively from recycled fabrics. - EDIT TBA</p><p>PARIS (France): Grape harvest in Montmartre at the foot of the Sacré-Coeur. - EDIT TBA</p><p>NANTES (France): The "Disgusting Food Museum" opens in Nantes. - EDIT TBA</p><p>SARLAT-LA-CANEDA (France): France Tabac, the country's last tabacco factory, is set to close this autumn in a fresh blow for the industry. - EDIT TBA</p><p>THURSDAY, SEPTEMBER 26, 2019</p><p>+ EUROPE</p><p>MOSCOW (Russia): Moscow City Court considers appeal of actor jailed in protest crackdown ON MERIT - EDIT TBA</p><p>BRUSSELS (Belgium): Japanese PM Shinzo Abe and EU Commission president Jean-Claude Juncker give speeches at the opening of the European Connectivity Forum EU-Asia connectivity EDIT ON MERIT - TBA - LIVE 0700 GMT</p><p>WARSAW (Poland): Renia Spiegel, a Polish Jew, had only just turned 18 when she was shot dead by the Nazis in 1942. Her secret diary however survived has now been turned into a book and movie - EDIT 1000 GMT</p><p>BRUSSELS (Belgium): Japanese PM Shinzo Abe meets EU Commission president Jean-Claud Juncker - EDIT 1130 GMT</p><p>FRANKFURT AM MAIN (Germany): Merkel gives a speech at a conference marking 70th anniversary of Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung daily - EDIT ON MERIT - LIVE 1110 GMT</p><p>MARGATE (United Kingdom): Press preview of Turner Prize 2019 shortlist - EDIT 1500 GMT TBC</p><p>GENEVA (Switzerland): Geneva city and area will switch-off of street lighting during an action to raise awareness about the impact of light pollution - EDIT 1930 GMT</p><p>+ SUB SAHARAN AFRICA</p><p>CHOBE (Botswana): Prince Harry visits Chobe National park - EDIT TBA</p><p>JOHANNESBURG (South Africa): UN expert on albinism press conference - EDIT TBA</p><p>+ ASIA PACIFIC</p><p>CAIRNS (Australia): Croc-spotting drone patrolling northern Australia launched - 0400 GMT</p><p>SHENZHEN (China): Huawei founder Ren Zhengfei headlines panel discussion, answers reporter questions - LIVE 0600 GMT</p><p>HONG KONG (China): Embattled Hong Kong leader Carrie Lam to hold first "dialogue session" - LIVE 1100 GMT</p><p>+ NORTH AMERICA</p><p>SAN FRANCISCO (United States): New Uber products launch - EDIT TBA</p><p>NEW YORK (United States): Day three of the UN General Assembly general debate with speeches expected from Venezuela, Palestine, South Sudan - LIVE 1300 GMT</p><p>NEW YORK (United States): Iranian President Rohani holds presser - LIVE 1600 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>+ SPORT</p><p>IWATA (Japan): Rugby/WC-2019: First round Pool A: Japan-Ireland. Ireland train two days ahead of match - EDIT 0330 GMT</p><p>KUALA LUMPUR (Malaysia): Underwater hockey to make waves at Southeast Asia mini-Olympics - EDIT 0400 GMT</p><p>IWATA (Japan): Rugby/WC-2019: First round Pool A: Japan-Ireland. Ireland team announcement - EDIT 0600 GMT</p><p>TOKYO (Japan): Rugby/World Cup: Wales press conference - EDIT 0600 GMT</p><p>TOKYO (Japan): Rugby/World Cup: Wales training - EDIT 0700 GMT</p><p>BEIJING (China): Press conference by former NBA star Jeremy Lin who has signed with Beijing Shougang Ducks - EDIT 0600 GMT</p><p>HAMAMATSU (Japan): Rugby/WC-2019: First round Pool A: Japan-Ireland. Japan team announcement - EDIT 0900 GMT</p><p>KARACHI (Pakistan): Cricket: Sri Lanka and Pakistan practice ahead of ODI clash - EDIT 1600 GMT</p><p>DOHA (Qatar): Opening press conference of the 17th IAAF World Athletics Championships - LIVE 1800 GMT - EDIT TO FOLLOW</p><p>+ FEATURES</p><p>Playa Hermosa (Costa Rica): In Costa Rica, following in the footsteps of Golfin turtles - EDIT 0500 GMT</p><p>SANTIAGO (Chile): From Chile to Panama, an ocean of plastic. Chile, Latin America's top garbage producer, seeks to reuse its plastic waste - EDIT 0500 GMT</p><p>SANTIAGO (Chile): From Chile to Panama, an ocean of plastic. Panama, Local anti-plastic initiatives battle against lack of environmental awareness - EDIT 0500 GMT</p><p>BERLIN (Germany): German woman boxer's fight to wear headscarf in the ring - EDIT 0200 GMT </p><p></p><p></p><p>* SPORT : AFPTV Sport subscribers only</p><p>Editorial contacts:</p><p>Email: afptv@afp.com</p><p>Europe (excluding France) desk: +44 207 776 2768</p><p>France desk: +33 1 40 41 79 40</p><p>Asia desk: +852 2829 6279</p><p>Middle East &amp; North Africa desk: +357 22 391 450</p><p>Sub-Saharan Africa desk (Mon-Fri): +33 1 40 41 46 81</p><p>North America desk: +1 202 414 0664</p><p>Latin America desk: +598 2 900 5095 ext. 257</p><p>AFPTV LIVE MCR: +33 1 40 41 79 63</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>