<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f69059d3-341c-4bea-9247-7b57beb25de0" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2NA:1283590326</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2NA:1283590326</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T110925Z_1283590326_L3N26G2NA_RTRMADT_0_BEST-BUY-OUTLOOK.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Best Buy targets $50 bln in revenue in 2025</title><summary>BEST BUY-OUTLOOK/:Best Buy targets $50 bln in revenue in 2025</summary><xmlText><p>Best Buy targets $50 bln in revenue in 2025</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - Best Buy Co Inc is aiming to rake in revenue of $50 billion in 2025 as it adds new products and bolsters investments as part of the second phase of its growth plan, the biggest U.S. consumer electronics retailer said on Wednesday.</p><p>The company also said it expects adjusted operating income to grow 5% in 2025, compared with its current estimate of flat to slightly up.</p><p>"In this next chapter, our focus continues to be top-line growth," Chief Financial Officer Matt Bilunas said in a statement.</p><p>The first phase of Best Buy's "New Blue Growth" plan was started in 2017 by former Chief Executive Hubert Joly, who stepped down in April.</p><p>The company, which reaffirmed its full-year revenue forecast, also set a target of $1 billion in additional cost reductions for fiscal 2025.</p><p>"The initiatives we will outline today, along with a continued focus on cost reductions, will result in operating income rate expansion over the five-year timeframe," Bilunas said.</p><p>Best Buy is set to kick off its investor meeting later in the day. (Reporting by Akanksha Rana in Bengaluru; Editing by Shailesh Kuber)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>