<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f746e06e-3dfc-4c9d-9ddd-4f7a874abab4" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2AP:785841874</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2AP:785841874</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T100110Z_785841874_L3N26G2AP_RTRMADT_0_TENNIS-WUHAN.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Tennis-Battling Barty downs Kenin to reach Wuhan quarter-finals</title><summary>TENNIS-WUHAN/:Tennis-Battling Barty downs Kenin to reach Wuhan quarter-finals</summary><xmlText><p>Tennis-Battling Barty downs Kenin to reach Wuhan quarter-finals</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - World number one Ash Barty fended off a late comeback attempt by American Sofia Kenin to reach the Wuhan Open quarter-finals on Wednesday, while Simona Halep retired from her match due to a lower back injury.</p><p>After cruising through the first set without any trouble, Barty fought back from a break down in the next, saving two set points to overcome Kenin 6-3 7-5 for her third win over the 20-year-old Guangzhou champion in four meetings this season.</p><p>Next up for the Australian top seed will be Petra Martic who defeated qualifier Veronika Kudermetova 6-3 6-1.</p><p>Former French Open champion Halep was forced to quit in the opening set of her encounter with wildcard Elena Rybakina while trailing 5-4 after feeling sharp pain.</p><p>"It's a lower back (injury). I think it's more muscle, but I don't know yet because I didn't check it properly," the fourth seed told a news conference.</p><p>The Romanian had suffered a herniated disk late last year which ruled her out of the season-ending WTA Finals.</p><p>"At four-all, 0-30, with the backhand. I had a sharp pain. I don't know yet (if it is the same as the previous injury). It looks a little bit different but it's still the same zone."</p><p>Rybakina will next face Belarusian ninth seed Aryna Sabalenka who dispatched sixth-seeded Dutchwoman Kiki Bertens 6-1 7-6(9) for a spot in her first Premier-level semi-final.</p><p>Ukraine's Elina Svitolina beat Russia's Svetlana Kuznetsova 6-4 6-2 to stay on course to qualify for the season-ending WTA Finals in Shenzhen where she will bid to retain her title. (Reporting by Shrivathsa Sridhar in Bengaluru; Editing by Ken Ferris)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>