<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="1421715e-dd8f-4759-9d04-689602fea2f8" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2RU:383875874</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2RU:383875874</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T114435Z_383875874_L3N26G2RU_RTRMADT_0_USA-STOCKS.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>US STOCKS-Futures fall on Trump impeachment push, Nike gains</title><summary>USA-STOCKS/:US STOCKS-Futures fall on Trump impeachment push, Nike gains</summary><xmlText><p>US STOCKS-Futures fall on Trump impeachment push, Nike gains</p><p>(For a live blog on the U.S. stock market, click or type LIVE/ in a news window)</p><p>* Futures down: Dow 0.19%, S&amp;P 0.24%, Nasdaq 0.39%</p><p>By Sruthi Shankar and Ambar Warrick</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - U.S. stock index futures edged lower on Wednesday as a move to launch an impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump injected a fresh dose of uncertainty, with forecast-beating results from Nike Inc helping dispel some gloom.</p><p>The inquiry, which pushed the S&amp;P 500 to post its biggest percentage drop in a month on Tuesday, worsened an already fragile sentiment after Trump hardened his stance over the trade dispute with China, saying he would not accept a "bad deal".</p><p>Futures pointed to opening losses for the main three indexes, with trade-sensitive shares of chipmakers and industrial companies trending lower.</p><p>Advanced Micro Devices Inc, Intel Corp and Nvidia Corp shed between 0.5% to 0.9% in premarket trading, while Boeing Co dropped 0.4%.</p><p>At 7:14 a.m. ET, Dow e-minis were down 51 points, or 0.19%. S&amp;P 500 e-minis were down 7.25 points, or 0.24% and Nasdaq 100 e-minis were down 30.25 points, or 0.39%.</p><p>Nike's shares jumped 5.7% premarket, on course for a record open and likely boosting the Dow Jones Industrial Average , after first-quarter results beat market expectations.</p><p>Shares in retailer Foot Locker Inc gained 1%.</p><p>Chipmaker Broadcom Inc dropped 3% after it priced an upsized offering of convertible preferred stock.</p><p>Investors will look to August new home sales data, due at 10:00 a.m. ET (1400 GMT), to gauge domestic spending strength ahead of the key holiday shopping season.</p><p>A weaker-than-expected consumer confidence reading on Tuesday had raised concerns over slowing individual spending, driving down several retail stocks, including Amazon.com Inc . (Reporting by Sruthi Shankar and Ambar Warrick in Bengaluru; Editing by Sriraj Kalluvila)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>