<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7bc62d91-e61f-47ef-a158-72df89fd66f7" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1YA:2114149951</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1YA:2114149951</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T074119Z_2114149951_L3N26G1YA_RTRMADT_0_JAPAN-STOCKS-CLOSE.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Nikkei slips to 1-week low on Trump's woes, trade uncertainty</title><summary>JAPAN-STOCKS/CLOSE:Nikkei slips to 1-week low on Trump's woes, trade uncertainty</summary><xmlText><p>Nikkei slips to 1-week low on Trump's woes, trade uncertainty</p><p>By Tomo Uetake</p><p>TOKYO, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Japan's Nikkei share average fell to a one-week low on Wednesday after U.S. lawmakers called for an impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump, while weak U.S. consumer confidence data heightened worries over the Sino-U.S. trade row.</p><p>The benchmark Nikkei average dropped 0.4% to 22,020.15, its lowest close since Sept. 18, while the broader Topix dipped 0.2% to 1,620.08, tracking a dismal Wall Street session.</p><p>Both indexes climbed to their highest finish in five-months the previous day.</p><p>U.S. shares slipped in volatile trade overnight, giving the S&amp;P 500 its biggest one-day drop in a month, as a push for impeaching Trump gained momentum among Democrats in Congress.</p><p>Major Wall Street indexes earlier lost their footing when Trump took a harsh tone about China's trade practices at the United Nations General Assembly, saying he would not accept a "bad deal" in U.S.-China negotiations.</p><p>Further pressuring Wall Street was the disappointing consumer confidence data.</p><p>On Tokyo's bourse, oil and coal products and machinery were among the worst performing of the 33 subsector indexes, down 1.0% and 1.2%, respectively.</p><p>One of the few bright spots was the air transport sector, up 1.1%, with Japan Airlines and ANA Holdings rising 1.2% and 1.0%, respectively.</p><p>Oil prices fell on Wednesday for a second day on worries about falling fuel demand after Trump's comments doused optimism over China-U.S. trade talks and reignited concerns on global economic growth.</p><p>Other notable movers included Nintendo Co, shedding 4.3% after Bloomberg reported initial domestic shipments of the gaming firm's "Switch Lite" were softer than expected.</p><p>Traders said Wednesday's profit-taking came as no surprise as some technical indicators looked overheated.</p><p>Indeed, the benchmark Nikkei's 14-day relative strength index (RSI) hit 97.4 the previous day, its highest in nearly two years. An RSI reading above 70 would be considered "overbought." (Editing by Jacqueline Wong)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>