<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="279f0081-a575-4bc2-ac71-9bdfd3254321" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0306</summary><sourceId>f7667b8c-336b-4651-651a-f96f3be8a996</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5626%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0306</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with RHP Addison Reed on a two-year contract. Designated LHP Buddy Boshers for assignment.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Designated INF Engelb Vielma and RHP Shane Carle for assignment.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON NATIONALS — Agreed to terms with OF Howie Kendrick on a two-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY T-BONES — Signed RHP Luis Paula.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed RHP Dimitri Kourtis.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX CITY EXPLORERS — Released INF Joe Bennie.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Signed OF Dan Motl.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed RHPs Jordan Wellander and Zach Hartman and LHP Josh Tols.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA CHAMPIONS — Signed RHPs Noah Gapp and Bobby St. Pierre.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed C Luis Alen.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed INF Culver Plant.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed OF Sean Hurley to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Signed OF Chris Scura.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Signed F Andrew White III to a two-way contract,</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES LAKERS — Signed G Gary Payton II to a two-way contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND BROWNS — Signed TE Gavin Escobar to a reserve/futures contract.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Mutually agreed to part ways with coach Mike Mularkey. Signed CB Jeremy Boykins, WR Darius Jennings, S Denzel Johnson, OL Tyler Marz, DE Johnny Maxey, WR Zach Pascal, TE Tim Semisch, DE Julius Warmsley, OL Cody Wichmann and DL Antwaun Woods to reserve/futures contracts.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Signed QB Kevin Glenn.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Reassigned LWs Ryan Lomberg and Marek Hrivik and Andrew Mangiapane to Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Reassigned F Zach Nastasiuk to Grand Rapids (AHL) from the Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LAS VEGAS GOLDEN KNIGHTS — Signed D Deryk Engelland to a one-year contract extension through the 2018-19 season.</p><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE PREDATORS — Recalled G Juuse Saros from Milwaukee (AHL). Reassigned G Anders Lindback to Milwaukee.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled F Peter Holland from Hartford (AHL). Assigned C Boo Nieves to Hartford.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Recalled F Tage Thompson from San Antonio (NBAGL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">GRAND RAPIDS GRIFFINS — Recalled F Luke Esposito from Toledo (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">BIG 12 CONFERENCE — Fined Texas Tech $25,000 and reprimanded West Virginia forward Wes Harris for hitting a fan who joined thousands of others in storming the court during a postgame celebration on Jan. 13.</p><p xmlns="">GEORGIA — LB Roquan Smith will enter the NFL draft.</p><p xmlns="">MEMPHIS — Announced the resignation of wide receivers coach David Johnson.</p><p xmlns="">NC STATE — Announced redshirt senior QB Jalan McClendon will transfer.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY CITY — Named Patrick O'Neill men's and women's cross country, indoor and outdoor track &amp; field coach.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE — Junior QB Quinten Dormady is transferring.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TECH — Named Donnie Suber defensive coordinator.</p><p xmlns=""></p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>