<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6b909d33-b89a-42aa-a60d-89166d719301" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T094202Z:TX-PAR-EJI78:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T094202Z:TX-PAR-EJI78:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T094202Z-TX-PAR-EJI78.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Prévisions</item><item>Graphics</item><item>Advisory</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>AFP Graphics Advisory</title><authors></authors><summary>Wednesday's graphics:- INTERNATIONAL -BRITAIN-EU-BREXIT-POLITICS: Key events in the Brexit process in 2019. 135 x 80 mmPAKISTAN-QUAKE: Map locating a 5.2-magnitude earthquake struck near the Kashmiri city of Mirpur in Punjab province, in Pakistan. 45 x 45 mmUN-CLIMATE:* Latest:- Updated map locating protests planned during Global Climate Action Week (Sept 20-27). 180 x 107 mm - Forecasts for Arctic sea ice melt comparing two scenarios: a) substantial worldwide push to curb carbon emissions,...</summary><city>Paris</city><country>FRA</country><xmlText><p>Wednesday's graphics:</p><p></p><p></p><p>BRITAIN-EU-BREXIT-POLITICS: Key events in the Brexit process in 2019. 135 x 80 mm</p><p></p><p>PAKISTAN-QUAKE: Map locating a 5.2-magnitude earthquake struck near the Kashmiri city of Mirpur in Punjab province, in Pakistan. 45 x 45 mm</p><p></p><p>UN-CLIMATE:</p><p>* Latest:</p><p>- Updated map locating protests planned during Global Climate Action Week (Sept 20-27). 180 x 107 mm </p><p>- Forecasts for Arctic sea ice melt comparing two scenarios: a) substantial worldwide push to curb carbon emissions, and b) countries focus on domestic concerns at the expense of international efforts to curb global warming. 180 x 95 mm</p><p>- Switzerland's Pizol glacier disappears. 90 x 65 mm</p><p></p><p>* National efforts:</p><p>- Top five greenhouse gas emitting countries, 2016. 135 x 175 mm; 135 x 120 mm</p><p>- Where different countries stand in their efforts to become carbon neutral. 135 x 108 mm</p><p>- Earth Overshoot Day. 90 x 118 mm</p><p></p><p>* Sea level rise:</p><p>- Risk of submersion in five major coastal cities. 180 x 83 mm</p><p>- Sea level rise forecasts to 2100, with contributions from different areas. 135 x 99 mm</p><p></p><p>* Temperature rise:</p><p>- Projected global temperature rise by 2100, based on new climate models. 90 x 80 mm</p><p>- Difference between recorded monthly temperatures and the 20th-century average for the corresponding month. 180 x 95 mm</p><p>- Difference between recorded annual temperatures and the 20th-century average for the corresponding year. 90 x 61 mm</p><p>- Maps showing the forecast temperature rise in selected cities in 2050. 90 x 85 mm</p><p></p><p>* Miscellaneous:</p><p>- The multiple effects of climate change on human health and living conditions. 135 x 199 mm</p><p>- Municipal waste recycling rate in 2017 in Europe. 90 x 85 mm</p><p></p><p>CHINA-POLITICS-ANNIVERSARY:</p><p>- Graphic showing how China fares on major international rankings. 180 x 120 mm</p><p>- Factfile on the PRC which marks its 70th anniversary on October 1. 135 x 236 mm</p><p>- Graphic timeline of major events during 70 years of China's communist rule. 180 x 223 mm</p><p>- Factfile on China's main economic indicators. 135 x 100 mm</p><p></p><p>SKOREA-NKOREA-DMZ: Map of the Demilitarized Zone that has divided the Korean peninsula since 1953. South Korean President Moon Jae-in on Tuesday proposed that the UN create an "international peace zone" to replace the divide. 180 x 110 mm</p><p></p><p>IRAN-SAUDI-OIL:</p><p>- Map locating major air and naval bases in the Gulf region. 135 x 131 mm</p><p>- Key dates in Iran-US tensions, since the Iranian revolution in 1979. 180 x 102 mm</p><p></p><p>BRAZIL-DEFORESTATION: </p><p>- The rate of deforestation in the Brazilian Amazon in km2 since 1988. 135 x 80 mm</p><p>- Loss of forest cover and Co2 emissions between 2001 and 2018 in the countries of the Amazon Basin. 105 x 135 mm</p><p></p><p>SPAIN-POLITICS-FRANCO: Map locating Valle de los Caidos (Valley of the Fallen) near Madrid. 180 x 126 mm; 45 x 62 mm</p><p></p><p>SKOREA-CHINA-ANIMAL: Map showing parts of Asia, where African swine fever spread has led to millions of pigs being culled since August 2018, as of Sep 24, 2019. 90 x 76 mm</p><p></p><p>UN-POLITICS: The UN General Assembly on September 23-27. 90 x 76 mm</p><p></p><p>ISRAEL-VOTE: </p><p>- The incoming Israeli parliament. 90 x 86 mm</p><p>- Socio-economic factfile on Israel. 180 x 94 mm</p><p></p><p></p><p>HISTORY-WALL-30YEARS: </p><p>- Map of Europe showing the Iron Curtain and various Cold War political and military pacts across Europe. 135 x 152 mm</p><p>- Description of what a portion of the Berlin Wall was like in 1983. 135 x 75 mm </p><p></p><p>DRCONGO-HEALTH-EBOLA: </p><p>- Map showing Ebola epidemic, number of cases and deaths in DR Congo and neighbouring Uganda. 90 x 90 mm</p><p>- Toll and chronology of the ebola epidemic in the Democratic Republic of Congo and neighbouring countries. 45 x 132 mm</p><p></p><p>INDIA-MUMBAI-CLIMATE: Factfile on how India's biggest metropolis is vulnerable to sea-level rise. 90 x 151 mm</p><p></p><p>USA-SPACE-MOON: Graphic on NASA's Artemis program to establish a mini-space station orbiting the Moon before landing on the surface in 2024. 135 x 104 mm</p><p></p><p>FRANCE-FERTILITY:</p><p>- Factfile on fertility treatment in France. 90 x 100 mm</p><p>- Egg and sperm donations as a share of all fertility treatment in France. 45 x 105 mm</p><p></p><p></p><p>BRITAIN-CHINA-LEISURE:</p><p>- Map showing where British travel firm Thomas Cook and its subsidiaries operated with the number of tourists present or abroad in selected countries. 180 x 120 mm</p><p>- Map showing where British travel firm Thomas Cook and its subsidiaries operated, based on the company's annual report in 2018. 135 x 104 mm</p><p>- Mini-profile of British travel firm Thomas Cook which declared bankruptcy on Monday. 45 x 106</p><p></p><p>EU-DEBT: </p><p>- Public debt as a percentage of GDP for countries in the European Union. 135 x 125 mm</p><p>-Public debt in Italy, France, Spain and Germany in % of GDP from 2005 to 2018, and forecasts from 2019 and 2020. 135 x 105 mm</p><p></p><p></p><p>VOLLEY-EURO: A chart of the final rounds of the men's 2019 European Volleyball Championship. 135 x 62 mm </p><p></p><p>ATHLETICS-BERLIN-MARATHON: Graphic showing marathon world records for men and women, ahead of the 2019 Berlin Marathon on September 29. 135 x 247</p><p></p><p>RUGBYU-WC-2019:</p><p>- Factfile on top teams and their performance in the opening games. 180 x 158 mm</p><p>- Match calendar with results and Pool standings. 180 x 175 mm</p><p>- Fiji-Uruguay matches on Sept 5. 45 x 37 mm</p><p>- Pool standings. Pools A-D. 45 x 62 mm each</p><p>- The New Zealand haka. 135 x 194 mm</p><p>- Match calendars. Overall (Sept 20-Nov 2): 296 x 188 mm; All pools: 180 x 133 mm. Individual pools: 45 x 126 mm each</p><p>- Team members and past performance for each participating team. Each 90 mm wide</p><p>- List of players for each of the 20 teams. 90 x 100 mm</p><p>- Star player for each team. 45 x 86 mm</p><p>- Venues. 90 x 140 mm</p><p>- Stadium capacities. 180 x 172 mm</p><p>- Changes in physique of rugby players by position since 1955. 90 x 85 mm</p><p>- Changes in world rankings between 2015 and 2019. 45 x 60 mm</p><p>- Basic rules of rugby. 90 x 140 mm</p><p>- A brief history of rugby union. 135 x 117 mm</p><p>- Referees and match signals. 180 x 104 mm</p><p></p><p>FBL-FIFA-AWARDS: Graphic on the main winners at the FIFA Best Awards 2019. 135 x 138 mm</p><p></p><p>AUTO-F1-RUS:</p><p>- Sochi circuit for the Russian Grand Prix. 45 x 65 mm, 90 x 85 mm</p><p>- Driver and team standings with the Sochi circuit for the Russian Grand Prix. 135 x 85 mm</p><p></p><p>FBL-EUR-C1:</p><p>- Clubs that have won the European Champions League since 2010. 45 x 73 mm</p><p>- Map of Europe detailing past winners of the Champions League. 135 x 135 mm</p><p>- Clubs that have played the most European Cup football matches. 180 x 190 mm</p><p></p><p>FBL-ENG-PR:</p><p>- English Premier League fixtures. 45 x 150 mm </p><p>- English Premier League standings. 45 x 150 mm</p><p></p><p>Impeachment</p><p>Climate ice shelves</p><p>Melting ice caps</p><p>Permafrost</p><p>Climate videographics</p><p>Climate heat in cities</p><p>How the human body reacts in space</p><p>UN General Assembly</p><p>Plastics</p><p>Jellyfish</p><p>F1 Russian Grand Prix</p><p></p><p></p><p>Paris: +33 1 40 41 77 75</p><p>Hong Kong: +852 2829 6295</p><p>afp</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>