<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e935e24a-8f8b-4791-befc-a7c36e84ecb6" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0599</summary><sourceId>e2614f17-df9c-4241-2418-06b6308fdb3d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1626%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0599</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Acquired C Andrew Susac from Milwaukee for a player to be named or cash considerations.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK YANKEES — Agreed to terms with C Francisco Diaz, INF Danny Espinosa, RHP David Hale, C Erik Kratz, LHP Wade LeBlanc, C Chace Numata and INF/OF Jace Peterson on minor league contracts.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Texas League</hl2><p xmlns="">FRISCO ROUGHRIDERS — Named Bernadette Miller chief financial officer and Tim Arseneau vice president, ballpark operations.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">TROIS-RIVIERES AIGLES — Released C Kyle Lafrenz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Women's National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON MYSTICS — Re-signed Fs Tianna Hawkins and LaToya Sanders and G Allison Hightower.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BILLS — Announced the retirement of director of training operations Bud Carpenter.</p><hl2 xmlns="">GYMNASTICS</hl2><p xmlns="">USA GYMNASTICS — Announced the resignation of women's national team coordinator Valeri Liukin.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NHL — Suspended Buffalo F Johan Larsson two games for cross checking Florida F Vincent Trocheck in the face during a Feb. 1 game.</p><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Recalled G Adin Hill from Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned D Steven Santini to Binghamton (AHL). Recalled F John Quenneville from Binghamton. Assigned F Jimmy Hayes to Binghamton on a conditioning stint.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Fined Atlanta's Darby Llewellyn an undisclosed amount for his actions during a Feb. 1 game at Jacksonville.</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Announced F Chris McCarthy was returned from the Lehigh Valley (AHL) and G John Muse was recalled on loan by Lehigh Valley. Signed G Brad Barone from Roanoke (SPHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS CREW — Signed M Ricardo Clark.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RED BULLS — Signed M Cristian Casseres, Jr.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Acquired M Cristhian Paredes from Club America (Liga MX), utilizing Targeted Allocation Money.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON SPIRIT — Waived D Alyssa Kleiner.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">BARUCH — Named Omar Durrani men's and women's assistant tennis coach.</p><p xmlns="">IOWA — Announced QB Ryan Boyle will transfer.</p><p xmlns=""></p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>