<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2a2732b1-169e-4862-bd1b-0eb8946f02f2" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T104900Z:TX-PAR-EJK24:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T104900Z:TX-PAR-EJK24:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T104900Z-TX-PAR-EJK24.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>RugbyU</item><item>WC</item><item>2019</item><item>AUS</item><item>Hodge</item><item>Reece Hodge</item><item>Dane Haylett-Petty</item><item>Peceli Yato</item><item>Nathan Grey</item><item>Kurtley Beale</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Wallaby Hodge to miss World Cup pool stage after three-match ban</title><authors></authors><summary>Australia were dealt a blow ahead of their Rugby World Cup Pool D showdown against Wales when long-range goal-kicking winger Reece Hodge was banned Wednesday for three matches for a high tackle in the Wallabies' opening game against Fiji.Fiji were leading 11-7 when Hodge charged into Peceli Yato, leaving the Fiji flanker concussed. The Wallabies wing went on to score a try and kick a penalty as Australia won 39-21.Hodge was cited after the match and went before an independent disciplinary...</summary><city>Tokyo</city><country>JPN</country><xmlText><p>Australia were dealt a blow ahead of their Rugby World Cup Pool D showdown against Wales when long-range goal-kicking winger Reece Hodge was banned Wednesday for three matches for a high tackle in the Wallabies' opening game against Fiji.</p><p>Fiji were leading 11-7 when Hodge charged into Peceli Yato, leaving the Fiji flanker concussed. The Wallabies wing went on to score a try and kick a penalty as Australia won 39-21.</p><p>Hodge was cited after the match and went before an independent disciplinary committee in Tokyo on Wednesday.</p><p>The ban means the 25-year-old Melbourne Rebels player, capable of slotting in anywhere in the backline, will miss Australia's remaining three Pool D games against Wales on Sunday, Uruguay in Oita on October 5 and Georgia in Shizuoka six days later.</p><p>The disciplinary committee "deemed that the incident was an act of foul play and warranted a red card in line with the high tackle sanction framework", World Rugby said in a statement.</p><p>It added that the tackle was "reckless, rather than deliberate", but contact with the head meant a high degree of danger.</p><p>Given Hodge's "exemplary disciplinary record, good character and conduct at the hearing, the committee reduced the six-match entry point by three matches".</p><p>Fiji's shock 30-27 defeat by Uruguay on Wednesday has now shaped Pool D into a straight contest between Australia and Wales to seal the winner and runners-up spots to reach the quarter-finals, for which Hodge would be eligible.</p><p>Assistant coach Nathan Grey said earlier Wednesday that the Australian management were "pretty confident the judicial system will look after itself".</p><p>"We'll have to deal with that whatever the outcome is," Grey added.</p><p>"You'd be crazy as a management not to manage both ways, so whether he's there or not, we'll be ready to go."</p><p>Full-back Kurtley Beale said he was "confident Reece will have a fair hearing", adding that the players had not discussed it.</p><p>"As a player, you want your teammate to play. I think Reece has done a fantastic job on the wing.</p><p>"To his credit, he really threw himself into those tackles. He's got no malice in trying to go out there and do wrongdoing."</p><p>Hodge's potential absence, Beale said, would be more than made up for by Dane Haylett-Petty, who enjoyed an eye-catching cameo against Fiji off the bench.</p><p>"We're confident as a back three, whoever's in those positions, we will get the job done," Beale said.</p><p>lp/th</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>