<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6bac17e4-1a98-4845-b242-c01cbfb681eb" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0563</summary><sourceId>27839e8a-807c-420a-20aa-50a7b0f4e341</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1057%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0563</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 3</hl2><p xmlns="">1944 — Syd Howe of the Detroit Red Wings scores six goals in a 12-6 victory over the New York Rangers.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — Larry Bird hits the first 3-point shot in the history of the NBA All-Star Game. Bird' 3 came in overtime as the East team outscores the West 16-8 in the overtime for a 144-136 win.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Skier Steve Mahre, twin brother of overall champion Phil Mahre, becomes the first American man to win a gold medal in Olympic or World Championship competition when he edges Sweden's Ingemar Stenmark by 0.51 seconds in the giant slalom.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Bill Shoemaker, the world's winningest jockey, finishes fourth on Patchy Groundfog in his final ride at Santa Anita. The 58-year-old Shoemaker finishes his 40-year career with $123,375,524 in earnings, a record 8,833 wins, 6,136 seconds and 4,987 thirds in 40,350 starts.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Visiting teams are 7-0, marking the first time in NBA history road clubs go undefeated on a day with more than five games. Expansion Toronto beats the Los Angeles Clippers 119-113 in overtime, Seattle defeats Houston 104-103 in overtime, Boston downs Miami 100-99, Portland tops Philadelphia 96-85, Sacramento defeats Detroit 94-85, Cleveland tops Milwaukee 111-88 and Minnesota downs Dallas 105-96.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — World Wrestling Federation mastermind Vince McMahon unveils his latest creation: the XFL, a new pro football league.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — One year later, the XFL muscles its way onto the national sports scene with its first two games. With exuberant cheerleaders and trash-talking players sharing center stage, the Las Vegas Outlaws beat the New York/New Jersey Hitmen 19-0, while the Orlando Rage beat the Chicago Enforcers 33-29 before a crowd of 35,603 in Orlando.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Martin Brodeur becomes the third goaltender in NHL history to reach 100 shutouts as New Jersey blanks Carolina 3-0. Brodeur joins Terry Sawchuk (115) and George Hainsworth (102).</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The Baltimore Ravens survive a power outage at the Super Bowl to edge the San Francisco 49ers 34-31. Jacoby Jones returns the second-half kickoff 108 yards, a Super Bowl record, to give Baltimore a 28-6 lead. Moments later, lights lining the Superdome fade. When action resumes 34 minutes later, Colin Kaepernick and the 49ers score 17 consecutive points, getting as close as 31-29. Baltimore stops San Francisco on fourth-and-goal from the 5 with under 2 minutes left when Kaepernick's pass sails beyond Michael Crabtree in the end zone.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Tara VanDerveer becomes the second NCAA women's coach to reach 1,000 career victories, when No. 8 Stanford beats Southern Cal 58-42 to give the Hall of Famer a major milestone in front of the home crowd at Maples Pavilion. VanDerveer joins the late Pat Summitt, with 1,098 wins to her name, as the only other women's coach in the elite club. Duke's Mike Krzyzewski is the only Division I men's coach with 1,000.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Boston's Isaiah Thomas scores 17 of his 38 points in the fourth quarter, and the Celtics beat the Los Angeles Lakers 113-107. Boston and Los Angeles began the night with 3,252 wins, tied for the most in NBA history. Before their loss, the Lakers held at least a share of the league's victories mark since 2001.</p><p xmlns="">___</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>