<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d3a36dc7-1898-4f7a-8dcc-7054edd36a7b" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T092205Z:TX-PAR-EJI34:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T092205Z:TX-PAR-EJI34:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T092205Z-TX-PAR-EJI34.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>News</item><item>advisory</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>AFP 0900 GMT News Advisory</title><authors></authors><summary>Duty Editor: Barry ParkerTel: +33 1 40 41 46 36-- TOP STORIES --+ Democrats launch formal Trump impeachment probe + MPs return after shock UK supreme court ruling+ Rescuers battle to save Pakistan quake victims+ US presses China over Uighurs, Hong Kong at UN+ Uruguay upset Fiji in Rugby World CupUS-politics-Congress-Trump,WRAPWASHINGTONTop US Democrat Nancy Pelosi announces the opening of a formal impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump, saying he betrayed his oath of office by...</summary><city>Paris</city><country>FRA</country><xmlText><p>Duty Editor: Barry Parker</p><p>Tel: +33 1 40 41 46 36</p><p></p><p>-- TOP STORIES --</p><p></p><p>+ Democrats launch formal Trump impeachment probe </p><p></p><p>+ MPs return after shock UK supreme court ruling</p><p></p><p>+ Rescuers battle to save Pakistan quake victims</p><p></p><p>+ US presses China over Uighurs, Hong Kong at UN</p><p></p><p>+ Uruguay upset Fiji in Rugby World Cup</p><p></p><p>US-politics-Congress-Trump,WRAP</p><p>WASHINGTON</p><p>Top US Democrat Nancy Pelosi announces the opening of a formal impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump, saying he betrayed his oath of office by seeking help from a foreign power to hurt his Democratic rival Joe Biden. </p><p>850 words moved by Paul Handley with Sebastian Smith in New York. Picture. Video</p><p>We have also moved:</p><p>US-politics-Democrats-Pelosi,PROFILE </p><p>US-politics-Congress-Trump-impeachment,FACTS </p><p>US-politics-justice-Congress-Trump,POINTS </p><p>US-intelligence-politics-Trump,POINTS</p><p></p><p>Britain-EU-Brexit-politics,WRAP</p><p>LONDON</p><p>British MPs return to parliament following a momentous Supreme Court ruling that Prime Minister Boris Johnson's decision to suspend parliament was unlawful.</p><p>700 words 1100 GMT by James Pheby and Alice Ritchie. Picture. Video. Graphic</p><p></p><p>Pakistan-quake,WRAP</p><p>MIRPUR, Pakistan</p><p>Rescue workers battle to reach people affected by a shallow earthquake that rocked northeast Pakistan, killing at least 22 and injuring hundreds more as it tore roads apart and felled buildings.</p><p>650 words at 0930 GMT by Nasir Jaffry and Zain Zaman. Picture. Video. Graphic</p><p></p><p>UN-summit-China-US,FOCUS</p><p>UNITED NATIONS</p><p>The United States ramps up pressure on China at the UN General Assembly, rallying countries against Beijing's treatment of Uighur Muslims and warning it is watching Hong Kong.</p><p>700 words moved by Francesco Fontemaggi. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>RugbyU-WC-2019-FIJ-URU,2ndlead</p><p>KAMAISHI, Japan</p><p>Underdogs Uruguay pull off the greatest win in their history to beat Fiji 30-27, the first upset at the Rugby World Cup in Japan after a pulsating game at the Kamaishi Recovery Stadium.</p><p>600 words 1030 GMT by Charly Triballeau. Picture</p><p>Also moved: </p><p>RugbyU-WC-2019-FIJ-URU-Kamaishi,WRAP</p><p>RugbyU-WC-2019-shocks,FACTS</p><p></p><p>-- UNITED NATIONS -- </p><p></p><p>UN-summit-diplomacy-Britain-Trump,FOCUS</p><p>UNITED NATIONS</p><p>Boris Johnson may be under siege at home, facing calls to resign after a court ruled he acted unlawfully, but in New York the British leader could rely on the support of his chum Donald Trump.</p><p>500 words moved by Peter Hutchison. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>UN-summit-SKorea-NKorea-peace,lead</p><p>UNITED NATIONS</p><p>South Korean President Moon Jae-in proposes that the United Nations create an "international peace zone" to replace the peninsula's divide, saying the idea would both reassure the North and inspire the world.</p><p>500 words moved by Shaun Tandon. Picture</p><p></p><p>UN-summit-Brazil-climate,3RDLEAD</p><p>UNITED NATIONS</p><p>Brazil's President Jair Bolsonaro says it is a lie that the Amazon is being devastated by fire and accuses countries critical of him of having a "colonialist spirit." </p><p>600 words moved by Issam Ahmed. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>UN-summit,WRAP</p><p>UNITED NATIONS</p><p>European leaders hold out hope of arranging a last-minute summit to ease tensions between Iran and the United States, but President Donald Trump vows no let-up in pressure.</p><p>800 words moved by Shaun Tandon and Jerome Cartillier. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- MIDDLE EAST -- </p><p></p><p>Algeria-politics-military-trial,WRAP</p><p>ALGIERS</p><p>In a swift decision handed down out of sight of the media, an Algerian military court sentences the brother of former president Abdelaziz Bouteflika and three co-defendants to 15 years in prison.</p><p>500 words 0930 GMT by Abdelhafid Daamache and Amal Belalloufi. File picture. File video</p><p></p><p>Egypt-politics-Sisi,PROFILE</p><p>CAIRO</p><p>Since ascending to power in 2014, Egypt's general-turned-president Abdel Fattah al-Sisi has imposed himself as an uncontested leader, stamping out opposition despite criticism by rights groups.</p><p>750 words moved by Emmanuel Parisse. File picture. File video</p><p></p><p>Syria-conflict-Russia,SCENE</p><p>YAFOUR, Syria</p><p>Wearing clean bullet-proof vests and knee pads, fighters from a new Syrian amy battalion showcase the skills they have learned from Russia's military advisers.</p><p>450 words 1000 GMT by Maxime Popov. Video. Picture</p><p></p><p>Tunisia-tourism-ThomasCook-Britain,FOCUS</p><p>TUNIS</p><p>British tour operator Thomas Cook going bankrupt may not spell the end of tourism in Tunisia, but it highlights the need to diversify the key sector beyond all-inclusive beach holidays.</p><p>650 words 1100 GMT by Caroline Nelly Perrot. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- AMERICAS --</p><p></p><p>UN-Sweden-climate-US-environment,FOCUS</p><p>WASHINGTON</p><p>Her imperious "How dare you?" to world leaders at the UN cemented Swedish teen Greta Thunberg's role as her generation's leading spokeswoman on climate change, the culmination of a year of dogged relentlessness, say those who know her.</p><p>750 words moved by Ivan Couronne</p><p></p><p>US-media-politics-vote-Facebook</p><p>SAN FRANCISCO</p><p>Facebook will not fact-check the statements politicians post to the site, the social network announces ahead of the US 2020 elections, even as it works to discredit false information meant to manipulate public opinion.</p><p>400 words moved</p><p></p><p>Caribbean-weather-hurricane-economy,FOCUS</p><p>ST. JOHNS, Antigua and Barbuda</p><p>After monster Hurricane Irma annihilated the farm sector of Barbuda in 2017, growers got smart: among other changes, they moved their crops to higher ground.</p><p>800 words moved by Gemma Handy. Picture</p><p></p><p>Brazil-science,FOCUS</p><p>CAMPINAS, Brazil</p><p>Brazilian scientists are racing against time to finish building a particle accelerator the size of the Maracana football stadium before government funds run out or it is superseded by rival technology.</p><p>450 words moved by Paula Ramon. Picture</p><p></p><p>-- AFRICA --</p><p></p><p>Senegal-religion-Islam-mosque,ADVANCER</p><p>DAKAR</p><p>Senegal's influential Mouride brotherhood is set to inaugurate a 30,000-capacity mosque in the capital Dakar, touted as the largest in West Africa and rivalling its most opulent peers in Arab nations.</p><p>450 words 1100 GMT by Malick Rokhy Ba. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- EUROPE -- </p><p></p><p>Austria-politics-vote-far-right,FOCUS</p><p>VIENNA</p><p>Austria's far-right Freedom Party (FPOe) looked to be in serious trouble earlier this year when then leader Heinz-Christian Strache was caught up in a bribery scandal linked to Russia but voters seem unfazed and ready to back the party again in Sunday's elections</p><p>700 words moved by Sophie Makris. Picture</p><p>Also moved:</p><p>Austria-politics-vote-far-right,FACTS</p><p></p><p>France-justice-women-trial</p><p>PARIS</p><p>The woman behind France's answer to the #MeToo campaign exposing male abusive behaviour faces the verdict in a defamation case brought by a media executive she accused of making lewd and sexist remarks.</p><p>400 words moved by Juliette Montesse. File picture</p><p></p><p>Germany-forest-climate-politics,FOCUS</p><p>WELZOW, Germany</p><p>Germany's forests have long been treasured by its people, so the country has reacted with alarm and dismay as a beetle infestation has turned climate-stressed woodlands into brown ecological graveyards.</p><p>700 words moved by Mathieu Foulkes. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- BUSINESS &amp; ECONOMY --</p><p></p><p>Germany-management-governance-Thyssenkrupp,FOCUS</p><p>FRANKFURT</p><p>German industrial giant Thyssenkrupp's announcement that it will replace chief executive Guido Kerkhoff, after years of intense pressure, reflects a broader picture in Germany of top managers struggling to satisfy multiple, competing demands.</p><p>500 words 1100 GMT by Tom Barfield</p><p></p><p>-- ASIA --</p><p></p><p>HongKong-China-politics-unrest</p><p>HONG KONG</p><p>A top Chinese envoy rules out making any further concessions to pro-democracy protesters in Hong Kong, just a day before the city's embattled leader meets the public in a bid to defuse the months of chaos.</p><p>600 words 0900 GMT by Jerome Taylor. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>China-politics-anniversary,ADVANCER</p><p>BEIJING</p><p>China marks 70 years of Communist rule next week, with a massive military parade in Beijing anchoring celebrations of its emergence as a global superpower, despite a damaging year of trade tensions with the US and pro-democracy unrest in Hong Kong.</p><p>850 words moved by Helen Roxburgh. Picture. Graphic.</p><p>Also moved:</p><p>China-politics-anniversary-history,FACTS</p><p></p><p>China-aviation-airport,LEAD</p><p>BEIJING</p><p>A futuristic new airport in Beijing, which is expected to become one of the busiest in the world, is opened by President Xi Jinping.</p><p>550 words moved by Poornima Weerasekara. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- SPORT --</p><p></p><p>Athletics-world-2019-Qatar,ADVANCER</p><p>DOHA</p><p>Qatar is preparing to welcome thousands of fans and competitors for the World Athletics Championships starting Friday, an event seen as a staging post towards the 2022 football World Cup.</p><p>700 words moved by Greg Walton and Ibrahim Badawy. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>-- FASHION --</p><p></p><p>Lifestyle-France-fashion-women-Dior,WRAP </p><p>PARIS </p><p>Dior goes back to nature in its Paris fashion week show with Greta Thunberg plaits and a garden-inspired collection that seemed to spring straight from the earth. </p><p>650 words moved by Fiachra Gibbons. Picture. Video</p><p></p><p>afp</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>