<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ef2d9d5c-909c-40af-93f7-6946fd41f059" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jimmy Golen And Caryn Rousseau</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-FBO--Youth Football-Concussions,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>CHICAGO (AP) — Organized tackle football would be banned for Illinois children younger than 12 years old under a bill to be unveiled on Thursday.The Dave Duerson Act to Prevent CTE is named for the Chicago Bears defensive back who was diagnosed...</summary><sourceId>ef44c63b-6878-4e25-e259-efd9c7cab2c3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL2712%limit%r%BC-FBO--Youth Football-Concussions,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Duerson Act would ban pre-teen tackle football in Illinois</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Updates with details of the bill; comment from bill's author; background.</p><byline xmlns="">By JIMMY GOLEN and CARYN ROUSSEAU</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO (AP) — Organized tackle football would be banned for Illinois children younger than 12 years old under a bill to be unveiled on Thursday.</p><p xmlns="">The Dave Duerson Act to Prevent CTE is named for the Chicago Bears defensive back who was diagnosed with chronic traumatic encephalopathy after he killed himself at the age of 50. Duerson shot himself in the chest so his brain could be studied for signs of the disease that has been linked to concussions or repeated head trauma.</p><p xmlns="">"When my father tragically took his own life, he donated his brain to science in hopes of being part of the solution," said Tregg Duerson, who like his father played football at Notre Dame.</p><p xmlns="">"Thanks to increased attention and research on brain trauma, we know that part of the solution is to guard young children's developing brains from the risks of tackle football," Tregg Duerson said in a statement, a copy of which was obtained by The Associated Press in advance of the announcement. "This bill honors my family's hopes and my father's legacy to protect future athletes and the future of football."</p><p xmlns="">State Rep. Carol Sente, a Democrat from Vernon Hills, announced the proposal at a news conference Thursday along with Chris Nowinski, the head of the Concussion Legacy Foundation. Also expected to attend were former Bears players Mike Adamle and Otis Wilson — a teammate of Dave Duerson's on the 1985 championship team — and Liz Nicholson, the wife of former Cleveland Brown Gerry Sullivan, who has sued the NFL over its handling of concussions.</p><p xmlns="">"We all want kids to have fun playing football and to learn to play the game the right way early on," Sente said in a statement. "But the overwhelming data and powerful stories of our supporters here today show the risks of playing tackle football before turning 12 just aren't worth it."</p><p xmlns="">CTE is a degenerative disease known to cause memory loss, violent moods and other cognitive difficulties in football players, members of the military and others who have endured repeated head trauma. It can only be diagnosed after death. Researchers believe the severity of the symptoms is increased for those who began playing football at a younger age.</p><p xmlns="">After years of denials, the NFL has acknowledged a link between head blows and brain disease and agreed in 2015 to a $1 billion settlement with former players.</p><p xmlns="">The Illinois bill is similar to a proposal in New York, and Nowinski said lawmakers in at least one other state are working to raise the age at which children begin playing tackle football.</p><p xmlns="">"I am confident we have the science on our side and can make a very persuasive argument that safer football for youth will lead to healthier and more rewarding lives for generations to come," Sente said.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">Golen reported from Boston.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>