<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2f72391e-57b2-4200-98d6-50f8f6b7f705" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOTT6KLVRA:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOTT6KLVRA:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYDOTT6KLVRA00000_DNMLENf-20190925080984.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>The Former CEO of Danske Bank in Estonia Has Been Found Dead</title><authors>Ott Ummelas</authors><summary>PYDOTT6KLVRA(Bloomberg) -- The former head of Danske Bank in Estonia has been found dead after he disappeared from his home on Monday morning.Aivar Rehe, who was the chief executive officer of the Danske branch at the center of a $220 billion money laundering scandal until he left in 2015, had been missing since leaving his home in greater Tallinn two days ago. Police had already warned that the 56-year-old, who was wearing a black jogging suit when he disappeared, was in personal danger...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- The former head of Danske Bank in Estonia has been found dead after he disappeared from his home on Monday morning.</p><p>Aivar Rehe, who was the chief executive officer of the Danske branch at the center of a $220 billion money laundering scandal until he left in 2015, had been missing since leaving his home in greater Tallinn two days ago. Police had already warned that the 56-year-old, who was wearing a black jogging suit when he disappeared, was in personal danger with suicide deemed a “likely” scenario.</p><p>Estonia police spokesman Kristjan Lukk said by phone on Wednesday that Rehe has been found dead, without giving further details. A statement will be issued shortly, he added.</p><p>A search in a wooded area around Rehe’s home was ended on Tuesday evening, Lukk said.</p><p>The case has dominated Estonian media since the former executive disappeared. Known as a workaholic, Rehe joined the bank a year before its 2007 takeover by Danske, from a job at the Estonian Tax and Customs Board. He wasn’t a suspect in the laundering investigations and wasn’t among a group of Estonian bankers detained by police last year.</p><p>Valdo Poder, operations chief of the Northern Police Prefecture, told public broadcaster ERR on Tuesday evening, that Rehe’s “actions, domestic situation, and the information we have gathered from his family” all pointed to the possibility of suicide.</p><p>In an interview with local media in March, Rehe said that as the CEO of the Estonian branch, he naturally felt “responsible.” But he also said the unit had a “very normal daily” workflow. “Competent bodies inside and outside the bank did their job to the best of their knowledge,” he told Postimees.</p><p>Danske, which was ordered by Estonia’s regulator to leave the country earlier this year, is now the target of numerous criminal investigations, including in Denmark, Estonia and the U.S. Several of its former executives in Denmark have had preliminary criminal charges brought against them, including former group CEO Thomas Borgen.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Ott Ummelas in Tallinn at oummelas@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Tasneem Hanfi Brögger at tbrogger@bloomberg.net;Christian Wienberg at cwienberg@bloomberg.net</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>