<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="921aaa00-2867-4ac3-bf95-1a9fc711fac3" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDWRFT1UM10:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDWRFT1UM10:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDWRFT1UM1000000_DNMLENf-20190925120967.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Nike ‘Crushed It’ and Now Its Shares Are Poised For Record High</title><authors>Janet Freund</authors><summary>PYDWRFT1UM10(Bloomberg) -- Nike Inc. shares are trading at a record high before the stock market opens Wednesday after fiscal first-quarter results “crushed it,” as Jefferies analyst Randal Konik put it.With impressive strength in sales and gross margins, Nike was able to report quarterly earnings per share that topped even the most bullish Wall Street estimate -- by 13 cents. The beat was especially welcome after the sneaker giant missed the consensus earnings estimate last quarter.Nike...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Nike Inc. shares are trading at a record high before the stock market opens Wednesday after fiscal first-quarter results “crushed it,” as Jefferies analyst Randal Konik put it.</p><p>With impressive strength in sales and gross margins, Nike was able to report quarterly earnings per share that topped even the most bullish Wall Street estimate -- by 13 cents. The beat was especially welcome after the sneaker giant missed the consensus earnings estimate last quarter.</p><p>Nike maintained its year revenue growth target of high-single digits, but boosted its gross margin expansion forecast to 50 to 75 basis points. It had been projecting a 50-basis point increase. “Accelerating investments in digital, supply chain, and product innovation are paving the way for a bright future of continued top-line growth and margin expansion,” Susquehanna’s Sam Poser wrote.</p><p>Shares rose as much as 6.3% pre-market, to $92.65, which would top the stock’s intraday high of $90 back in April.</p><p>Here’s more of what Wall Street had to say following the earnings report:</p><p>Stifel, Jim Duffy</p><p>Macquarie Research, Laurent Vasilescu</p><p>Bloomberg Intelligence“Nike’s strong fiscal 1Q results, led by a double-digit sales gain in constant currency and healthy gross margin expansion, show that it remains well-positioned to deliver on its five-year plan”. “Product innovation, speed to market and digital are catalysts for superior growth to stretch into 2020.”--Analyst Poonam Goyal, click here for note</p><p>Susquehanna, Sam Poser</p><p>Cowen, John Kernan</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Janet Freund in New York at jfreund11@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Catherine Larkin at clarkin4@bloomberg.net, Scott Schnipper</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>