<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e61c28cb-4576-4c35-87c2-b872c790befa" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</summary><sourceId>e8648093-3a79-4c94-c948-cd03e5720eff</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0378%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Baseball</hl2><p xmlns="">OFFICE OF THE COMMISSIONER OF BASEBALL — Suspended Baltimore minor league LHP Tucker Baca (GCL) 60 games after testing positive for Dehydrochlormethyltestosterone, a performance-enhancing substance. Suspended Pittsburgh minor league RHP Montana Durapau (Indianapolis-IL) 50 games following a second positive test for a drug of abuse. Suspended Atlanta minor league LHP Gabriel Noguera (GCL) 50 games following a second positive test for a drug of abuse.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Traded RHP Dominic Leone and RHP Connor Greene to St. Louis for OF Randal Grichuk.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">HOUSTON ASTROS — Promoted Josh Miller to minor league pitching coordinator and Chris Holt to assistant minor league pitching coordinator. Named Josh Bonifay minor league field coordinator; Mark Bailey minor league catching coordinator; Rodney Linares manager and Ray Hernandez development coach for Fresno (PCL); Omar Lopez manager, Bill Murphy pitching coach, Troy Snitker hitting coach and Mycal Jones development coach for Corpus Christi (Texas); Morgan Ensberg manager, Drew French pitching coach, Ben Rosenthal hitting coach and Nate Shaver development coach for Buies Creek (Cal); Mickey Storey manager, Graham Johnson pitching coach, Dillon Lawson hitting coach and Rafael Pena development coach for Quad Cities (MWL); Cesar Cedenn and Rene Rojas hitting coaches for the GCL Astros; Todd Naskedov pitching coordinator and Ralph Dickenson pitching coordinator at the West Palm Beach complex; and Charlie Romero manager and Rick Aponte pitching coach for the Dominican Summer League Astros.</p><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Agreed to terms with 1B Jonathan Rodriguez on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Announced RHP Chasen Bradford was claimed off waivers by Seattle. Announced RHP Kevin McGowan cleared waivers and was sent outright to Las Vegas (PCL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Released INF Trey Vavra and C Mike Falsetti.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed INF Abel Nieves.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed RHP Charle Rosario.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed LHP Jose Velez, INF Josh Silver and RHP Dylan Brammer.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed RHP Aroni Nina and OF Jose R Gomez.</p><p xmlns="">0395</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>