<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="072dcb5c-f281-4951-a3ba-4e9990c79fc4" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G0R7:601764274</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G0R7:601764274</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T080406Z_601764274_L5N26G0R7_RTRMADT_0_EUROZONE-BONDS.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Euro zone bond yields edge down as political risks jangle nerves</title><summary>EUROZONE-BONDS/:Euro zone bond yields edge down as political risks jangle nerves</summary><xmlText><p>Euro zone bond yields edge down as political risks jangle nerves</p><p>By Yoruk  Bahceli</p><p>LONDON, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Euro zone government bond yields edged down on Wednesday, as investors rushed to safe-haven assets in the wake of dismal economic data and heightened political uncertainty this week.</p><p>Democrats in the United States House of Representatives launched a formal impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump on Tuesday, accusing him of seeking foreign help to smear Democratic rival Joe Biden ahead of next year's election.</p><p>Trump also delivered a stinging rebuke to China's trade practices on Tuesday at the United Nations General Assembly, saying he would not accept a "bad deal" in U.S.-China trade negotiations.</p><p>The British parliament is set to reconvene after the UK Supreme Court decided the decision to suspend it for five weeks was unlawful.</p><p>"It's political uncertainty that is dominating, with British parliament opening today. I think they will try to paralyse Johnson with his evil hard Brexit plan. This might be taken as a sign of hope and could stabilise the market," said Bayerische Landesbank rates strategist Norbert Wuthe.</p><p>"But on the other hand we have the impeachment (inquiry) process in the U.S., which could lead to some further safe haven movements."</p><p>Most 10-year benchmark euro zone government bond yields were down 1 to 2 bps on the day</p><p>Political risks have added to investor worries about economic data, sending them flocking into safe-haven government bonds, with Germany's benchmark 10-year bond yield down 9 basis points this week.</p><p>Poor purchasing managers' index readings on Monday and a German business sentiment on Tuesday showed economic outlook expectations deteriorating in Europe.</p><p>Yields on euro zone bonds are at their lowest since Sept. 12, when the European Central Bank unleashed a fresh wave of stimulus measures including rate cuts and asset purchases to boost economic growth and inflation.</p><p>But French consumer confidence data provided a glimmer of hope, exceeding expectations with the reading at its highest level since January 2018.</p><p>In the primary market, Germany is due to auction 3 billion euros of 2029 bonds on Wednesday. (Editing by Jacqueline Wong)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>