<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2a4a0f17-ed3b-4099-968d-661d1995f3de" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G3L3:368933982</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G3L3:368933982</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T120237Z_368933982_L5N26G3L3_RTRMADT_0_SOCCER-SPAIN-FCB-VIL.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Soccer-Pique blames pre-season tour for Barca's slow start</title><summary>SOCCER-SPAIN-FCB-VIL/:Soccer-Pique blames pre-season tour for Barca's slow start</summary><xmlText><p>Soccer-Pique blames pre-season tour for Barca's slow start</p><p>BARCELONA, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Barcelona defender Gerard Pique blamed the club's pre-season trips to the United States and Japan for their shaky start to the season.</p><p>The Catalans narrowly beat Villarreal 2-1 on Tuesday to provisionally move up to fourth in La Liga with 10 points from six games.</p><p>Barcelona have not won away from home all season and failed to keep a clean sheet in the league.</p><p>"We have not been able to train a lot, we have had many trips and it shows, there are players who are still not in form, others who have (injury) discomfort," Pique told reporters.</p><p>"The pre-season we had has not helped us, but this is Barca and there are no excuses."</p><p>Barcelona played Chelsea and Vissel Kobe in Japan in July, before heading back to Catalonia to host Arsenal in the Joan Gamper Trophy.</p><p>The Spanish champions then flew to the United States to play Napoli twice, in Miami and Michigan.</p><p>Six days later they travelled to face Athletic Bilbao in La Liga's opening game, where they capitulated to a 1-0 defeat.</p><p>Luis Suarez suffered an injury in the game and recently returned, but has struggled to find his best form.</p><p>Some supporters whistled the Uruguayan off against Villarreal as he failed to make an impact.</p><p>"I understand that fans have their opinion and express it, but I wouldn't pay too much attention to it," added Pique.</p><p>"We would like to win every game by four or five goals but it's not always possible." (Reporting by Rik Sharma, editing by Pritha Sarkar)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>