<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="bef82943-4297-4638-82bf-dfdcec90c296" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDZLYT0AFB8:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDZLYT0AFB8:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYDZLYT0AFB800000_DNMLENf-20190925120985.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Philip Morris, Altria End Merger Talks</title><authors>Lisa Wolfson and Corinne Gretler</authors><summary>PYDZLYT0AFB8(Bloomberg) -- Philip Morris International Inc. and Altria Group Inc. ended merger talks, walking away from a deal that would have reunited the giants of the U.S. and international tobacco industries and pointed them both to a future beyond cigarettes.The unwinding of the talks, which would have been the largest since AT&amp;T Inc.’s bid for Time Warner in 2016, comes amid a health crisis over the use of electronic cigarette devices that have sickened more than 500 people and been...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Philip Morris International Inc. and Altria Group Inc. ended merger talks, walking away from a deal that would have reunited the giants of the U.S. and international tobacco industries and pointed them both to a future beyond cigarettes.</p><p>The unwinding of the talks, which would have been the largest since AT&amp;T Inc.’s bid for Time Warner in 2016, comes amid a health crisis over the use of electronic cigarette devices that have sickened more than 500 people and been blamed for at least seven deaths. Separately, Altria Chief Strategy and Growth Officer K.C. Crosthwaite stepped down from the company to become CEO of vaping company Juul Labs Inc., replacing Kevin Burns, who is leaving.</p><p>“While we believed the creation of a new merged company had the potential to create incremental revenue and cost synergies, we could not reach agreement,” said Howard Willard, Altria’s chairman and chief executive officer. Both he and Philip Morris CEO André Calantzopoulos said the companies would focus on launching PMI’s IQOS heat-not-burn device in the U.S.</p><p>Shares of Philip Morris jumped more than 5% in early trading, while Altria rose about 1%.</p><p>When asked to elaborate on why the deal talks ended, Philip Morris declined to comment, and an Altria spokesman couldn’t immediately be reached.</p><p>Philip Morris, the maker of Marlboro cigarettes in overseas markets, and Altria said in August that they were in talks to reunite more than 10 years after splitting their operations.</p><p>The deal was aimed at challenges stemming from shrinking cigarette sales, after Altria invested $12.8 billion in e-cigarette upstart Juul. A reunification would have combined two of the most popular smoking alternative products: Philip Morris’s IQOS and Juul. Altria has also invested in cannabis companies and holds a 10% stake in beer giant Anheuser-Busch InBev.</p><p>Altria’s tobacco business has been hit particularly hard by the smoking decline in the U.S., giving the company more reason to entertain a deal. But the sudden backlash against vaping made a combination less appealing.</p><p>(Adds comment from Altria CEO)</p><p>--With assistance from Tiffany Kary.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Lisa Wolfson in Boston at lwolfson@bloomberg.net;Corinne Gretler in Zurich at cgretler1@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Anne Riley Moffat at ariley17@bloomberg.net, Eric Pfanner</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>