<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8bc722f2-7374-4e87-914a-1a30bc6d5d12" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G25W:1103651517</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G25W:1103651517</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T092727Z_1103651517_L5N26G25W_RTRMADT_0_EASTEUROPE-MARKETS.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>CEE MARKETS-Forint loses ground after central bank's dovish turn</title><summary>EASTEUROPE-MARKETS/:CEE MARKETS-Forint loses ground after central bank's dovish turn</summary><xmlText><p>CEE MARKETS-Forint loses ground after central bank's dovish turn</p><p>    By Krisztina  Than     BUDAPEST, Sept 25 (Reuters) - The Hungarian forint resumed its downward trend on Wednesday, after the central bank projected lower inflation and an economic slowdown and shifted to a more dovish stance.     Czech rate setters will hold a policy meeting on Wednesday, where they are expected to keep main interest rates on hold despite the European Central Bank and the U.S. Federal Reserve's policy easing.         The forint bounced back from a record low against the euro on Tuesday after the central bank kept interest rates at the lowest level in Central Europe, shrugging off the slide in the currency.      The bank even announced a moderate liquidity adjustment for the fourth quarter of 2019, which analysts said amounted to a mild loosening.        "This suggests further forint weakening but for the time being, the 'buy on the rumour sell on the news' sentiment could work," Erste analysts said in a note.      They said on a technical basis, there was room for further short-term gains but "the forint is and could remain on an easing path".     Some other analysts said the forint, which slumped to an all-time low of 336.10 to the euro on Tuesday before the central bank meeting, could recover on solid economic fundamentals.     "In addition, the dovish ECB and U.S. Fed should support CEE currencies going forward," Raiffeisen said in a note.     The Hungarian central bank said downward inflation risks have strengthened further as the euro zone economy slows.      By 0807 GMT, the forint was down 0.1% at 334.44 against the euro, off its all-time low, but weaker than 333.57 hit after the central bank's meeting on Tuesday. The Polish zloty and the Czech crown lost 0.1% each.     The Czech National Bank (CNB) is likely to hold interest rates unchanged through 2020 as it balances inflationary pressures at home with policy easing and economic weakness abroad, a Reuters poll showed on Monday.     Czech forward rates have stayed stable this month after having scaled back previous rate-cut expectations. The market still prices in a rate cut by the middle of 2020      Stock markets across the region headed south, with Prague , Warsaw and Budapest all trading about 1% lower at 0840 GMT, amid a worse international sentiment on trade war jitters.                    CEE      SNAPSHO   AT                                          MARKETS  T        1007                                                    CET                                            CURRENC                                                        IES                                                     Latest   Previou  Daily    Change                                      s                                              bid      close    change   in 2019  EURCZK  Czech     &lt;EURCZK  25.8860  25.8600   -0.10%   -0.69%  =       crown     =&gt;                                    EURHUF  Hungary   &lt;EURHUF  334.440  334.200   -0.07%   -3.99%  =       forint    =&gt;             0        0             EURPLN  Polish    &lt;EURPLN   4.3829   4.3790   -0.09%   -2.13%  =       zloty     =&gt;                                    EURRON  Romanian  &lt;EURRON   4.7490   4.7490   +0.00%   -2.00%  =       leu       =&gt;                                    EURHRK  Croatian  &lt;EURHRK   7.4080   7.4035   -0.06%   +0.03%  =       kuna      =&gt;                                    EURRSD  Serbian   &lt;EURRSD  117.370  117.605   +0.20%   +0.79%  =       dinar     =&gt;             0        0                     Note:     calculated from            1800                      daily                                CET                change                                                                                                                                    Latest   Previou  Daily    Change                                      s                                                       close    change   in 2019  .PX     Prague             1037.45  1047.57   -0.97%   +5.16%                                           00             .BUX    Budapest           40545.4  40848.0   -0.74%   +3.59%                                   8        4             .WIG20  Warsaw    &lt;.WIG20  2153.89  2175.24   -0.98%   -5.39%                    &gt;                                     .BETI   Buchares           9490.97  9483.43   +0.08%   +28.54          t                                                   %  .SBITO  Ljubljan  &lt;.SBITO   856.63   858.09   -0.17%   +6.51%  P       a         P&gt;                                    .CRBEX  Zagreb    &lt;.CRBEX  1924.48  1923.06   +0.07%   +10.05                    &gt;                                         %  .BELEX  Belgrade  &lt;.BELEX   752.96   753.45   -0.07%   -1.15%  15                15&gt;                                   .SOFIX  Sofia     &lt;.SOFIX   570.40   572.20   -0.31%   -4.05%                    &gt;                                                                BONDS                                                          Yield    Yield    Spread   Daily                             (bid)    change   vs Bund  change                                                        in          Czech                                         spread          Republic                                        CZ2YT=    2-year  &lt;CZ2YT=   1.3570   0.0020   +208bp    +1bps  RR                RR&gt;                              s    CZ5YT=    5-year  &lt;CZ5YT=   1.0890  -0.0660   +188bp    -6bps  RR                RR&gt;                              s    CZ10YT            &lt;CZ10YT   1.3240  -0.0090   +194bp    +0bps  =RR     10-year   =RR&gt;                             s            Poland                                                 PL2YT=    2-year  &lt;PL2YT=   1.4820   0.0040   +220bp    +1bps  RR                RR&gt;                              s    PL5YT=    5-year  &lt;PL5YT=   1.7980  -0.0230   +258bp    -2bps  RR                RR&gt;                              s    PL10YT            &lt;PL10YT   2.0390  -0.0110   +265bp    +0bps  =RR     10-year   =RR&gt;                             s                      FORWARD  RATE     AGREEME                                                        NT                                             3x6      6x9      9x12     3M                                                        interba                                                        nk          Czech     &lt;CZKFRA     2.16     2.09     1.95     2.14          Rep       &gt;&lt;PRIBO                                                 R=&gt;                                           Hungary   &lt;HUFFRA     0.28     0.27     0.37     0.21                    &gt;&lt;BUBOR                                                 =&gt;                                            Poland    &lt;PLNFRA     1.72     1.70     1.66     1.72                    &gt;&lt;WIBOR                                                 =&gt;                                            Note:     are for ask                                          FRA       prices                                        quotes                                                 (Reporting by Krisztina Than in Budapest and Jason Hovet in Prague, Editing by Subhranshu Sahu)   </p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>