<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2bee4992-dd0a-9205-8dbb-fe8634e2180e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Bryce Miller</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-FBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — You ask Al Michaels how long ago that first Super Bowl he called feels, No. 22 to us non-Romans — the one played in San Diego 30 years ago as Doug Williams made history and the Redskins made mincemeat of the Broncos defense in a...</summary><sourceId>113a7df7-b930-cdef-def3-f38f8e4c3c28</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K4308%kniht%r%BC-FBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Bryce Miller: Al Michaels prepares to ‘shake my booty’ 30 years after Super Bowl run began</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Bryce Miller</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — You ask Al Michaels how long ago that first Super Bowl he called feels, No. 22 to us non-Romans — the one played in San Diego 30 years ago as Doug Williams made history and the Redskins made mincemeat of the Broncos defense in a single quarter.</p><p xmlns="">Then you really apply the heat.</p><p xmlns="">It was this long ago: The national anthem came from the trumpet of Herb Alpert, festivities included a tribute to Bob Hope and that set of gyrating halftime hips belonged to Chubby Checker.</p><p xmlns="">Michaels laughed.</p><p xmlns="">He’s about to call his 10th Super Bowl, joining Pat Summerall (11) as the only broadcasters to push play-by-play duties into double digits. He also has been publicly challenged by Justin Timberlake, this year’s halftime entertainment, to “shake his booty” when the Patriots meet the Eagles on Sunday in Minneapolis (3:30 p.m., NBC).</p><p xmlns="">“As a guy who, when I was in high school, could dance only one dance and it was called The Twist, I love that Chubby Checker was the entertainment,” Michaels, 73, told the Union-Tribune. “Now Timberlake wants me to shake my booty. If you’re battling spinal stenosis, it’s not really a good thing to do. But I’ve got to do something.</p><p xmlns="">“My 8-year-old granddaughter knows all about this and wants to give me lessons. She’s like ‘Pop-pop, I can help.’ So sometime, I’ll be attempting to shake one’s booty — but not very effectively, I can guarantee you.”</p><p xmlns="">The game that unfolded at the old Murph on Jan. 31, 1988, found itself bathed in the storyline of Williams, the first black quarterback to start a Super Bowl. The Broncos rushed in front 10-0 before a 35-point, second-quarter blitz — as Williams threw four touchdowns — sealed the outcome before Checker had time warm up his midsection.</p><p xmlns="">Brief moments of scintillation morphed into a San Diego snoozer.</p><p xmlns="">“When the game starts and Denver takes a 10-0 lead, I kind of looked over at Dan Dierdorf and he’s got that look, ‘Oh, no, are we in for another rout?’ ” said Michaels, ticking off the underwhelming majority of the 21 games that came before.</p><p xmlns="">“Little could we have imagined, we were in for another rout, but the rout was going to be turned around. … Dan and I looked at each other at halftime and went, ‘We can’t believe this.’ ”</p><p xmlns="">Michaels’ Super Bowl highlights came, in time. And when they did, the plays became legendary — and forever.</p><p xmlns="">He was there in 2000, when Mike Jones of the Rams tackled straining Kevin Dyson of Tennessee on the final play — one yard short in a 23-16 heart-stopper. He was there in 2009, when Pittsburgh’s James Harrison ran an interception back a Super Bowl-record 100 yards to stagger Arizona.</p><p xmlns="">He was there in 2015, when Seattle made the most controversial play call in Super Bowl history by opting not to use Marshawn Lynch on second-and-goal from the 1. Instead, Malcolm Butler cut off a quick slant for an interception that sealed another one of New England’s improbable escapes.</p><p xmlns="">“I’ve done some of the most iconic plays in the history of the Super Bowl,” Michaels said.</p><p xmlns="">Michaels has read the rumblings about his status remaining in question after this season. A piece on The Big Lead referenced a story from four years ago that indicated his contract ended after this Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">Update: He’ll be back.</p><p xmlns="">“My contract goes longer than this year,” Michaels said. “We extended it. … It’ll be next year for sure, then we’ll see after that. I don’t want to put a number on this whole thing.</p><p xmlns="">“I love what I’m doing. It’s the greatest job in the world.”</p><p xmlns="">Sharing the Super Bowl first with Michaels was Dierdorf, who was coming off of his rookie season in football’s most prominent booth.</p><p xmlns="">“It was kind of a whirlwind for me,” Dierdorf said. “In April, I signed with ABC. All of a sudden it’s football season and I’m doing ‘Monday Night Football.’ I jumped right on the treadmill and it was going full speed.</p><p xmlns="">“But it didn’t take me long to figure out that Al Michaels was different and that he was special.”</p><p xmlns="">The former offensive tackle who carved out a Hall of Fame career soon began picking the brain of Michaels, shaping his broadcasting approach to the treacherous footing on Monday nights.</p><p xmlns="">“Al said, don’t take for granted the size of the club you wield when you do ‘Monday Night Football,’ ” Dierdorf said. “And he was right. It was a sobering piece of advice. I tried to always be prepared. An opinion’s one thing, but you’re going to say something, make every effort to make sure you’re right.</p><p xmlns="">“The second thing Al told me, is that you’re never going to get everything in. When you leave, your saddlebags are going to be half full. Don’t try to jam the square peg into the round hole. Timing was always a strength of Al. He’s just a gifted guy.”</p><p xmlns="">That undimmed skill will be on display this weekend for millions in bars and man caves across America. Again.</p><p xmlns="">This time, however, a 73-year-old booty will be at the ready.</p><p xmlns="">“Having known Al for all these years and knowing him as well as I do,” Dierdorf said, “all I can say is, please, please, please don’t.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000046469,t000003194,t000424479,t000003183,t000381264</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>