<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7a214d2e-7932-4de3-b5a4-ba499573da83" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0447</summary><sourceId>14fd9208-f466-4acc-acc9-c111067e6eff</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5556%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0447</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Agreed to terms with RHPs Rob Scahill, Chris Volstad and Michael Ynoa, LHP T.J. House and INFs Patrick Leonard and Matt Skole on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with C Jack Murphy and LHP Adam Wilk on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">HOUSTON ASTROS — Claimed LHP Buddy Boshers off waivers from Minnesota.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Agreed to terms with OF Tyler Collins on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO CUBS — Agreed to terms with LHP Brian Duensing on a two-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Agreed to terms with C Ryan Lavarnway on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY T-BONES — Signed RHP Jake Matthys.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed RHP JR Bunda and OF Brandon Jacobs.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed INF Leo Vargas.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">QUEBEC CAPITALES — Signed OF James McOwen.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed LHP Colton Freeman and INF Trae Santos.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BUCKS — Fired coach Jason Kidd.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">DELAWARE 87ERS — Acquired G Donte McGill from the available player pool.</p><p xmlns="">RIO GRANDE VALLEY VIPERS — Signed G Kyle Davis.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA CARDINALS — Named Steve Wilks coach.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA FALCONS — Named Greg Knapp quarterbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA PANTHERS — Named Eric Washington defensive coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Signed OT Dieugot Joseph, DT Caushaud Lyons, OT Cedrick Lang, DE Ifeadi Odenigbo, CB Horace Richardson and LB Antwione Williams to reserve/futures contracts.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK GIANTS — Named Pat Shurmur coach.</p><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SEAHAWKS — Mutually parted ways with defensive assistant coach Travis Jones .</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Signed RB Korliss Marshall.</p><hl2 xmlns="">GYMNASTICS</hl2><p xmlns="">USA GYMNASTICS — Announced the resignations of chairman Paul Parilla, vice chairman Jay Binder and treasurer Bitsy Kelly.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Acquired D John Ramage from Columbus for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Activated C Artem Anisimov from injured reserve.</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Recalled F Jason Dickinson from Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Traded G Jeff Zatkoff to Columbus for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Recalled D Mirco Mueller from Binghamton (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Syracuse F Alex Gallant two games and Laval F Jeremy Gregoire one game.</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Released F Chris Langkow from his professional tryout agreement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED — Announced F Tito Villalba obtained his U.S. green card and no longer occupies an international spot on the club's roster.</p><p xmlns="">LA GALAXY — Signed M Chris Pontius.</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Signed D Matt Lewis to a one-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK COSMOS — Agreed on a transfer fee with the San Jose M Eric Calvillo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CUMBERLAND (TENN.) — Named Tim Mathis football coach.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN STATE — Named Don Treadwell assistant football coach and offensive consultant.</p><p xmlns="">WAGNER — Announced the addition of women's field hockey that will compete as a club team in the 2018-19 academic year before being elevated to Division I varsity status in 2019-2020.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON STATE — Named Patrick Chun athletic director.</p><p xmlns=""></p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>