<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7c2f8be2-4300-44f7-a3a8-996c93ff8252" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_FLM4c9QRF:574644551</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_FLM4c9QRF:574644551</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T074934Z_574644551_FLM4C9QRF_RTRMADT_0_BASEBALL-MLB-SF-COL-RECAP.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Blackmon homers in 16th to lift Rockies past Giants</title><summary>BASEBALL-MLB-SF-COL: </summary><xmlText><p>Blackmon homers in 16th to lift Rockies past Giants</p><p>The visiting Colorado Rockies spoiled the opening of Bruce Bochy Appreciation Week Tuesday night, belting five home runs, including a tiebreaking, three-run shot by Charlie Blackmon in the 16th inning, en route to an 8-5 victory over the San Francisco Giants in the opener of a three-game series.</p><p>The Giants (75-82) are celebrating the final week of Bochy's 25-year career with six home games, the last three against the Los Angeles Dodgers following the Colorado series.</p><p>Tuesday's loss was the 2,026th of Bochy's career and dropped his record with the Giants to 1,050-1,051.</p><p>After San Francisco ace Madison Bumgarner homered in the third and left a 4-4 tie after seven innings, the Rockies' Garrett Hampson and Giants' Evan Longoria traded eighth-inning home runs, setting up Blackmon's eventual heroics.</p><p>Hampson got the 16th rolling against the 12th Giants pitcher, Dereck Rodriguez (8-10), with a one-out single. After Nolan Arenado followed with an infield hit, Blackmon bombed his 31st homer to center field, giving the Rockies (68-89) just their seventh win in 17 head-to-heads with San Francisco this season.</p><p>Sam Howard (2-0), the 11th Rockies pitcher, was credited with the win after throwing two shutout innings. Bryan Shaw notched his first save with a 1-2-3 bottom of the 16th.</p><p>Hampson had a two-homer game, the first of his two-year career, to raise his season total to eight. Ian Desmond (19th) and Trevor Story (34th) also homered for the Rockies.</p><p>Bumgarner allowed four runs and six hits, including three homers, in his seven innings. He walked two and struck out nine.</p><p>He is also tentatively scheduled to pitch Bochy's finale on Sunday.</p><p>Bumgarner's homer was one of three hit by the Giants, who led 3-1 after the power-hitting pitcher went deep for the first time this season in the third inning.</p><p>Buster Posey (seventh) also homered for the Giants.</p><p>Rockies starter Jeff Hoffman went 3 1/3 innings before getting nailed in the right knee with a line drive off the bat of Alex Dickerson. Hoffman had to be carted off the field.</p><p>He was charged with three runs on three hits in his 3 1/3 innings. He walked three and struck out three.</p><p>Hampson had three hits and scored three times for the Rockies, who won for just the second time in their last six games.</p><p>Posey collected two hits, two runs and two RBIs for the Giants.</p><p>--Field Level Media</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>