<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b4e5ea54-45d1-4ab7-9480-7d3886db75c1" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T121720Z:TX-PAR-EJM67:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T121720Z:TX-PAR-EJM67:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T121720Z-TX-PAR-EJM67.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Wrightbus</item><item>N.Ireland</item><item>Britain</item><item>administration</item><item>London</item><item>enterprises</item><item>transport</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>London red bus maker Wrightbus enters administration</title><authors></authors><summary>Wrightbus, the manufacturers of London's iconic red "double decker" buses, entered administration on Wednesday, a spokesman for the company confirmed.Wrightbus is best known for supplying New Routemaster buses to Transport for London (TFL) under the mayorship of Boris Johnson, who is now Britain's prime minister.Based in Ballymena, Northern Ireland, the company is one of the province's largest employers.The Unite union has predicted 1,300 job losses with a further 3,400 jobs endangered...</summary><city>Dublin</city><country>IRL</country><xmlText><p>Wrightbus, the manufacturers of London's iconic red "double decker" buses, entered administration on Wednesday, a spokesman for the company confirmed.</p><p>Wrightbus is best known for supplying New Routemaster buses to Transport for London (TFL) under the mayorship of Boris Johnson, who is now Britain's prime minister.</p><p>Based in Ballymena, Northern Ireland, the company is one of the province's largest employers.</p><p>The Unite union has predicted 1,300 job losses with a further 3,400 jobs endangered throughout the supply chain.</p><p>A spokesman for Wrightbus confirmed the business -- founded in 1946 -- had entered administration, but told AFP that a statement was not planned on Wednesday.</p><p>The administration procedure is to be undertaken by Deloitte.</p><p>DUP MP Ian Paisley said the administrator now "has a week to find a buyer".</p><p>Wrightbus -- which based its business model on production of low-emissions vehicles -- has been seeking investment or a new owner as it struggles with cash problems.</p><p>"This is a workforce at the cutting edge of technological advancements in the design and supply of green public transport," said Jackie Pollock, regional secretary of the Unite trade union.</p><p>"We cannot afford to lose any more jobs or skills in this area."</p><p>As recently as 2016 the firm was awarded a £62 million ($77 million, 70 million euro) contract to produce the vehicles for the streets of the capital.</p><p>The iconic red "double decker" vehicles with a sleek updated design were dubbed "Boris buses", becoming a flagship project for the capital's then-leader.</p><p>But they were plagued with cost overrun and design issues -- including ventilation problems which saw passengers suffer in uncomfortable heat.</p><p>Pollock called on Johnson to intervene if no buyer is found.</p><p>"He has a chance today to do something decent," Pollock said.</p><p>jts/dt/cw</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>