<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="118b8031-1e70-465d-8d56-f350c07b294c" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T113801Z:TX-PAR-EJL49:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T113801Z:TX-PAR-EJL49:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T113801Z-TX-PAR-EJL49.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Indonesia</item><item>religion</item><item>politics</item><item>demonstration</item><item>Suharto</item><item>Joko Widodo</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Indonesia students rally again to protest major changes to laws</title><authors></authors><summary>Indonesian students Wednesday rallied for a third day over moves to introduce sweeping changes to the country's laws after hundreds were sent to hospital following clashes with riot police.The demonstrations erupted in response to a proposed criminal-code overhaul that includes everything from criminalising pre-marital sex and restricting sales of contraceptives, to making it illegal to insult the president and toughening the Muslim majority country's blasphemy laws.There has also been a...</summary><city>Jakarta</city><country>IDN</country><xmlText><p>Indonesian students Wednesday rallied for a third day over moves to introduce sweeping changes to the country's laws after hundreds were sent to hospital following clashes with riot police.</p><p>The demonstrations erupted in response to a proposed criminal-code overhaul that includes everything from criminalising pre-marital sex and restricting sales of contraceptives, to making it illegal to insult the president and toughening the Muslim majority country's blasphemy laws.</p><p>There has also been a public backlash against a separate bill that critics fear would dilute the investigative powers of Indonesia's corruption-fighting agency -- known as the KPK -- including its ability to wire-tap graft suspects.</p><p>"This bill will obviously weaken the KPK and cause corruption to run rampant -- and that's going to hurt people," Angga Prasetyo, a 22-year-old engineering student in protest-hit Makassar on Sulawesi island, told AFP on Wednesday.</p><p>The rallies are among the biggest anti-government demonstrations since 1998 when mass street protests brought down the three-decade Suharto dictatorship.</p><p>Students have issued a list of demands including scrapping some of the criminal-code changes, withdrawing troops from Indonesia's unrest-hit Papua region, and halting forest fires in Sumatra and Borneo that have unleashed toxic haze across Southeast Asia.</p><p>Hundreds rallied in the capital Jakarta -- as did scores in the second-biggest city Surabaya, and in Borneo on Tuesday -- but the crowds were smaller than the thousands who took to the streets nationwide the previous day.</p><p>On Tuesday, police fired tear gas and water cannon to disperse protesters in chaotic scenes that saw about 300 people -- including dozens of officers -- sent to hospital for treatment with hundreds arrested, according to police officials. Most had minor injuries, authorities said.</p><p>A vote on the criminal code bill was originally scheduled for Tuesday.</p><p>But President Joko Widodo last week called for a delay in passing controversial changes that could affect millions of Indonesians, including gay and heterosexual couples who might face jail for having sex outside wedlock, or having an affair.</p><p>Updating Indonesia's criminal code, which dates back to the Dutch colonial era, has been debated for decades and appeared set to pass in 2018 before momentum fizzled out.</p><p>A renewed push this year, backed by conservative Islamic groups, was met with a wave of criticism over what many saw as a draconian law that invaded the bedrooms of a nation with some 260 million people -- the fourth most populous on Earth.</p><p>bur-pb/rbu</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>