<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2f45792e-5bd2-41e5-981b-1649741dd4d7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Anti-Bullying Video</title><summary>LEBANON, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee high school student's anti-bullying video has drawn nearly 600,000 views on YouTube and netted a two-day suspension for its 16-year-old creator. Emily Gipson tells news outlets school that administrators accused...</summary><sourceId>efccf9b8-52a5-494c-94cb-8be556b7145f</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:e2905%tntn-%r%BC-US--Anti-Bullying Video;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Viral anti-bullying video nets teen girl a school suspension</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. PMS refire. Link video if it becomes available. New heads, precoded on planner, sorhold.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">LEBANON, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee high school student's anti-bullying video has drawn nearly 600,000 views on YouTube and netted a two-day suspension for its 16-year-old creator. Emily Gipson tells news outlets school that administrators accused her of "trying to incite violence" and handed her the in-school suspension for the video entitled "Welcome to Lebanon High School." Her free-verse speech contained no profanity but likened school to an "emotional prison" and complained that bullies there go unpunished.</p><p xmlns="">Principal Scott Walters told The Lebanon Democrat he can't discuss the 16-year-old's punishment, but said he took issue with the fact that the free-verse speech was recorded in a classroom without a teacher's permission. Gipson disputed that, saying she had two coaches' permission.</p><p xmlns="">Walters also said the video hurt his feelings, and those of teachers, too.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>