<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0183a94d-739c-4ea9-a03b-2b9c253fa814" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0599</summary><sourceId>b1ec5147-0748-456d-56db-ff189d343fa8</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8636%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0599</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY RAYS — Fired team physician Michael Reilly.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA DIAMONDBACKS — Agreed to terms with C Alex Avila on a two-year contract. Designated OF Rey Fuentes for assignment.</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Named Dave Joppie hitting coach for Colorado Springs (PCL); Dave Chavarria pitching coach and Al LeBoeuf hitting coach for Biloxi (SL); Sandy Guerrero hitting coach for Carolina (Carolina); and Connor McCarthy strength and conditioning specialist for Wisconsin (MWL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Traded LHP Josh Smoker to Pittsburgh Pirates for LHP Daniel Zamora and cash.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed LHP Kenny Roder.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA PANTHERS — Named Chase Blackburn special teams coordinator, Brady Hoke defensive line coach, Steve Russ linebackers coach, Scott Turner quarterbacks coach, Heath Farwell assistant special teams coach and Travelle Wharton assistant offensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND BROWNS — Signed TE Devon Cajuste, DB Denzel Rice and OL Christian Schneider.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Named Pat O'Hara quarterbacks coach, Kerry Coombs secondary coach, Shane Bowen outside linebackers coach, Tyrone McKenzie inside linebackers coach and Rob Moore wide receivers coach. Promoted Craig Aukerman to special teams coach.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NHL — Fined New Jersey F Taylor Hall $5,000 for a boarding penalty against Buffalo F Kyle Okposo, during a Jan. 30 game.</p><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Recalled DKyle Capobianco from Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Recalled F A.J. Greer from San Antonio (AHL). Reassigned D David Warsofsky to San Antonio.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Reassigned F Oskar Sundqvist to San Antonio (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Orlando's Aleksandr Mikulovich one game and fined him an undisclosed amount for his actions during a Jan. 29 game at Atlanta. Suspended Kalamazoo's Justin Taylor one game and fined him an undisclosed amount for his actions during a Jan. 28 game against Indy.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RED BULLS — Added MF Marc Rzatkowski on loan from Red Bull Salzburg (Austria).</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Acquired F Johnny Russell in a transfer from Derby County (EFL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">SACRAMENTO REPUBLIC FC — Named Todd Dunivant general manager.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CALIFORNIA — Announced the resignation of men's rowing coach Mike Teti after the 2018 season to become coach of the U.S. Men's National Team.</p><p xmlns="">GEORGETOWN — Named Patrick Murphy offensive coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>