<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="bf047880-df68-45ed-a332-57f0fe9762df" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T071930Z:TX-PAR-EJF77:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T071930Z:TX-PAR-EJF77:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T071930Z-TX-PAR-EJF77.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>US</item><item>mass-media</item><item>merger</item><item>internet</item><item>NewYorkmagazine</item><item>Denzel Washington</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Vox Media and owner of 'New York' magazine to merge</title><authors></authors><summary>Vox Media announced a merger agreement Tuesday with New York Media, home of the prestigious "New York" magazine and a series of other titles.   A joint statement presented the move as a merger, although Jim Bankoff, the head of Vox will "lead all aspects" of the new company and the New York Times reported that New York Media would be "effectively taking a minority stake" in Vox. Launched in 1968 New York magazine has become a prominent voice in culture and lifestyle writing in its home city...</summary><city>New York</city><country>USA</country><xmlText><p>Vox Media announced a merger agreement Tuesday with New York Media, home of the prestigious "New York" magazine and a series of other titles.   </p><p>A joint statement presented the move as a merger, although Jim Bankoff, the head of Vox will "lead all aspects" of the new company and the New York Times reported that New York Media would be "effectively taking a minority stake" in Vox. </p><p>Launched in 1968 New York magazine has become a prominent voice in culture and lifestyle writing in its home city and beyond, winning dozens of National Magazine Awards and a Pulitzer in 2018 for criticism.</p><p>The 1977 classic film "Saturday Night Fever" was inspired by an article that appeared in the magazine, as was 2007's "American Gangster" starring Denzel Washington.</p><p>New York Media also owns a stable of websites on style (The Cut), food (Grub Street) and pop culture (Vulture).</p><p>The company was running at a loss before the announcement, according to the New York Times.</p><p>Vox Media, a child of the internet, was founded in 2005 originally as a network of sports websites.  </p><p>In recent years Vox and New York Media have sought to diversify, into podcasts, video production and event organizing.</p><p>The merger comes as many online-only players like Buzzfeed, Vice and HuffPost also look to partnerships with rivals after seeing advertising revenues decimated by Facebook and Google.</p><p>The joint statement said the deal was expected to be finalised in the fall.</p><p>tu/cn/rma/ind</p><p>Facebook</p><p>THE NEW YORK TIMES COMPANY</p><p>GOOGLE</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>