<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7a072342-98b9-4e00-bf57-d71a9e806c53" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T130844Z:TX-PAR-EJN61:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T130844Z:TX-PAR-EJN61:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T130844Z-TX-PAR-EJN61.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Britain</item><item>US</item><item>retail</item><item>merger</item><item>earnings</item><item>Sainsburys</item><item>Asda</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UK supermarket Sainsbury's says to slash costs</title><authors></authors><summary>British supermarket Sainsbury's, which failed to merge with Walmart-owned Asda earlier this year, unveiled Wednesday a major cost-cutting plan.Sainsbury's will seek to axe £500 million ($623 million, 566 million euros) in costs over the next five years, it announced in a trading update, which also revealed sliding quarterly sales amid fierce competition.The company will shutter up to 70 standalone branches of catalogue division Argos -- but will also open another 80 Argos units inside its...</summary><city>London</city><country>GBR</country><xmlText><p>British supermarket Sainsbury's, which failed to merge with Walmart-owned Asda earlier this year, unveiled Wednesday a major cost-cutting plan.</p><p>Sainsbury's will seek to axe £500 million ($623 million, 566 million euros) in costs over the next five years, it announced in a trading update, which also revealed sliding quarterly sales amid fierce competition.</p><p>The company will shutter up to 70 standalone branches of catalogue division Argos -- but will also open another 80 Argos units inside its existing Sainsbury's stores.</p><p>Sainsbury's will also close 15 large supermarkets and 40 smaller convenience stores, but at the same time will also open ten big stores and some 110 convenience outlets.</p><p>The London-listed retail giant did not specify how many jobs are due to be shed, but the overhaul is forecast to cost between £230 million and £270 million.</p><p>And it warned that this year's first-half profits would take a £50-million hit from the restructuring, unseasonal weather and high marketing costs.</p><p>Sainsbury's also revealed falling sales in the second quarter of the group's financial year, or 12 weeks to September 21, compared with a year earlier.</p><p>Britain's long-established supermarkets are suffering from the weak economic climate before the nation's departure from the European Union next month.</p><p>They also continue to battle intense competition from German-owned discounters Aldi and Lidl, as well as online rival Amazon.</p><p>Back in May, a mega-merger of Sainsbury's and British-based rival Asdsa collapsed because regulators blocked the deal on the grounds it would spark higher prices and damage competition.</p><p>jbo/rfj/bcp/cw</p><p>J. SAINSBURY PLC</p><p>AMAZON.COM</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>