<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="cdc90fac-7269-4844-a7b1-0decab3570ad" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2EV:1556389343</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2EV:1556389343</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T094619Z_1556389343_L3N26G2EV_RTRMADT_0_SOCCER-FRANCE-AMO-GOLOVIN-PIX.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Soccer-Polished Golovin delivers for struggling Monaco</title><summary>SOCCER-FRANCE-AMO/GOLOVIN (PIX):Soccer-Polished Golovin delivers for struggling Monaco</summary><xmlText><p>Soccer-Polished Golovin delivers for struggling Monaco</p><p>PARIS, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Russian midfielder Aleksandr Golovin finally made his impact at Monaco by scoring two superb goals and setting up another to give his side their first win of the Ligue 1 season on Tuesday.</p><p>The 23-year-old delivered a man-of-the-match performance in the 3-1 victory against neighbours Nice, justifying his 30-million euro ($33.01 million) price tag after being transferred from CSKA Moscow last year.</p><p>For coach Leonardo Jardim, back on the Monaco bench in early 2019 less than three months after being sacked, Golovin's breakthrough was expected.</p><p>The central midfielder struggled in his first season, but he since taken up more responsibilities as veteran Cesc Fabregas has disappointed since signing in January.</p><p>"I'm used to help players improve and Golovin needed that," said Jardim, the man behind the breakthrough of young talents such as Bernardo Silva and Kylian Mbappe.</p><p>"He's a very talented player but he had to be polished like a diamond.</p><p>"He has improved a lot, notably concentration wise. With him you have to take it step by step."</p><p>Golovin's team mates were also expecting the Russian international, who took part in his national team's run to the World Cup quarter-finals last year, to bloom.</p><p>"It's a real treat to play with him, he's a super player," said French international striker Wissam Ben Yedder, who scored the third goal on Tuesday after he collected a brilliant through ball from Golovin.</p><p>Monaco, who have six points from seven games, will be relying on Golovin again to deliver against Brest at home on Saturday.</p><p>"There's nothing surprising about 'Golo', he's a super talented player but we're expecting him at that level again next weekend," said keeper Benjamin Lecomte. ($1 = 0.9088 euros) (Reporting by Julien Pretot; Editing by Christian Radnedge)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>