<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="03b357b8-e1b3-b2e4-bbcf-1e267ae60584" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Chip Alexander</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-HKN-SENATORS-HURRICANES:RA — sports (400 words)</title><summary>RALEIGH, N.C. — Tom Dundon was asked Tuesday if there have been any disappointments in his first few weeks as the Carolina Hurricanes’ new majority owner.“Where we are in the standings is disappointing,” he said.The standings looked better for...</summary><sourceId>19b475cf-e924-332b-32b0-08ec220f9f15</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K0591%knihr%r%BC-HKN-SENATORS-HURRICANES:RA — sports (400 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Hurricanes begin homestand with 2-1 win over Senators</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTOS)</p><byline xmlns="">By Chip Alexander</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">RALEIGH, N.C. — Tom Dundon was asked Tuesday if there have been any disappointments in his first few weeks as the Carolina Hurricanes’ new majority owner.</p><p xmlns="">“Where we are in the standings is disappointing,” he said.</p><p xmlns="">The standings looked better for the Canes after Tuesday’s game, after a 2-1 win over the Ottawa Senators at PNC Arena.</p><p xmlns="">Victor Rask’s power-play goal at 11:32 of the third period gave the Canes a 2-1 lead, Rask scoring from the left wing.</p><p xmlns="">The Canes (23-19-8) tied it at 1 earlier in the period as winger Sebastian Aho, back in the lineup after missing four games with a concussion and lower-body injury, scored on a blast from the left wing.</p><p xmlns="">That left it up to goalie Cam Ward to finish it up and the veteran earned his 14th win of the season.</p><p xmlns="">The Hurricanes were four points out of wild-card playoff position in the Eastern Conference standings before Tuesday’s game. They were facing a team that had lost five straight games, scoring just seven goals.</p><p xmlns="">“We’ve got a real good schedule that sets up well,” Canes coach Bill Peters said after Tuesday’s morning skate.</p><p xmlns="">It has been a long, frustrating season for the Sens, filled with injuries and more downs than ups. In the five-game skid they had been outscored 17-7.</p><p xmlns="">For nearly 40 minutes Tuesday, neither team could score. It was a grind of a game, with Ward and Sens goalie Craig Anderson matching saves.</p><p xmlns="">Jean-Gabriel Pageau finally broke through for the Sens with 1:12 left in the second, winging a shot from the left wing that may have grazed Canes defenseman Jaccob Slavin in front of Ward.</p><p xmlns="">Jeff Skinner was active offensively for the Canes, with six shots through two periods. Had Anderson not denied Rask at the doorstep in the final seconds of the second, it would have been a 1-1 game.</p><p xmlns="">Aho’s goal early in the third, his 17th of the season, tied it at 1 — a blast from the left circle that Anderson couldn’t track.</p><p xmlns="">Aho was injured Jan. 14 against the Calgary Flames, taking a big hit from defenseman Mark Giordano. He began Tuesday’s game on a line with Jordan Staal and Elias Lindholm before Peters made a change, putting Teravainen back with Staal and Aho — the “TSA” line that has been productive this season.</p><p xmlns="">The Canes’ last home win was Dec. 29 against the Pittsburgh Penguins, losing four in a row at PNC Arena before Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTOS (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>