<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b3836f8c-81dc-f4dd-fd72-d10849d279c5" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Ron Gallagher, Camila Molina And Abbie Bennett</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-NC-GIRL-MISSING-1ST-LEDE:RA — national (450 words)</title><summary>JACKSONVILLE, N.C. — The boyfriend of Mariah Woods’ mother was charged Wednesday with murder and felony child abuse in the 3-year-old’s death, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said.Adolphus Earl Kimrey II, 32, reported Mariah missing on Nov....</summary><sourceId>f9d14ebb-1b69-fc92-c928-23a035473813</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K2833%knihr%r%BC-NC-GIRL-MISSING-1ST-LEDE:RA — national (450 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Mom’s boyfriend charged with murder of 3-year-old Mariah Woods</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">WRITETHRU (EDITORS: Updates with changes throughout.) (PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Ron Gallagher, Camila Molina and Abbie Bennett</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE, N.C. — The boyfriend of Mariah Woods’ mother was charged Wednesday with murder and felony child abuse in the 3-year-old’s death, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said.</p><p xmlns="">Adolphus Earl Kimrey II, 32, reported Mariah missing on Nov. 27. A dive team found Mariah’s body Dec. 2 in a creek in Pender County.</p><p xmlns="">Kimrey was charged that day with obstruction of justice, concealing a death, possession of stolen goods, second-degree burglary and larceny after breaking or entering, and he has been in custody since then as the investigation continued.</p><p xmlns="">On Wednesday, Kimrey was charged with first-degree murder and felony child abuse resulting in serious bodily injury or death.</p><p xmlns="">He appeared in Onslow County District Court Wednesday afternoon to hear the new charges.</p><p xmlns="">An autopsy at East Carolina University determined Monday that chloroform toxicity caused Mariah’s death, the sheriff’s office said in a Facebook post.</p><p xmlns="">The sheriff’s office also said, in announcing the murder charge, that the case is not closed.</p><p xmlns="">The investigation “will continue until all leads and information is (sic) thoroughly evaluated,” the office said.</p><p xmlns="">A dive team recovered Mariah’s body under Holly Shelter Creek bridge on Dec. 2, almost a week after she was reported missing.</p><p xmlns="">Kimrey lived with Mariah’s mother, Kristy Woods, in Jacksonville, according to an Amber Alert.</p><p xmlns="">Mariah and her brothers were put to bed by Kristy Woods on Nov. 28, the evening before Kimrey reported Mariah missing, according to the sheriff’s office.</p><p xmlns="">Kimrey told investigators that while Kristy Woods was asleep, Mariah had gotten up but he had sent her back to bed. He also told investigators he left the house for a short period of time and left the door unlocked.</p><p xmlns="">Kimrey was arrested Dec. 1 and has been held on a bond set at $1.01 million.</p><p xmlns="">State arrest records show that Kimrey had previously been charged with larceny, assault, and drunk and disorderly conduct.</p><p xmlns="">Alex Woods, Mariah’s biological father, alleged in Child Protective Services documents that Kimrey sexually abused Mariah and physically abused the two brothers, according to photos of the documents he provided to The Jacksonville Daily News.</p><p xmlns="">The documents outlined why he was seeking custody of his two biological sons. Alex Woods alleged that Kimrey hit the boys with a belt — one of them in the face, causing a nosebleed.</p><p xmlns="">One of the boys said that their mother, Kristy Woods, knew Kimrey was sexually abusing Mariah, according to the documents.</p><p xmlns="">Kristy Woods and Kimrey have a history with the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office, including: Kimrey’s arrest in 2012; an assault of a juvenile at the home in 2016; property damage at the home in 2016; and communicated threats, neighborhood disputes and a “suspicious incident” involving Kimrey two days after Mariah was reported missing, according to county records.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194): Kimrey</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002458,t000027866,t000149877,t000027879</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>