<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d30fd5fb-14af-4ee2-bdf3-609b07e10d45" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0469</summary><sourceId>19794100-bc1c-43a8-3a89-68e4d3d5e502</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5668%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0469</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 30</hl2><p xmlns="">1926 — The major league rules committee mandates that pitchers must have access to a rosin bag.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — UCLA starts its 88-game winning streak with a 74-61 win over UC Santa Barbara.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — John Riggins rushes for a Super Bowl-record 166 yards on 38 carries to spark the Washington Redskins to a comeback 27-17 victory over the Miami Dolphins. For Riggins, the game's MVP, it's his fourth consecutive 100-yard rushing game during the playoffs, also a record.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Jockey Mike Smith wins six races in one day at Aqueduct for the second time in the month. His first six-winner day at Aqueduct was on Jan. 13.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Monica Seles beats Steffi Graf 4-6, 6-3, 6-2 to capture her third straight Australian Open.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — The Dallas Cowboys, behind MVP Emmitt Smith and safety James Washington, beat Buffalo 30-13 for their second straight NFL title while giving the Bills four straight Super Bowl losses.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Magic Johnson finishes with 19 points, 10 assists and eight rebounds in the Los Angeles Lakers' 128-118 victory over Golden State. It is Johnson's first regular-season game back from a 4 1/2-season retirement.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Martina Hingis wins her fifth Grand Slam title and third straight Australian Open with a 6-2, 6-3 victory over France's Amelie Mauresmo.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Daron Rahlves wins the super giant slalom, the first American to capture the event at the world championships.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Teemu Selanne scores two goals for his 1,000th career point in Anaheim's 4-3 overtime victory against Los Angeles.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Serena Williams ends Justine Henin's hopes of a Grand Slam title in her return from retirement with a 6-4, 3-6, 6-2 victory in the Australian Open final.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — MVP DeAngelo Hall has one of his team's five interceptions and returns a fumble 34 yards for a touchdown to help the NFC match a Pro Bowl scoring record in a 55-41 victory over the AFC. AFC quarterbacks Philip Rivers, Peyton Manning and Matt Cassel each throw first-half interceptions to help the NFC blow open a 42-0 lead.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Loui Eriksson's second goal, an empty-netter at 18:49 of the third period, helps seal an 11-10 victory for Team Lidstrom against Team Staal in the NHL All-Star Game.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — The Phoenix Open continues without Tiger Woods and Phil Mickelson. The biggest shock is Woods, who bogeys on his last hole for an 82, the worst score in his two decades as a pro. Mickelson shoots 76 and misses the cut by two shots.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Angelique Kerber upsets Serena Williams 6-4, 3-6, 6-4 to win the Australian Open title, ending the six-time champion's unbeaten streak in finals at Melbourne Park.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>