<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d2a51789-e0c7-45fb-afde-5a5cbc37b27d" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2J9:441406267</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2J9:441406267</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T114753Z_441406267_L3N26G2J9_RTRMADT_0_MYONGSHIN-ELECTRIC-CHINA-UPDATE-2-PIX.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UPDATE 2-S.Korea's Myongshin to build EVs for Chinese brand at ex-GM plant</title><summary>MYONGSHIN-ELECTRIC/CHINA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-S.Korea's Myongshin to build EVs for Chinese brand at ex-GM plant</summary><xmlText><p>UPDATE 2-S.Korea's Myongshin to build EVs for Chinese brand at ex-GM plant</p><p>(Adds Byton statement)</p><p>SEOUL, Sept 25 (Reuters) - South Korea's Myongshin has agreed to build more than 50,000 electric vehicles a year for Chinese venture Future Mobility Corp (FMC) at a closed plant it bought from General Motors.</p><p>A parts supplier to Hyundai Motor and Tesla Inc , Myongshin signed a deal on Wednesday to build the electric vehicles for FMC's Byton brand beginning in 2021, the government of Jeonbuk province said in a statement.</p><p>A Byton representative confirmed the company had signed a deal with Myongshin which would involve sales, production and investment.</p><p>The deal comes as made-in-China vehicles exported to the United States are currently subject to tariffs. Sales of cars made in South Korea can avoid those tariffs.</p><p>Myongshin bought a factory from GM's local unit for 113 billion won ($94 million) in June after the U.S. carmaker closed one of its four South Korean plants last year.</p><p>Myongshin will produce Byton's M-Byte electric SUV in the factory in the southwestern city of Gunsan, the Jeonbuk provincial government said.</p><p>The cars will be sold in South Korea and overseas, Park Ho-seok, vice president of Myongshin, told Reuters.</p><p>The plant could allow FMC to take advantage of South Korea’s free trade deal with the United States and Europe, as well as the country's electric car supply chain.</p><p>Former BMW and Nissan Motor executives co-founded Chinese electric-car venture FMC, which in September 2017 named its brand "Byton".</p><p>FMC, the parent company, plans to launch the vehicles in the United States and Europe soon after starting sales in China in 2019.</p><p>($1 = 1,199.3900 won) (Reporting by Heekyong Yang and Hyunjoo Jin; Additional reporting by Yilei Sun in Beijing; editing by Ju-min Park and Jason Neely)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>