<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d130ec74-0f15-b290-6e1d-6686447125e2" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Dennis Lin</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER:SD — sports (350 words)</title><summary>Padres Executive Chairman Ron Fowler indicated Tuesday the team is not planning significant changes to its offer to free-agent first baseman Eric Hosmer. The Union-Tribune reported earlier this month that the Padres had presented agent Scott...</summary><sourceId>cf554ddb-d4ce-6395-3958-2d9a7c342085</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K6363%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER:SD — sports (350 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres owner on Eric Hosmer offer: ‘We like it. I don’t know if Mr. Boras likes it.’</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Dennis Lin</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Padres Executive Chairman Ron Fowler indicated Tuesday the team is not planning significant changes to its offer to free-agent first baseman Eric Hosmer. The Union-Tribune reported earlier this month that the Padres had presented agent Scott Boras with a seven-year deal worth less than $140 million, and the club apparently has not budged from that position.</p><p xmlns="">“I think we were pretty creative in the way we put a contract proposal together,” Fowler said in an interview on The Mighty 1090. “We like it. I don’t know if Mr. Boras likes it, but that’s probably another story.”</p><p xmlns="">Boras began the winter seeking an eight-year contract in the neighborhood of $200 million, according to industry sources. But the free-agent market has been the most lethargic in recent memory, and Hosmer has not attracted a long list of suitors. The Kansas City Royals, who would like to retain their franchise first baseman, have been the Padres’ main competition.</p><p xmlns="">The fit for either club has been a source of curiosity. Both small-market franchises are rebuilding and have never committed to a nine-figure contract.</p><p xmlns="">Hosmer does represent a younger alternative to other free agents. The Padres and Royals believe the 28-year-old could remain in his prime when postseason baseball returns to their respective ballparks.</p><p xmlns="">Fowler said the front office broached the idea of pursuing Hosmer roughly six months ago.</p><p xmlns="">“They like him, they like his makeup, they like his leadership in the clubhouse, and obviously they like him as an athlete,” Fowler said. “We met with him, and he’s a very impressive individual.”</p><p xmlns="">How much the Padres are willing to pay for Hosmer’s qualifications — both tangible and otherwise — has been the subject of extensive debate. In Tuesday’s interview, it was suggested to Fowler that a six-year deal would be preferable.</p><p xmlns="">“I think you’re taking my side of the discussions I’ve had with Andy (Green) and A.J. (Preller) and (Josh Stein),” Fowler said, referencing his manager and front office.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>