<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9358b3dc-4eb4-4f45-a38b-a447c0ee775f" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDVW76TTDS0:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDVW76TTDS0:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDVW76TTDS000000_DNMLENf-20190925110990.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Tariff Tide Rolls in Alabama Toward Airbus, Mercedes</title><authors>Shawn Donnan</authors><summary>PYDVW76TTDS0(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Terms of Trade newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Economics on Twitter for more.Trade wars are fought between nations. But the damage is often about regions and politics. Which is exactly how things are developing when it comes to President Donald Trump’s forthcoming escalation with the European Union.In the coming days the World Trade Organization is expected to give the U.S. the  final go-ahead to...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Terms of Trade newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Economics on Twitter for more.</p><p>Trade wars are fought between nations. But the damage is often about regions and politics. Which is exactly how things are developing when it comes to President Donald Trump’s forthcoming escalation with the European Union.In the coming days the World Trade Organization is expected to give the U.S. the  final go-ahead to apply punitive tariffs on $5 billion to $7 billion in imports from the EU, bringing to an end one leg of a nearly 15-year fight over aircraft subsidies.</p><p>The move will hurt the EU. But it could also be bad news for the good  people of Alabama.High on the list of imports to be targeted are Airbus fuselages and landing gear made in Europe that are shipped in and turned into A320 aircraft for the U.S. market in Mobile, Alabama. Depending on how high they are, the tariffs could threaten the economics of the Mobile operation, which Airbus is ironically in the process of expanding.It’s not just planes in the firing line, of course. Trump has threatened to hit  European carmakers with tariffs on imported cars and parts and faces a self-imposed deadline in November over whether to go ahead with those. That too could have repercussions across Alabama. Mercedes has had a plant near Tuscaloosa since the 1990s. The SUVs assembled there feature engines imported from Germany.Alabama doesn’t have to look far to see how other states have been hit by the  trade wars. Bourbon distillers in nearby Kentucky, home of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, have been weathering the storm since the EU responded to Trump’s steel tariffs by targeting the whiskey for retaliatory duties.That has actually turned Kentucky into a curious EU ally in the diplomatic fight against tariffs.At a recent reception in Washington, the EU’s new ambassador to the U.S., Stavros Lambrinidis, hosted the mayor of Louisville, distillers and other  Kentucky businesses as well as the state’s poet laureate at a good-natured, anti-tariff party fueled by Old Fashioneds and other bourbon cocktails.Guests left with specially branded, wax-sealed bottles of “Kentucky&amp;EU” bourbon and glasses with the words “Raise a glass — not tariffs!” etched on them. Among the swag was a wooden baton with a simple cocktail recipe attached. It called for ice, a shot of either bourbon, scotch, cognac or Irish whiskey and one final important step: “Muddle tariffs.”</p><p>Charting the Trade War</p><p>Nigeria and Benin are embroiled in a  trade dispute two months after signing an agreement to free up the movement of goods and services in Africa. Nigeria ordered the partial closing of its boundary with Benin last month to curb smuggling of rice and other commodities. The blockade has had a ripple effect across West Africa, with factories and traders struggling to import key raw materials and having to use alternative routes for their exports.</p><p>Today’s Must Reads</p><p>Economic Analysis</p><p>Coming Up</p><p>Like Terms of Trade?</p><p>Don’t keep it to yourself. Colleagues and friends can sign up here. We also publish Balance of Power, a daily briefing on the latest in global politics.</p><p>For even more: Subscribe to Bloomberg All Access for full global news coverage and two in-depth daily newsletters, The Bloomberg Open and The Bloomberg Close.</p><p>How are we doing? We want to hear what you think about this newsletter. Let our trade tsar know.</p><p>To contact the author of this story: Shawn Donnan in Washington at sdonnan@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editor responsible for this story: Brendan Murray at brmurray@bloomberg.net, Zoe SchneeweissRichard Bravo</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>