<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TEN-RESULTS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8e09ea74-828e-4b46-afce-21f622898738" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</title><summary>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</summary><sourceId>c7f7e115-3f05-4f12-f12a-c3cdd17f902d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6852%-----%r%BC-TEN--Australian Open Results;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">MELBOURNE (AP) — Results Wednesday from the Australian Open at Melbourne Park (seedings in parentheses):</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Pablo Carreno-Busta (10), Spain, def. Gilles Simon, France, 6-2, 3-0.</p><p xmlns="">Nikoloz Basilashvili, Georgia, def. Ruben Bemelmans, Belgium, 7-5, 6-1, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Andreas Seppi, Italy, def. Yoshihito Nishioka, Japan, 6-1, 6-3, 6-4.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Luksika Kumkhum, Thailand, def. Belinda Bencic, Switzerland, 6-1, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Denisa Allertova, Czech Republic, def. Shuai Zhang, China, 6-4, 7-6 (5).</p><p xmlns="">Marta Kostyuk, Ukraine, def. Olivia Rogowska, Australia, 6-3, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Elina Svitolina (4), Ukraine, def. Katerina Siniakova, Czech Republic, 4-6, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Katerina Bondarenko, Ukraine, def. Anastasia Pavlyuchenkova (15), Russia, 6-2, 6-3.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Fabio Fognini, Italy and Marcel Granollers, Spain, def. Alex Bolt, Australia and Bradley Mousley, Australia, 6-7 (6), 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Feliciano Lopez, Spain and Marc Lopez (9), Spain, def. Nenad Zimonjic, Serbia and Florin Mergea, Romania, 6-2, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Artem Sitak, New Zealand and Wesley Koolhof, Netherlands, def. Frederic Niemeyer, Canada and Peter Gojowczyk, Germany, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Oliver Marach, Austria and Mate Pavic (7), Croatia, def. Victor Estrella Burgos, Dominican Republic and Federico Delbonis, Argentina, 6-1, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Robert Farah, Colombia and Juan Sebastian Cabal (11), Colombia, def. Andrew Whittington, Australia and Marc Polmans, Australia, 7-6 (5), 7-6 (4).</p><p xmlns="">Sam Querrey, United States and Steve Johnson, United States, def. Fernando Verdasco, Spain and Ivan Dodig (14), Croatia, 6-4, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Robert Lindstedt, Sweden and Franko Skugor, Croatia, def. Roman Jebavy, Czech Republic and Jiri Vesely, Czech Republic, 7-5, 7-5.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Varvara Lepchenko, United States and Oksana Kalashnikova, Georgia, def. Qiang Wang, China and Yafan Wang, China, 6-4, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Michaella Krajicek, Netherlands and Alla Kudryavtseva, Russia, def. Pauline Parmentier, France and Tatjana Maria, Germany, 6-4, 1-6, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Katarina Srebotnik, Slovenia and Hao-Ching Chan (14), Taiwan, def. Coco Vandeweghe, United States and Laura Robson, Britain, 7-6 (3), 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Viktorija Golubic, Switzerland and Nina Stojanovic, Serbia, def. Andreja Klepac, Slovenia and Maria Jose Martinez Sanchez (9), Spain, 6-3, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Barbora Strycova, Czech Republic and Lucie Safarova (4), Czech Republic, def. Anna Smith, Britain and Naomi Broady, Britain, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Jessica Moore, Australia and Ellen Perez, Australia, def. Darija Jurak, Croatia and Nao Hibino, Japan, 6-4, 6-4.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TEN-RESULTS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>