<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0a71bdc2-d12b-4f55-8930-750edbe31895" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Ivan Moreno</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US-TEC--Smart Floor Sensors</title><summary>MILWAUKEE (AP) — Floor sensors that track people's movements are providing insight into consumer habits for stores looking to gain ground on e-commerce giants like Amazon.Brick-and-mortar stores have lagged behind online retailers on data...</summary><sourceId>375f7b42-bebd-4f95-f95b-eab64988bb11</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL9270%limit%r%BC-US-TEC--Smart Floor Sensors;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Intel underfoot: Floor sensors rise as retail data source</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Will be updated. With AP Photos.</p><byline xmlns="">By IVAN MORENO</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE (AP) — Floor sensors that track people's movements are providing insight into consumer habits for stores looking to gain ground on e-commerce giants like Amazon.</p><p xmlns="">Brick-and-mortar stores have lagged behind online retailers on data collection because computer clicks are more easily analyzed than customers in physical spaces. But Milwaukee-based startup Scanalytics is helping businesses explore ways to track customers with paper-thin sensors tucked under existing flooring or utility mats.</p><p xmlns="">The sensors help stores know where customers linger the longest, what products are popular and precisely when to schedule staff to handle heavy traffic.</p><p xmlns="">The sensors are just one of many tracking options that have become available to retailers in recent years. Video cameras with artificial intelligence can analyze body motions to identify products that attract customers and given them customized offers.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>