<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b10976fe-6c94-4e92-bb96-918a232644f8" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDM1DSYF01T:9</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDM1DSYF01T:9</followId><sourceFileName>PYDM1DSYF01T00000_DNMLENf-20190925070951.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Stocks Drop in Europe and Asia as Dollar Advances: Markets Wrap</title><authors>Adam Haigh and Todd White</authors><summary>PYDM1DSYF01T(Bloomberg) -- Stocks dropped in Europe and Asia while U.S. index futures steadied as investors weighed the deepening political gridlock in Washington against prospects for reduced trade tension between America and China. The dollar advanced.Energy and technology shares led the Stoxx Europe 600 index lower. Equity benchmarks retreated across Asia hours after the biggest decline for the S&amp;P 500 Index in a month in the wake of an announcement the U.S. House of Representatives is...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Stocks dropped in Europe and Asia while U.S. index futures steadied as investors weighed the deepening political gridlock in Washington against prospects for reduced trade tension between America and China. The dollar advanced.</p><p>Energy and technology shares led the Stoxx Europe 600 index lower. Equity benchmarks retreated across Asia hours after the biggest decline for the S&amp;P 500 Index in a month in the wake of an announcement the U.S. House of Representatives is opening a formal impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump. </p><p>U.S. futures steadied on Wednesday, suggesting limited market fallout for now. The contracts got further support after Bloomberg reported that China is preparing to buy more American pork. The greenback headed toward its biggest advance in a week, the yen fell, and Treasuries also stabilized. While the new impeachment push threatens to stymie legislative progress in Washington, the Republican party’s majority in the Senate could limit the chances of any attempt by Democrats to oust the president.</p><p>Markets have seemed to gyrate with every twist and turn of the protectionist battle between the two largest economies, with this year’s epic bond rally recovering from a pullback and U.S. stocks lingering within sight of a record high. The sudden escalation of political risk in Washington comes as economic signals deteriorate globally, and adds a fresh complication for investors trying to decide whether central banks will be able to shore up growth.</p><p>Elsewhere, West Texas oil futures extended losses as industry data indicated U.S. crude inventories expanded. The pound retraced some of its Tuesday gain as U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson returned to the country after Britain’s Supreme Court ruled that he’d broken the law by suspending Parliament.</p><p>In Japan, five-year government bond yields fell to a record low following comments from central bank Governor Haruhiko Kuroda that added to speculation of an interest-rate cut in October.</p><p>These are some key events coming up this week:</p><p>Here are the main moves in markets:</p><p>Stocks</p><p>Currencies</p><p>Bonds</p><p>Commodities</p><p>--With assistance from Sarah Ponczek and Vildana Hajric.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Adam Haigh in Sydney at ahaigh1@bloomberg.net;Todd White in Madrid at twhite2@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editor responsible for this story: Samuel Potter at spotter33@bloomberg.net</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>