<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TEN-RESULTS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="801e8b32-6df4-473d-ad8f-5dc4f52b48d4" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</title><summary>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</summary><sourceId>bcbf16da-b992-4c06-c06b-5f5f9fe57c3f</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9779%-----%r%BC-TEN--Australian Open Results;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">MELBOURNE (AP) — Results Friday from the Australian Open at Melbourne Park (seedings in parentheses):</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Third Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Pablo Carreno-Busta (10), Spain, def. Gilles Muller, Luxembourg, 7-6 (4), 4-6, 7-5, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Grigor Dimitrov (3), Bulgaria, def. Andrey Rublev (30), Russia, 6-3, 4-6, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Kyle Edmund, Britain, def. Nikoloz Basilashvili, Georgia, 7-6 (0), 3-6, 4-6, 6-0, 7-5.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Third Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Petra Martic, Croatia, def. Luksika Kumkhum, Thailand, 6-3, 3-6, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Elise Mertens, Belgium, def. Alize Cornet, France, 7-5, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Denisa Allertova, Czech Republic, def. Magda Linette, Poland, 6-1, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Elina Svitolina (4), Ukraine, def. Marta Kostyuk, Ukraine, 6-2, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Magdalena Rybarikova (19), Slovakia, def. Katerina Bondarenko, Ukraine, 7-5, 3-6, 6-1.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Rajeev Ram, United States and Divij Sharan (16), India, def. Fabio Fognini, Italy and Marcel Granollers, Spain, 4-6, 7-6 (4), 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Jan-Lennard Struff, Germany and Ben Mclachlan, Japan, def. Feliciano Lopez, Spain and Marc Lopez (9), Spain, 4-6, 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Edouard Roger-Vasselin, France and Rohan Bopanna (10), India, def. Leonardo Mayer, Argentina and Joao Sousa, Portugal, 6-2, 7-6 (3).</p><p xmlns="">Oliver Marach, Austria and Mate Pavic (7), Croatia, def. Artem Sitak, New Zealand and Wesley Koolhof, Netherlands, 6-7 (5), 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Robert Farah, Colombia and Juan Sebastian Cabal (11), Colombia, def. Alexander Peya, Austria and Nikola Mektic, Croatia, 7-6 (5), 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Pablo Andujar, Spain and Albert Ramos-Vinolas, Spain, def. Sam Querrey, United States and Steve Johnson, United States, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Bob Bryan, United States and Mike Bryan (6), United States, def. Max Mirnyi, Belarus and Philipp Oswald, Austria, 6-7 (5), 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Radu Albot, Moldova and Hyeon Chung, Republic of Korea, def. Henri Kontinen, Finland and John Peers (2), Australia, 6-4, 7-6 (5).</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Yung-Jan Chan, Taiwan and Andrea Sestini Hlavackova (1), Czech Republic, def. Varvara Lepchenko, United States and Oksana Kalashnikova, Georgia, 6-0, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Katarina Srebotnik, Slovenia and Hao-Ching Chan (14), Taiwan, def. Michaella Krajicek, Netherlands and Alla Kudryavtseva, Russia, 4-6, 6-3, 7-6 (2).</p><p xmlns="">Barbora Strycova, Czech Republic and Lucie Safarova (4), Czech Republic, def. Olga Savchuk, Ukraine and Raluca-Ioana Olaru, Romania, 6-2, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Anna-Lena Groenefeld, Germany and Raquel Atawo (12), United States, def. Miyu Kato, Japan and Eri Hozumi, Japan, 6-1, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Shuai Peng, China and Su-Wei Hsieh (8), Taiwan, def. Lidziya Marozava, Belarus and Lesley Kerkhove, Netherlands, 6-4, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Monica Niculescu, Romania and Irina Begu (10), Romania, def. Jessica Moore, Australia and Ellen Perez, Australia, 3-6, 6-3, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Yi-Fan Xu, China and Gabriela Dabrowski (6), Canada, def. Anastasija Sevastova, Latvia and Ekaterina Alexandrova, Russia, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Elena Vesnina, Russia and Ekaterina Makarova, Russia, def. Irina Khromacheva, Russia and Dalila Jakupovic, Slovenia, 6-2, 6-3.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Mixed Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Marcelo Demoliner, Brazil and Maria Jose Martinez Sanchez, Spain, def. Nicholas Monroe, United States and Nicole Melichar, United States, 6-2, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Franko Skugor, Croatia and Vania King, United States, def. John-Patrick Smith, Australia and Arina Rodionova, Australia, 4-6, 7-5, 10-7.</p><p xmlns="">Sam Groth, Australia and Samantha Stosur, Australia, def. Matt Reid, Australia and Priscilla Hon, Australia, 6-3, 7-6 (3).</p><p xmlns="">Matwe Middelkoop, Netherlands and Johanna Larsson, Sweden, def. Santiago Gonzalez, Mexico and Alicja Rosolska, Poland, 6-2, 7-5.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TEN-RESULTS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>