<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="827852f8-44d0-4056-9394-de34c61a394e" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1VU:1152145626</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1VU:1152145626</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T072301Z_1152145626_L3N26G1VU_RTRMADT_0_EUROPE-STOCKS-URGENT.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>European shares stumble as techs drop; political uncertainty in Washington weighs</title><summary>EUROPE-STOCKS/ (URGENT):European shares stumble as techs drop; political uncertainty in Washington weighs </summary><xmlText><p>European shares stumble as techs drop; political uncertainty in Washington weighs</p><p>(For a live blog on European stocks, type LIVE/ in an Eikon news window)</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - European shares fell broadly on Wednesday, with technology stocks leading losses, while an impeachment inquiry into U.S. President Donald Trump raised concerns of political uncertainty in the world's largest economy.</p><p>The European technology sector slid 1.2%, the most among the major sub-sectors, while the pan-European STOXX 600 index fell 0.6%.</p><p>The move by Democrats in the U.S. House of Representatives only piled on worries of a global economic downturn and the impact of a prolonged trade war between the United States and China.</p><p>Adding pressure on stocks was a harsher tone by Trump on U.S.-China trade talks, with export-reliant Germany falling 0.5%. Trump said he would not accept a "bad deal" in negotiations with Beijing at the United Nations General Assembly on Tuesday. Germany's Pfeiffer Vacuum plunged 13.6%, after it warned of delays to orders, cut its full0-year sales and EBIT margin forecasts.</p><p>In a bright spot, British supermarket group Sainsbury's gained 1% following news of a new plan to cut costs, speed up debt reduction and shake up its store estate and financial services division. (Reporting by Shreyashi Sanyal in Bengaluru; Editing by Bernard Orr)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>