<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="fc205baa-57ee-e86b-97f7-3e93936f1e63" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Dennis Lin</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-HOFFMAN-STATUE:SD — sports (350 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Cooperstown won’t be the only place where Trevor Hoffman soon finds himself in the company of Tony Gwynn.Sometime around July 29, when Hoffman officially joins “Mr. Padre” in the Hall of Fame, the Padres intend to unveil a bronze...</summary><sourceId>a77e4d94-843f-6046-0468-5aad48502212</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3692%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-HOFFMAN-STATUE:SD — sports (350 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres to unveil Trevor Hoffman statue at Petco Park this summer</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Dennis Lin</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Cooperstown won’t be the only place where Trevor Hoffman soon finds himself in the company of Tony Gwynn.</p><p xmlns="">Sometime around July 29, when Hoffman officially joins “Mr. Padre” in the Hall of Fame, the Padres intend to unveil a bronze statue of their former closer at Petco Park. Hoffman was elected Wednesday as a member of the 2018 class, and this summer’s statue reveal will continue an observance of his forthcoming induction.</p><p xmlns="">The exact location remains to be announced, but the National League’s all-time saves leader will be immortalized not far from the pre-existing bronze statue of Gwynn beyond the outfield walls.</p><p xmlns="">“It will be consistent in character with the Tony Gwynn statue,” Padres Executive Chairman Ron Fowler told the Union-Tribune. “Both those guys are high-water marks for Padres as players.”</p><p xmlns="">In 2007, eight days before his own induction, Gwynn applauded as a 91/2-foot behemoth, cast in his likeness, debuted at Petco Park. More than a decade later, the statue stands as a San Diego landmark and homage to the late outfielder.</p><p xmlns="">William Behrends, who depicted Gwynn in mid-swing, has lent his craftsmanship again. The sculptor will capture Hoffman mid-windup, complete with the right-hander’s familiar high leg kick.</p><p xmlns="">During a news conference Thursday in New York City, Hoffman saluted his former teammate of 81/2 seasons, a teammate he will follow into Cooperstown six months from now.</p><p xmlns="">“I know I was a pitcher, but to watch (Gwynn) command a city, command a locker room, I was just a little brother watching,” Hoffman said. “So to ultimately have the opportunity, I’m pinching myself. It’s something that I don’t think has even really set in.”</p><p xmlns="">As part of an expanded slate of promotions, the Padres have planned a Hoffman replica statue giveaway for their Aug. 19 home game against Arizona.</p><p xmlns="">“Obviously, he and Tony have achieved iconic status while playing for the Padres in San Diego,” Fowler said. “And, more importantly, they were great human beings.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000424479,t000007391,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>