<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="25d53cbd-47f8-41fb-b524-c18c63736d26" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0318</summary><sourceId>27417ce5-decc-414b-14b8-f54f07963378</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6416%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0318</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Released OT Storm Norton from the practice squad. Signed TE Nick Truesdell to the practice squad.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CFL — Suspended Saskatchewan OL Bruce Campbell two games for testing positive for a banned substance.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled F Michael Amadio and D Paul LaDue from Ontario (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Recalled G Louis Domingue from Syracuse (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Hershey D Colby Williams three games and Manitoba F Mike Sgarbossa two games.</p><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Recalled F Jeff Kubiak from Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LEHIGH VALLEY PHANTOMS — Recalled F Chris McCarthy on loan from Reading (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">LA GALAXY — Signed D Emrah Klimenta.</p><p xmlns="">REAL SALT LAKE — Re-signed M Kyle Beckerman.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE SC — Signed F Ropapa Mensah and Ds London Woodberry and Jordan Dunstan.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALABAMA A&amp;M — Named Connell Maynor football coach.</p><p xmlns="">CHATTANOOGA — Promoted senior associate athletics director Scott Altizer to deputy athletics director, senior associate athletics director/senior woman administrator Laura Herron to executive associate athletics director/senior woman administrator and associate athletics director of student support services Dr. Emily Blackman to senior associate athletics director. Named Lee Roberts associate athletics director for development, Beth Luehrs director of business affairs, Andrew Horton senior associate athletics director for external operations. Adjusted the title of Dr. Jay Blackman to senior associate athletics director for strategic communications.</p><p xmlns="">RUTGERS — Named John McNulty offensive coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>