<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b5b3cecc-a198-4b47-88d1-c936dbe621e3" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2FJ:555487489</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G2FJ:555487489</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T095220Z_555487489_L5N26G2FJ_RTRMADT_0_CROATIA-ECONOMY.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Croatia central bank expects 2020 growth slowdown on export fall</title><summary>CROATIA-ECONOMY/:Croatia central bank expects 2020 growth slowdown on export fall</summary><xmlText><p>Croatia central bank expects 2020 growth slowdown on export fall</p><p>ZAGREB, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Croatia's economy is expected to grow at between 2.5% and 3.0% in 2020, slightly below this year's level of around 3.0%, as external risks may hit the country's exports, a senior central bank official said on Wednesday.</p><p>"We have reasons for optimism amid solid growth prospects, low inflation and a positive current account balance. However, the external uncertainties are immense and a share of exports in growth structure is expected to fall," deputy central bank governor Sandra Svaljek told a business conference.</p><p>She said the main worries about exports came from economic slowdown in Croatia's key trading partners Italy and Germany.</p><p>She also said that the average annual inflation this year is seen at 0.7%, rising slightly to 1.1% in 2020.</p><p>"The biggest inflationary pressure comes from faster increase in labour costs in comparison with productivity growth," she said.</p><p>Croatia is expected to maintain a current and capital account surplus this year, but it is expected to fall to 3.1% of gross domestic product from 3.8% in 2018. In 2020 it is seen falling further to 2.2% of GDP.</p><p>"It is mostly due to an expected slowdown in exports," Svaljek said.</p><p>She said that the central bank would continue with its expansive monetary policy in 2020. The current liquidity surplus amounts to some 10% of GDP or more than 30 billion kuna ($4.46 billion). ($1 = 6.7291 kuna) (Reporting by Igor Ilic; Editing by Alexander Smith)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>