<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="52e57276-f466-40c1-b92d-ead024b45240" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDMUVT1UM0Y:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDMUVT1UM0Y:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDMUVT1UM0Y00000_DNMLENf-20190925080933.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Sainsbury’s to Cut Costs and Close Stores After Asda Deal’s Demise</title><authors>Ellen Milligan</authors><summary>PYDMUVT1UM0Y(Bloomberg) -- J Sainsbury Plc pledged to reduce costs and close stores as Chief Executive Officer Mike Coupe seeks to move on from a failed bid to take over rival grocer Asda.The U.K. supermarket operator plans to reduce expenditures by around 500 million pounds ($623 million) over the next five years as it integrates dozens of Argos home-goods outlets, acquired in 2016, into Sainsbury’s stores.The company also plans to close some supermarkets while opening more convenience...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- J Sainsbury Plc pledged to reduce costs and close stores as Chief Executive Officer Mike Coupe seeks to move on from a failed bid to take over rival grocer Asda.</p><p>The U.K. supermarket operator plans to reduce expenditures by around 500 million pounds ($623 million) over the next five years as it integrates dozens of Argos home-goods outlets, acquired in 2016, into Sainsbury’s stores.</p><p>The company also plans to close some supermarkets while opening more convenience stores. It said it will stop issuing mortgages, a business that’s grown tougher as the U.K. housing market suffers from Brexit.</p><p>The changes are the most sweeping since U.K. antitrust regulators blocked the company’s planned acquisition of Walmart Inc.’s Asda in April. Sainsbury’s had promised 1 billion pounds in price cuts and 10% reductions on a range of everyday items if the acquisition was successful.</p><p>The shares rose as much as 3% in early London trading, but they’re down 17% this year.</p><p>The company, which is holding an investor briefing on Wednesday, reported a 0.6% increase in grocery sales for the second quarter. It expects first-half underlying profit before tax to decline by around 50 million pounds because of unseasonal weather and the impact of cost savings but still sees full-year results in line with consensus views.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Ellen Milligan in London at emilligan11@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editor responsible for this story: Eric Pfanner at epfanner1@bloomberg.net</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>