<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e3781b82-21be-4ab7-829b-05f65b70e228" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV20</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV20,3575</summary><sourceId>0e69bbcf-725a-4bf0-bf09-762d85f1cff3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1473%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV20;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV20</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV20,3575</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">ADV20</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend editions Jan. 20-21</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 21</hl2><p xmlns="">1921 — Kenesaw Mountain Landis takes office as baseball's commissioner.</p><p xmlns="">1947 — Carl Hubbell, Frank Frisch, Mickey Cochrane, and Lefty Grove are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1953 — Dizzy Dean and Al Simmons are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame. The baseball writers pass over Joe DiMaggio in his first year of eligibility.</p><p xmlns="">1954 — For the first time in NBA All-Star history, an overtime period is needed. Boston's Bob Cousy scores 10 points in the overtime to give the East a 98-93 victory and Cousy the MVP honors.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Bob Pettit of St. Louis becomes the first member of the losing team to win the NBA All-Star MVP award, scoring 28 points and grabbing 26 rebounds, even though the East beats the West 130-118.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Roy Campanella and Stan Musial are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1979 — Terry Bradshaw throws four touchdown passes to lead the Pittsburgh Steelers to their third Super Bowl win, a 35-31 victory over the Dallas Cowboys. Bradshaw, the game's MVP, completes 17 of 30 passes for 318 yards.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — John McEnroe becomes the first player thrown out of the Australian Open. McEnroe's tantrum comes while leading Mike Pernfors 6-1, 4-6, 7-5, 2-4.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Karrie Webb becomes the second quickest winner in LPGA Tour history winning the HealthSouth Inaugural at Walt Disney World. Webb, in her second LPGA start, beat Jane Geddes and Martha Nause on the fourth hole of a playoff. Webb finished second in her first LPGA start a week earlier in the Chrysler-Plymouth Tournament of Champions.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Four-time Olympic champion Ole Einar Bjoerndalen wins his 49th career World Cup biathlon, breaking the record for career victories. Bjoerndalen edges fellow Norwegian Frode Andresen in the 10-kilometer sprint event to pass former cross country great Bjorn Daehlie at 48 career wins.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Lovie Smith becomes the first black head coach to make it to the Super Bowl when his Chicago Bears win the NFC championship. Tony Dungy joins him when his Indianapolis Colts take the AFC title.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — New Jersey Institute of Technology ends its 51-game losing streak, getting 26 points from Jheryl Wilson in a 61-51 victory over Bryant. NJIT had not won since it defeated Longwood on Feb. 19, 2007.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Los Angeles guard Kobe Bryant becomes the 15th player in NBA history to reach 25,000 career points and the youngest to hit the milestone. Bryant finishes with 31 points in the Lakers' 93-87 loss at Cleveland.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Notre Dame upsets No. 1 Syracuse 67-58 and hands the Orange their first loss after 20 straight victories. It's the eighth time Notre Dame has beaten a No. 1 team — that ties for fourth-most all-time.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Adam Hadwin shoots a 13-under 59 in the CareerBuilder Challenge for the ninth sub-60 round in PGA Tour history and the second in 10 days. The 29-year-old Canadian reaches 13 under with a 7-foot birdie putt on the par-4 17th and makes a 3-footer from just off the green for par on the 18th at La Quinta Country Club.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 22</hl2><p xmlns="">1920 — The New York Yankees announce they will be the first team to wear uniform numbers, according to the player's position in batting order.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Paul Pender beats Sugar Ray Robinson in a 15-round split decision to capture the world middleweight boxing title.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Bob Feller and Jackie Robinson are elected into the Baseball Hall of Fame. Robinson, who had the distinction of becoming the first black to play in the Major League, is also the first to enter the Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — The NBA awards expansion franchises to Milwaukee and Phoenix.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — George Foreman knocks out Joe Frazier in the second round in Kingston, Jamaica, to win the world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — Houston becomes the first NBA team not to score a point in overtime as the Portland Trail Blazers outscore the Rockets 17-0 for a 113-96 victory.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Mike Tyson knocks out Larry Holmes in the fourth round at Atlantic City to retain his world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — New York Islanders' Pierre Turgeon has four assists to help the Eastern Conference beat the Western Conference 9-8 in the NHL All-Star game.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — New York's Pat LaFontaine reaches the 1,000-point mark, scoring his 19th goal in the Rangers' 4-3 loss to Philadelphia.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Jockey Russell Baze passes Bill Shoemaker to take over second place on the all-time win list. Russell gets his 8,834th victory aboard Hollow Memoires in the seventh race at Golden Gate Fields.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — The Pittsburgh Steelers are the first team since the 1985 Patriots to win three postseason road games thanks to a 34-17 dismantling of the Denver Broncos in the AFC title game.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Kobe Bryant scores a staggering 81 points — the second-highest total in NBA history — and the Los Angeles Lakers beat the Toronto Raptors 122-104.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — The New England Patriots beat the stunned Ravens 23-20 in the AFC championship game after Baltimore's Billy Cundiff misses a 32-yard field goal attempt with 11 seconds remaining that would have tied the score.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Lawrence Tynes kicks a winning 31-yard field goal in sudden-death overtime and New York beat the San Francisco 49ers 20-17 in the NFC championship game.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Atlanta's Matt Ryan throws for 392 yards and four touchdowns and runs for another score, leading the Falcons to a 44-21 blowout of Green Bay in the NFC championship game.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — New England's Tom Brady passes for a Patriots playoff-record 384 yards, going 32 of 42 with three TD tosses to lead the Patriots to the Super Bowl with a 36-17 win over Pittsburgh.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Nathan Chen follows a record-setting short program with a near-flawless free skate featuring five quadruple jumps to become the youngest men's U.S. figure skating champion in more than five decades. The 17-year-old Chen, performing to "The Polovtsian Dances," became the first skater in the world to land five clean quads in competition.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 23</hl2><p xmlns="">1944 — The Detroit Red Wings defeat the New York Rangers 15-0 to set an NHL record for consecutive goals.</p><p xmlns="">1959 — In the NBA All-Star game in Detroit, St. Louis' Bob Pettit and Elgin Baylor of Minneapolis become the first co-winners of the MVP award as their West team wins 124-108.</p><p xmlns="">1975 — Ralph Kiner is elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame in his 15th and final year of eligibility.</p><p xmlns="">1979 — Willie Mays is named on 409 of 432 ballots and elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame in his first year of eligibility.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — George Gervin of San Antonio scores 55 points in a 144-130 victory over the Indiana Pacers.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Hana Mandlikova upsets Martina Navratilova 7-5, 7-6 to win the Australian Open.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Steffi Graf wins the Australian Open with a 6-1, 7-6 victory over Chris Evert.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Mike Gartner of the New York Rangers sets an NHL record when he reaches the 30-goal mark for the 14th consecutive season. Gartner, with three goals in the Rangers' 8-3 victory over Los Angeles, surpasses Phil Esposito, Bobby Hull and Wayne Gretzky.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Jennifer Rodriguez becomes the first American woman in nine years to win the World Sprint Speedskating Championship. Rodriguez sets a personal best in the 500 for the second straight day and had the fastest 1,000 meters in the women's field to claim the world sprint championship.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Baylor, which waited 39 years to get back into the Top 25, has to wait some more, enduring five overtimes to get their first win as a ranked team. Curtis Jerrells scores a career-high 36 points, including 11 in the fifth overtime to lead No. 25 Baylor to a 116-110 win over No. 18 Texas A&amp;M.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Francesca Schiavone wins the longest women's match in Grand Slam history — a 6-4, 1-6, 16-14 victory over Svetlana Kuznetsova that takes 4 hours, 44 minutes at the Australian Open.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Aaron Rodgers runs for a touchdown and makes a saving tackle, B.J. Raji returns an interception for a score and Sam Shields has two interceptions to lead the Green Bay Packers to a 21-14 win over the Chicago Bears in the NFC championship game. The Packers, with road wins in Philadelphia, Atlanta and Chicago, become the first NFC No. 6 seed to advance to the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Klay Thompson sets an NBA record for the most points in a quarter, a thrilling 37-point third period that powers the Golden State Warriors to a 126-101 victory over the Sacramento Kings.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 24</hl2><p xmlns="">1939 — Eddie Collins, Wee Willie Keeler and George Sisler are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1956 — Bob Pettit of the St. Louis Hawks captures the first of his NBA record four All-Star MVP awards. Pettit leads the West team with 20 points and 24 rebounds in a 108-94 win over the East.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Mike Bossy of the New York Islanders scores his 50th goal in the 50th game of the season in a 7-3 victory over the Quebec Nordiques.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Ray Wersching kicks a Super Bowl record-tying four field goals to help the San Francisco 49ers beat the Cincinnati Bengals 26-21.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — Mike Bossy of the New York Islanders scores his 1,000th career point with an assist in a 7-5 victory over the Toronto Maple Leafs.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Winston-Salem State basketball coach Clarence "Big House" Gaines wins his 800th career game, 79-70 over Livingstone.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — David Duval shoots a magic number — a round of 59 that matches the best score in PGA Tour history. Duval surges from seven strokes off the pace for a one-stroke victory over Steve Pate in the Bob Hope Chrysler Classic.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Mirai Nagasu pulls off one of the biggest upsets ever at the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. The 14-year-old — in her first competition as a senior — wins the short program with a spectacular performance. Her score of 70.23 is the second-highest ever by an American woman in a short program.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Kelly Kulick becomes the first woman to win a PBA Tour title, beating Chris Barnes in the final of the 45th Tournament of Champions. Kulick outscores Barnes 265-195 to take home the $40,000 first prize and a two-year PBA Tour exemption.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Peyton Manning throws three touchdown passes and the Indianapolis Colts rally from an 11-point, first-half deficit to beat the New York Jets 30-17 in the AFC championship game.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The New Orleans Saints make it to their first Super Bowl after battering Brett Favre and the Minnesota Vikings 31-28 in overtime on unheralded Garrett Hartley's 40-yard field goal.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Carmelo Anthony scores a career-high and franchise-record 62 points, most at the current Madison Square Garden, and the New York Knicks beat the Charlotte Bobcats 125-96. Anthony, with 56 after three quarters, stays in for the first few minutes of the fourth to break Bernard King's Knicks record of 60 points and Kobe Bryant's arena record of 61, set five years ago.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Denver cornerback Bradley Roby picks off Tom Brady's pass on a 2-point try with 12 seconds left to preserve a 20-18 victory for the Broncos over the New England Patriots in the AFC title game.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Cam Newton throws two touchdowns and runs for two others, and Carolina's big-play defense stifles Arizona's top-ranked offense in a 49-15 romp for the NFC championship.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Venus Williams beats No. 24-seeded Anastasia Pavlyuchenkova 6-4, 7-6 (3) to become the oldest player to reach the Australian Open women's semifinals in the Open era. The 36-year-old posts her 50th career win at Melbourne Park to earn her a spot in the last four for the first time in 14 years.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 25</hl2><p xmlns="">1894 — Jim Corbett knocks out Charley Mitchell in the third round to retain the world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1924 — The first Winter Olympics are held in Chamonix, France.</p><p xmlns="">1939 — Joe Louis knocks out John Henry Lewis at 2:39 of the first round to retain the world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1945 — Larry MacPhail, Dan Topping and Del Webb purchase the New York Yankees for $2.8 million.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Philadelphia Warriors sets a record for rookies with 58 points in a 127-117 triumph over the Detroit Pistons. Chamberlain also grabs 42 rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Bob Seagren sets an indoor pole vault record in the Millrose Games at New York's Madison Square Garden. Seagren's world record leap is 17 feet, 4 1/4 inches.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Eddie Woods of Oral Roberts grabs 30 rebounds in a 109-95 victory over Louisiana Tech.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Jim Plunkett's two first-quarter touchdown passes, including a Super Bowl-record 80-yard strike to running back Kenny King, leads the Oakland Raiders to a 27-10 victory over the Philadelphia Eagles.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — The New York Giants win the Super Bowl with a 39-20 rout of the Denver Broncos. The Giants, trailing 10-9 at halftime, score 30 points in the second half to set a Super Bowl record. Phil Simms completes a record 10 straight passes and 22 of 25 attempts overall.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Utah guard Rickey Green scores the NBA's 5,000,000th point as the Jazz beat Cleveland 119-96.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Brett Hull scores two goals to become the third player in NHL history to score 50 goals in less than 50 games (49). Hull adds two assists to lead the St. Louis Blues to a 9-4 rout of the Detroit Red Wings.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — John Elway and the Denver Broncos win a Super Bowl for themselves and the AFC, by beating the Green Bay Packers 31-24.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Serena Williams survives an error-filled match to beat elder sister Venus 7-6 (4), 3-6, 6-4 to win the Australian Open for her fourth straight major championship.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Travis and Chavis Holmes shoot their way into the NCAA record books, becoming the highest scoring twin brothers in Division I history. The 6-foot-4 brothers from Virginia Military Institute combined for 47 points to move them 10 points past former VMI twins Ramon and Damon Williams as the top-scoring twin brothers with 3,262 points.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Li Na, who turns 32 next month, beats Dominika Cibulkova 7-6 (3), 6-0 in the Australian Open final to become the oldest woman to clinch the title here in the Open era.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Kate Hansen becomes the first American in nearly 17 years to win a World Cup singles luge race, prevailing at the season finale in Sigulda, Latvia. She's the first World Cup winner for USA Luge since Cameron Myler won in 1997.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Tiger Woods shoots a 79 at Torrey Pines to match his worst score on American soil. Woods misses the 54-hole cut for the first time in his career at the Farmers Insurance Open. Woods is an eight-time winner at Torrey Pines, including the 2008 U.S. Open.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The Anaheim Ducks beats the Los Angeles Kings 3-0 at Dodger Stadium in the NHL's first warm-weather outdoor game.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Mike Krzyzewski earns his 1,000th career win, making him the first NCAA Division I men's coach to reach the milestone, when No. 5 Duke surges past St. John's for a 77-68 victory at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — John Tavares of the New York Islanders matches a record with four goals, and Team Toews beat Team Foligno 17-12 in the highest-scoring NHL All-Star game.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 26</hl2><p xmlns="">1913 — Jim Thorpe gives up his track medals from the 1912 Olympic games as a result of his having been a professional. He had been paid $25 for playing in a semipro baseball game.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Jimmie Foxx and Mel Ott are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1955 — Joe DiMaggio is elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Pete Rozelle is chosen the new commissioner of the National Football League.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Edmonton's Wayne Gretzky scores his 50th goal in the 49th game of the season, a 6-3 victory over the Pittsburgh Penguins.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — The Chicago Bears win their first NFL championship since 1963 by setting a Super Bowl-record for points scored in defeating the New England Patriots 46-10.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Houston guard Vernon Maxwell joins Wilt Chamberlain, David Thompson and George Gervin as the only players in NBA history to score 30 points or more in a quarter. Maxwell scores 30 of his career-high 51 points in the fourth period to help Houston beat Cleveland 103-97.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — The Washington Redskins win their third Super Bowl in 10 years, beating the Buffalo Bills 37-24, putting the game away with 24 straight points after a scoreless first quarter.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — The Green Bay Packers, behind big plays, beat the New England Patriots 35-21 in the Super Bowl. Brett Favre finds Andre Rison for a 54-yard touchdown on the Packers' second offensive play, then throws an 81-yard TD pass to Antonio Freeman in the second quarter. Desmond Howard, the first special teams MVP, scores on a 99-yard kickoff return to put away the Patriots.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Jennifer Capriati produces the greatest comeback in a Grand Slam final to overcome Martina Hingis and defend her Australian Open title. Capriati saved four match points before clinching a 4-6, 7-6 (7), 6-2 victory over Hingis.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Mark Recchi scores two goals, including the 500th of his career, in Pittsburgh's 4-3 shootout win over Dallas.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Martin Brodeur makes 28 saves, extending his NHL record for consecutive 30-win seasons to 11, as the New Jersey Devils beat the Tampa Bay Lightning 2-0.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Mirai Nagasu becomes the second-youngest woman to win the title at the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. The 4-foot-11 14-year-old falls on her opening jump, a double axel, but lands six triple jumps, three in combination, in her program.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Victoria Azarenka wins her second consecutive Australian Open title, beating Li Na 4-6, 6-4, 6-3. Mike and Bob Bryan become the most decorated doubles team in Grand Slam history by winning their 13th major title, beating Robin Haase and Igor Sijsling 6-3, 6-4 in 53 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Ashley Wagner became the first woman since Michelle Kwan in 2005 to win back-to-back titles in the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. Earlier, Olympic silver medalists and 2011 world champions Meryl Davis and Charlie White win their fifth straight dance title, matching a U.S. record.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Stan Wawrinka holds off an injured Rafael Nadal to win his first Grand Slam title with a 6-3, 6-2, 3-6, 6-3 victory in the Australian Open final.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 27</hl2><p xmlns="">1937 — Tris Speaker and Cy Young are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — UCLA, led by Bill Walton, sets an NCAA record for consecutive victories with its 61st win, an 82-63 victory over Notre Dame. UCLA breaks the record of 60 set by San Francisco in 1956. Walton scores 16 points, grabs 15 rebounds and blocks 10 shots.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Geoff Houston of the Cleveland Cavaliers hands out 27 assists, two short of the NBA record and scores 24 points in a 110-106 victory over the Golden State Warriors.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — The New York Giants survive the closest Super Bowl ever when Scott Norwood's 47-yard field goal attempt with 8 seconds left in the game goes wide. The Giants win their second Super Bowl in five years, 20-19 over the Buffalo Bills.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — American Chad Rowan is awarded the highest rank in sumo wrestling, the ancient Japanese sport, making him the first foreign "yokozuna." The 6-foot-8, 455-pounder from Honolulu, becomes the 64th person to hold the top rank in the sport's history.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — The U.S. Golf Association elects Judy Bell as the first female president in its 101-year history.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Jennifer Capriati upsets three-time winner Martina Hingis 6-4, 6-3 to win the Australian Open and her first Grand Slam tournament title.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Hermann Maier wins a World Cup super giant slalom in Kitzbuehel, Austria, a victory he ranks among his finest triumphs. The win comes 18 months after he almost loses his leg in a motorcycle crash.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Serena Williams wins her third Australian Open singles title, routing Maria Sharapova 6-1, 6-2. Unseeded and ranked 81st, Williams wins her eighth and most improbable Grand Slam. She is the second unseeded woman to win the Australian title in the Open era.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Novak Djokovic fends off unseeded Frenchman Jo-Wilfried Tsonga 4-6, 6-4, 6-3, 7-6 (2) in the Australian Open final, earning his first Grand Slam title.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Washington's Gilbert Arenas and Javaris Crittenton are suspended for the remainder of the season by NBA commissioner David Stern. Both players admit bringing a gun or guns into the Wizards' locker room — a violation of the collective bargaining agreement — after a dispute stemming from a card game on a team flight.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Roger Federer, the 16-time Grand Slam winner, is knocked out of the Australian Open by Novak Djokovic in a semifinal match, 7-6 (3), 7-5, 6-4. Federer's loss marks the first time since 2003 that he wouldn't hold any of the four major titles.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Novak Djokovic beats Andy Murray 6-7 (2), 7-6 (3), 6-3, 6-2 to become the first man in the Open era to win three consecutive Australian Open titles.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Speedskater Heather Richardson edges Canada's Christine Nesbitt in the final women's race to become the first American woman to win the World Sprint Championships since 2005. Richardson wins the overall title based on points, with a gold today to go with a pair of bronze medals yesterday.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The NFC blew past the AFC 62-35 in the Pro Bowl. Minnesota tight end Kyle Rudolph is voted the game's MVP with five catches for 122 yards and a touchdown.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>