<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="cac78762-6d81-4020-81cf-115055e0df80" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0375</summary><sourceId>b16298f2-0048-4286-2869-bbabc128b26b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0893%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0375</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Agreed to terms with OF Lorenzo Cain on a five-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed RHPs Austin Boyle and Josh Lang, and LHPs Felix Carvallo and LHP Peter Irvin.</p><hl2 xmlns="">CAN-AM LEAGUE</hl2><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed INF Jerrod Mederos.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BUCKS — Announced Joe Prunty will remain the coach for the rest of the season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">DELAWARE 87ERS — Acquired G Shannon Brown and F Cameron Oliver from Wisconsin for G James Blackmon Jr. and the returning player rights to G Russ Smith. Acquired a 2018 first-round draft pick and the returning player rights to Corey Hawkins from Northern Arizona for F James Michael McAdoo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">CYCLING</hl2><p xmlns="">USADA — Announced cyclist Craig Webb accepted a four-year sanction for an anti-doping rule violation due to his refusal to provide a sample after he finished the 2017 Bell's Iceman Cometh Challenge on November 4, 2017.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BILLS — C Eric Wood announced his retirement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Reassigned LWs Ryan Lomberg, Marek Hrivik and Andrew Mangiapane to Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Reassigned F Jason Dickinson, D Dillon Heatherington and D Julius Honka to Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Recalled F David Booth from Grand Rapids (AHL). Assigned F Dominic Turgeon to Grand Rapids.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned F Kevin Rooney and G Mackenzie Blackwood to Binghamton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK ISLANDERS — Loaned Fs Michael Dal Colle, Ross Johnston and Tanner Fritz to Bridgeport (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Assigned D Tony DeAngelo and Fs Peter Holland and Vinni Lettieri to Hartford (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO GULLS — Assigned C Mitch Hults to Utah (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK CITY FC — Signed D Ben Sweat.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">FLOIRDA — Named Larry Scott tight ends coach.</p><p xmlns="">MEMPHIS — Named Desmond Lindsey wide receivers coach.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN STATE — Announced the retirement of athletic director Mark Hollis.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>