<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f3d8ded7-8b7a-4585-a1ae-108b7150f920" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE2NVSYF01T:3</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE2NVSYF01T:3</followId><sourceFileName>PYE2NVSYF01T00000_DNMLENf-20190925130978.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Credit Suisse Spy Probe Has Potential to Topple Top Ranks</title><authors>Patrick Winters</authors><summary>PYE2NVSYF01T(Bloomberg) -- Credit Suisse Group AG plans to finish its probe into a corporate spying case this week, and the findings have the potential to bring down Chief Executive Officer Tidjane Thiam or other senior executives.Investigators are reporting directly into Chairman Urs Rohner, who will move swiftly to either exonerate or take punitive action against top executives, according to a person familiar with the situation, who asked not to be identified because of the sensitivity of...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Credit Suisse Group AG plans to finish its probe into a corporate spying case this week, and the findings have the potential to bring down Chief Executive Officer Tidjane Thiam or other senior executives.</p><p>Investigators are reporting directly into Chairman Urs Rohner, who will move swiftly to either exonerate or take punitive action against top executives, according to a person familiar with the situation, who asked not to be identified because of the sensitivity of the matter. The bank said on Monday that its board of directors was starting a detailed investigation into the surveillance of former wealth management head Iqbal Khan.</p><p>The speed with which Credit Suisse is moving ahead with the probe underscores the explosiveness of the scandal and how quickly its escalated from tabloid fodder into a very real threat for the bank’s top ranks. Among the key questions is who authorized and knew about the hiring of the private investigators to shadow Khan after his resignation to join rival UBS Group AG as co-head of wealth management.</p><p>According to people familiar with the matter, the operation was ordered internally to prevent Khan from poaching private bankers to take to his new employer. It culminated in an altercation last week in the center of Zurich between Khan and representatives of the investigative firm following him, shining a spotlight on the intense rivalry in Switzerland’s outwardly calm financial center.</p><p>The rift between Thiam and Khan had been an open secret for months in the corridors of Credit Suisse’s imposing Zurich headquarters before it spilled into the outside world during the summer. Tensions between the men had already hit a low point back in January during a party at Thiam’s house in the upscale neighborhood of Herrliberg outside the city when the two men had a “very intense row” Swiss daily Tages-Anzeiger reported.</p><p>As with so much in the saga, the two sides give a different version of events. The paper, citing unidentified people close to Thiam, said the argument had been “a personal thing” and not related to the bank, while people close to Khan were quoted as saying that the CEO had grown increasingly exasperated with the younger executive’s success and the fact that he had taken on the role of “crown prince” in a possible CEO succession.</p><p>Both Thiam and chairman Rohner, announcing the probe earlier this week, said that they’re confident that the “truth will emerge,” in the case, according to an internal memo seen by Bloomberg. The lender said media coverage of the recent incidents contained inaccuracies and “sensationalized both facts and events,” before issuing a follow up release which said that Rohner would be in charge of the investigation.</p><p>A spokesman for Credit Suisse declined to comment. The shares fell as much as 3.5% and were trading 3.1% lower as of 3:22 p.m. in Zurich.</p><p>‘Extraordinary Twist’</p><p>As tensions escalated, Khan abruptly exit Credit Suisse in July. A rising star at the bank’s key wealth-management business, he was seen as a potential successor to the CEO, enjoying a rapid ascent to the highest echelons of the bank where his ambitions ultimately put him on a collision course with Thiam.</p><p>The case is also making its way into the city’s legal system. Zurich prosecutor said on Friday it had launched criminal proceedings in response to a complaint from Khan, who said he was threatened. The prosecutor declined further comment, citing ongoing investigations.</p><p>The scandal risks shattering a period of relative calm for Credit Suisse -- and Thiam -- after the bank recently completed a three-year restructuring. The lender had enjoyed better results at the volatile global markets business and seen revenue from securities trading rise recently even as peers posted declines, giving a boost to Thiam amid the acrimony.</p><p>The relationship between Khan and Thiam had soured in the months before his exit, according to people with knowledge of the matter. When a corporate reorganization came in February, Khan’s brief stayed the same, even as two colleagues were elevated to the executive committee. Tensions mounted as Khan’s name surfaced in media reports as a candidate to replace Bernhard Hodler as head of Julius Baer. That job eventually went to Philipp Rickenbacher, a little-known internal candidate.</p><p>UBS has been running due diligence checks on Khan as recently as today, that bank’s chairman, Axel Weber, said on Bloomberg TV today.</p><p>“We have made our due diligence, believe me, as a bank in making close contact and making sure that there will be no regret moves,” Weber told Bloomberg TV in an interview with Matthew Miller in Zurich on Wednesday. He added that Khan hadn’t started his new job at UBS and the matter was between him and Credit Suisse.</p><p>(Adds UBS chairman’s comments in final paragraph.)</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Patrick Winters in Zurich at pwinters3@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Dale Crofts at dcrofts@bloomberg.net, Christian Baumgaertel</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>