<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="3ba0bc4d-249a-4f0a-b364-c1bbbf9efd9d" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T095857Z:TX-PAR-EJJ17:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T095857Z:TX-PAR-EJJ17:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T095857Z-TX-PAR-EJJ17.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>fbl</item><item>ENG</item><item>Pr</item><item>Liverpool</item><item>Alisson</item><item>Alisson Becker</item><item>Adrián San Miguel del Castillo</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Alisson cannot wait to make Liverpool return</title><authors></authors><summary>Liverpool goalkeeper Alisson Becker is back in full training and nearing a return to competitive action after six weeks out with a calf injury.The Brazilian number one was carried off in Liverpool's 4-1 victory over Norwich on the opening night of the Premier League season on August 9."I'm on a good way, I think we are nearly there," he told the Liverpool website."I can go outside to the pitch to do some goalkeeper work and I feel very well."I feel confident and I think now it's just about...</summary><city>London</city><country>GBR</country><xmlText><p>Liverpool goalkeeper Alisson Becker is back in full training and nearing a return to competitive action after six weeks out with a calf injury.</p><p>The Brazilian number one was carried off in Liverpool's 4-1 victory over Norwich on the opening night of the Premier League season on August 9.</p><p>"I'm on a good way, I think we are nearly there," he told the Liverpool website.</p><p>"I can go outside to the pitch to do some goalkeeper work and I feel very well.</p><p>"I feel confident and I think now it's just about getting all my power, all my confidence to come back and do what I love to do."</p><p>Alisson was named men's goalkeeper of the year at FIFA's annual awards ceremony in Milan on Monday for his role in helping Liverpool win the Champions League last season.</p><p>Even without the inspirational goalkeeper, the Reds have also made a brilliant start in their quest to end a 30-year wait to win the Premier League, winning all six of their opening games to take a five-point lead over Manchester City.</p><p>Stand-in 'keeper Adrian, who only joined the club four days before the Norwich game, has overcome an uncertain start and was pivotal to a 2-1 win at Chelsea on Sunday.</p><p>And Alisson admitted the Spaniard's form has allowed him not to rush his recovery.</p><p>"I think the boys are doing very well, all the team (and) Adrian especially," he added.</p><p>"He's a special guy who came late in the season, he just came and shows everyone his value, not just as a player but as a person and that is the more important thing.</p><p>"He is doing very well on the pitch. I have peace to recover in a proper way so it's better for everyone."</p><p>Liverpool manager Jurgen Klopp has hinted Alisson may not return until after the October international break, but the 26-year-old is desperate to get back on the field and play his part in the push for the title.</p><p>"If I look back, two weeks ago I couldn't even walk properly. Now I'm running, jumping on my right leg that was injured so I'm really happy for that," he said.</p><p>"The games, the atmosphere at Anfield, the away games, all games when I watch on the TV, I just think how I want to play, I want to be there, I want to help my team-mates. I'm looking forward (to being back), I can't wait any more!"</p><p>kca/bsp</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>