<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="920744d9-103f-88e9-9900-c5a0ff331b85" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Nedra Rhone</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (300 words)</title><summary>LIKE BUTTERL’Occitane’s new Shea Body Melting Butter ($34) features new technology that blends the richness of a whipped body butter with the lighter texture of an oil. The melting butter uses 70 percent shea butter. It also comes in a...</summary><sourceId>6e870f8b-1b81-be56-e56d-9c36f2ba59be</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1242%ksigt%w%BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (300 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Eyecatchers: Body butter; Casper Wave; corrective masque</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(NOT INCLUDED IN YOUR TRIBUNE NEWS SERVICE SUBSCRIPTION. To subscribe to Trends and Shopping, see purchase information below.) (PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Nedra Rhone</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">LIKE BUTTER</p><p xmlns="">L’Occitane’s new Shea Body Melting Butter ($34) features new technology that blends the richness of a whipped body butter with the lighter texture of an oil. The melting butter uses 70 percent shea butter. It also comes in a limited-edition jasmine-scented version. In addition, try the new Shea 3-in-1 Cleansing Water ($24), which serves as a cleanser, makeup remover and a toner all-in-one. Ingredients include shea extract, orange blossom floral water and cornflower floral water which leave skin feeling hydrated. All products are available at L’Occitane stores nationwide.</p><p xmlns="">CATCH THE WAVE</p><p xmlns="">The new Casper Wave is an ergonomic mattress designed to respond to body geometry for deeper, more restorative sleep. Casper’s patented system mimics the shape of the body at 36 different points. With a new foam top layer, the Wave offers a more velvety feel and is taller than other Casper mattresses. The Wave starts at $1,000 for a twin size mattress.</p><p xmlns="">WINE RECOVERY</p><p xmlns="">Banish the redness and inflammation that can come with overindulging when you use SkinCeuticals Phyto Corrective Masque. The new masque offers double the cooling, calming and hydrating power of the original formula. The light, gel-formula masque is perfect for sensitive or problem skin. It contains botanical extracts which have anti-inflammatory and antiseptic properties to soothe skin. It costs $57 and is available at LovelySkin.com, SkinCeuticals.com and dermatologists nationwide.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.) at www.ajc.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">TO SUBSCRIBE TO TRENDS AND SHOPPING</p><p xmlns="">This column/content is for subscribers only. It is sold separately and is not included in your Tribune News Service subscription. To subscribe, please contact Rick DeChantal at Tribune Content Agency, (1-312-222-8682) or rdechantal@tribpub.com, or you can purchase individual columns a la carte at www.tribunenewsservice.com.</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002609,t000014987,t000002537,t000032262,t000014995</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>