<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="bc404b8c-0dd9-4b24-9eae-561bc59e617e" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE0EZSYF01Y:14</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE0EZSYF01Y:14</followId><sourceFileName>PYE0EZSYF01Y00000_DNMLENf-20190925120900.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>U.S. Futures Edge Lower as Dollar Jumps, Oil Drops: Markets Wrap</title><authors>Todd White</authors><summary>PYE0EZSYF01Y(Bloomberg) -- U.S. equity-index futures edged lower while stocks slumped in Europe and Asia as investors weighed the deepening political gridlock in Washington against prospects for reduced trade tension between America and China. The dollar jumped, while oil fell.Contracts for all three main equity gauges signaled a weak start in New York as traders grappled with the impeachment investigation into President Donald Trump, taking little comfort from a Bloomberg report that China...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- U.S. equity-index futures edged lower while stocks slumped in Europe and Asia as investors weighed the deepening political gridlock in Washington against prospects for reduced trade tension between America and China. The dollar jumped, while oil fell.</p><p>Contracts for all three main equity gauges signaled a weak start in New York as traders grappled with the impeachment investigation into President Donald Trump, taking little comfort from a Bloomberg report that China is preparing to buy more U.S. pork. Philip Morris and Altria both climbed in pre-market trading after ending merger talks. The Stoxx Europe 600 Index headed for its largest drop in six weeks. Asian benchmarks retreated across the board, with losses of more than 1% in Hong Kong, South Korea, mainland China and India.</p><p>Crude futures declined after Saudi Aramco said it was ahead of schedule in restoring output that was reduced by a drone attack earlier in September. A dollar gauge was on track for its biggest advance since July as Treasuries stabilized.</p><p>Markets have seemed to gyrate on the twists and turns of the protectionist battle between the two largest economies, with this year’s epic bond rally recovering from a pullback and U.S. stocks lingering within sight of a record high. The sudden escalation of political risk in Washington comes as economic signals deteriorate globally, adding a fresh complication for investors trying to decide whether central banks will be able to shore up growth.</p><p>Elsewhere, the pound slumped as Britain’s attorney general said a motion for a general election will be brought to Parliament “shortly.” In Japan, five-year government bond yields fell to a record low following comments from central bank Governor Haruhiko Kuroda that added to speculation of an interest-rate cut in October.</p><p>These are some key events coming up this week:</p><p>Here are the main moves in markets:</p><p>Stocks</p><p>Currencies</p><p>Bonds</p><p>Commodities</p><p>--With assistance from Sarah Ponczek, Vildana Hajric and Adam Haigh.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Todd White in Madrid at twhite2@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editor responsible for this story: Samuel Potter at spotter33@bloomberg.net</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>