<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="eef688a9-6f30-4677-ab1d-0e323228e984" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T114823Z:TX-PAR-EJL85:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T114823Z:TX-PAR-EJL85:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T114823Z-TX-PAR-EJL85.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>China</item><item>politics</item><item>anniversary</item><item>Xi Jinping</item><item>Dalai Lama</item><item>Mao Zedong</item><item>Deng Xiaoping</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>70 years of Communist China</title><authors></authors><summary>Key dates in the history of communist China, founded 70 years ago.- 1949: communist republic declared - After the defeat of the nationalists in a civil war, Communist Party chairman Mao Zedong proclaims the establishment of the People's Republic of China on October 1, 1949.The nationalists flee to the island of Taiwan and form a government in Taipei.In the Hundred Flowers campaign of 1956-1957, Mao urges intellectuals to criticise the Communist Party, later sending 500,000 of those who speak...</summary><city>Beijing</city><country>CHN</country><xmlText><p>Key dates in the history of communist China, founded 70 years ago.</p><p></p><p></p><p>After the defeat of the nationalists in a civil war, Communist Party chairman Mao Zedong proclaims the establishment of the People's Republic of China on October 1, 1949.</p><p>The nationalists flee to the island of Taiwan and form a government in Taipei.</p><p>In the Hundred Flowers campaign of 1956-1957, Mao urges intellectuals to criticise the Communist Party, later sending 500,000 of those who speak out to labour camps.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Mao implements the Great Leap Forward campaign to overhaul the agrarian economy through industrialisation and collective farming.</p><p>It results in economic catastrophe and a three-year famine in which as many as 45 million people perish.</p><p>In 1959 Beijing sends soldiers to crush a revolt in Tibet against Chinese rule. The Dalai Lama, Tibet's spiritual leader, flees to India.</p><p>In 1964 China obtains the nuclear bomb.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Mao launches the decade-long Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution ostensibly to purge capitalists to create social equality, but also to remove his political rivals.</p><p>The drive sees armies of youthful Red Guards targeting anyone deemed to be part of the bourgeoisie, including intellectuals and academics.</p><p>It unleashes chaos, with millions of people persecuted, imprisoned or killed until the army re-establishes order in 1969. </p><p></p><p></p><p>Beijing takes China's seat at the United Nations, which had previously been held by Taipei.</p><p>It becomes one of five countries to have a permanent seat at the UN Security Council.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Mao dies in September 1976 and the next month the "Gang of Four" -- powerful party members who directed his Cultural Revolution and include his wife -- are arrested.</p><p>They are accused of being "anti-Party and anti-socialist", and sentenced to long jail terms.</p><p>The next supreme leader, Deng Xiaoping, initiates economic reforms.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Troops open fire on students in peaceful pro-democracy demonstrations in Beijing's Tiananmen Square. </p><p>The death toll is estimated at between several hundred to over a thousand.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Britain returns Hong Kong to China at the end of a 99-year lease and with the pledge that the commercial and financial hub will be able to maintain a high degree of autonomy for 50 years.</p><p></p><p></p><p>China joins the World Trade Organisation.</p><p>In 2003 China sends its first man to space.  </p><p>In 2010 China overtakes Japan as the world's second biggest economy after the United States.</p><p></p><p></p><p>In March China's parliament endorses a move by Xi Jinping -- in power since 2012 -- to abolish a 10-year limit on presidential terms.</p><p>Xi's name is also added to the constitution, enhancing the authority of China's most powerful leader since Mao.</p><p></p><p></p><p>The UN accuses China in August of detaining up to one million Uighurs and other Muslim minorities in "reeducation" camps as part of a long-running crackdown. </p><p>Chinese authorities say the camps are being used to halt separatist sentiments and religious extremism.</p><p></p><p></p><p>Hong Kong is rocked by months of massive and increasingly violent protests sparked by a government bill that would allow extraditions to mainland China.</p><p>Pro-democracy protests continue even after the bill is withdrawn in September, in the biggest challenge to China's rule since the 1997 handover.</p><p>mm-eab-br/rox/rbu</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>