<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0aeb72de-eeda-467a-b39e-2162299684cc" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T131247Z:TX-PAR-EJN77:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T131247Z:TX-PAR-EJN77:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T131247Z-TX-PAR-EJN77.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>France</item><item>wine</item><item>Burgundy</item><item>police</item><item>Vincent Gros</item><item>Manuel Fernandes</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Cop au vin: French police on patrol to protect vineyards</title><authors></authors><summary>Amid the rolling green expanse of France's prestigious Burgundy wine lands there is an unusual sight: shiny police helmets bobbing between rows of vines.Mounted on bikes and motorcycles, these gendarmerie officers are entrusted with shielding Burgundy's celebrated wine grapes from thieves.Day and night they criss-cross the vineyards looking for raiders, both large-scale and small, who pose a perpetual threat to France's viticulturists."The damage is enormous," said Vincent Gros, who heads...</summary><city>Vosne-Romanée</city><country>FRA</country><xmlText><p>Amid the rolling green expanse of France's prestigious Burgundy wine lands there is an unusual sight: shiny police helmets bobbing between rows of vines.</p><p>Mounted on bikes and motorcycles, these gendarmerie officers are entrusted with shielding Burgundy's celebrated wine grapes from thieves.</p><p>Day and night they criss-cross the vineyards looking for raiders, both large-scale and small, who pose a perpetual threat to France's viticulturists.</p><p>"The damage is enormous," said Vincent Gros, who heads the Gros Frere et Soeur wine estate in the Cote d'Or region that hosts the central French region's most exclusive wines. </p><p>Sometimes just a bunch is stolen here and there, sometimes several rows or entire blocks of grapes, lamented 32-year-old Gros, who said he had installed security cameras in isolated fields. </p><p>"The presence of the police reassures us," he told AFP.</p><p></p><p></p><p>So who are the thieves? </p><p>Often other farmers whose crops were damaged by frost, hail or sunburn. </p><p>"When the harvest is small, it is tempting to go and steal grapes. All you need are cutting shears and a bucket," said Gros. </p><p>"With 40 thieves cutting, it can go very quickly!"  </p><p>Sometimes the loss is accidental -- contractors have been known to harvest the wrong tract of land. </p><p>At the start of the harvest in the Cote d'Or, under a brilliant sun, seasonal workers are carefully prising loose the precious fruit that will yield the next vintage. </p><p>They stop occasionally to wave at two policemen zipping past on bikes.</p><p>Two more use offroad motorcycles for their surveillance, while after sunset, a team of three patrollers drive around by car and peer into the dark with night-vision goggles. </p><p></p><p></p><p>"When we spot people who have no business in the vineyards at night, we turn a spotlight on them.... and we question them," said a patrolling officer who identified himself only as Philippe.</p><p>"The thefts mostly happen at night... and in the early morning hours. Sometimes the thieves are many, and using harvesting machines." </p><p>The patrols were started in the Burgundy region, whose unique wine-growing tradition has been inscribed on the UNESCO World Heritage list, after a poor harvest in 2016 that was aggravated by a rise in theft.</p><p>According to Cote d'Or police department, stealing grapes is punishable by up to three years in prison and a fine of 45,000 euros (almost $50,999). </p><p>"Grape theft is not only a crime but also directly affects the economy of the region and its wine sector already heavily affected by climate hazards," the department stressed on its Facebook page.</p><p>cha/mlr/sjw/dl</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>