<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2aa715d4-a053-875b-a681-d05c8603ac13" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Nedra Rhone</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (250 words)</title><summary>DEEP CLEANSENew from Tatcha comes a purifying gel cleanser with natural exfoliants to clarify and clean normal to oily skin. The Deep Cleanse is an oil-free cleanser that features silk-derived amino acids, fruit extracts and natural fruit fibers...</summary><sourceId>1e621e9c-a985-ec26-c261-5c279d925de9</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7579%ksigt%w%BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (250 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Eyecatchers: Deep cleanser; lipstick from Pat McGrath</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(NOT INCLUDED IN YOUR TRIBUNE NEWS SERVICE SUBSCRIPTION. To subscribe to Trends and Shopping, see purchase information below.) (PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Nedra Rhone</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">DEEP CLEANSE</p><p xmlns="">New from Tatcha comes a purifying gel cleanser with natural exfoliants to clarify and clean normal to oily skin. The Deep Cleanse is an oil-free cleanser that features silk-derived amino acids, fruit extracts and natural fruit fibers that work together to give skin a healthy glow. The gel lathers into a foam that lifts dirt from skin without over-drying. It is safe for even the most delicate skin and helps reduce the appearance of pores. Use it with Tatcha’s best-seller The Water Cream. The Deep Cleanse costs $38 and is available online at Sephora and Tatcha.com</p><p xmlns="">DECADENCE FOR LIPS</p><p xmlns="">Makeup artist Pat McGrath has introduced 11 new shades of her Mattetrance Lipstick. The award-winning, highly pigmented lipstick took over the beauty industry last summer when shades sold out almost immediately. The new shades are inspired by the opulence of three decades of couture shows in McGrath’s archives. The shades range from soft peach (Peep Show) to velvet wine (Full Blooded). FemmeBot, a mid-tone neutral pink, promises to be a favorite. The new colors are available now for $38 at patmcgrath.com and sephora.com</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.) at www.ajc.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">TO SUBSCRIBE TO TRENDS AND SHOPPING</p><p xmlns="">This column/content is for subscribers only. It is sold separately and is not included in your Tribune News Service subscription. To subscribe, please contact Rick DeChantal at Tribune Content Agency, (1-312-222-8682) or rdechantal@tribpub.com, or you can purchase individual columns a la carte at www.tribunenewsservice.com.</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>