<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="742b5d50-e32d-4314-b115-c72abda5e64f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0342</summary><sourceId>b91e67e8-70b7-4260-2608-aa7310ab119b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2030%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0342</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Saturday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agered to terms with C Audry Perez, OF D'Arby Myers, RHP Eddie Gamboa and 3B Anderson Feliz on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with RHP Omar Bencomo and OF Jermaine Curtis on minor league contracts.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Agreed to terms with RHP Ernesto Frieri on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE PREDATORS — Reassigned F Frederick Gaudreau to Milwaukee (AHL). Activated F Viktor Arvidsson from injured reserve.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Reassigned G Brandon Halverson and D Sergey Zborovskiy from Greenville (ECHL) to Hartford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">VEGAS GOLDEN KNIGHTS — Assigned D Jason Garrison to Chicago (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG JETS — Recalled F Jansen Harkins from Jacksonville (ECHL) to Manitoba (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">MANITOBA MOOSE — Recalled F Elgin Pearce from Jacksonville (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">ROCKFORD ICEHOGS — Assigned D Brandon Anselmini to Indy (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MARLIES — Recalled F Josh Winquist from Orlando (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Added G Nolan Bowker as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Released F Gary Steffes.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY MAVERICKS — Released G Kent Patterson.</p><p xmlns="">MANCHESTER MONARCHS — Signed G Joe Spagnoli and F Jake Wood.</p><p xmlns="">TULSA OILERS — Signed F Ryan Rosenthal.</p><p xmlns="">WHEELING NAILERS — Loaned F Garrett Meurs to Manitoba (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">LA GALAXY — Traded F Gyasi Zardes and targeted allocation money to Columbus for F Ola Kamara.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK COSMOS — Agreed on a transfer fee for M Eric Calvillo with the San Jose (MLS).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">KANSAS — Announced freshman men's basketball F Billy Preston signed with BC Igokea (Division I-Bosnia).</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN CAL — Promoted Bryan Ellis to quarterbacks coach and Keary Colbert tight ends and inside receivers coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>