<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TEN-RESULTS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c9387d70-d59b-4ced-90bb-4bf71a379323" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</title><summary>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</summary><sourceId>ad598f1b-4577-4c1c-c1c8-43dad403ef52</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7149%-----%r%BC-TEN--Australian Open Results;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">MELBOURNE (AP) — Results Wednesday from the Australian Open at Melbourne Park (seedings in parentheses):</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Rafael Nadal (1), Spain, def. Leonardo Mayer, Argentina, 6-3, 6-4, 7-6 (4).</p><p xmlns="">Damir Dzumhur (28), Bosnia-Herzegovina, def. John Millman, Australia, 7-5, 3-6, 6-4, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Diego Schwartzman (24), Argentina, def. Casper Ruud, Norway, 6-4, 6-2, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Pablo Carreno-Busta (10), Spain, def. Gilles Simon, France, 6-2, 3-0.</p><p xmlns="">Gilles Muller, Luxembourg, def. Malek Jaziri, Tunisia, 7-5, 6-4, 6-7 (5), 3-6, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Ryan Harrison, United States, def. Pablo Cuevas (31), Uruguay, 6-4, 7-6 (5), 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Marin Cilic (6), Croatia, def. Joao Sousa, Portugal, 6-1, 7-5, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Jo-Wilfried Tsonga (15), France, def. Denis Shapovalov, Canada, 3-6, 6-3, 1-6, 7-6 (4), 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Kyle Edmund, Britain, def. Denis Istomin, Uzbekistan, 6-2, 6-2, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Nikoloz Basilashvili, Georgia, def. Ruben Bemelmans, Belgium, 7-5, 6-1, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Andreas Seppi, Italy, def. Yoshihito Nishioka, Japan, 6-1, 6-3, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Ivo Karlovic, Croatia, def. Yuichi Sugita, Japan, 7-6 (3), 6-7 (3), 7-5, 4-6, 12-10.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Second Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Luksika Kumkhum, Thailand, def. Belinda Bencic, Switzerland, 6-1, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Petra Martic, Croatia, def. Irina Begu, Romania, 6-4, 7-6 (3).</p><p xmlns="">Alize Cornet, France, def. Julia Goerges (12), Germany, 6-4, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Denisa Allertova, Czech Republic, def. Shuai Zhang, China, 6-4, 7-6 (5).</p><p xmlns="">Magda Linette, Poland, def. Daria Kasatkina (22), Russia, 7-6 (4), 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Marta Kostyuk, Ukraine, def. Olivia Rogowska, Australia, 6-3, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Elina Svitolina (4), Ukraine, def. Katerina Siniakova, Czech Republic, 4-6, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Jelena Ostapenko (7), Latvia, def. Ying-Ying Duan, China, 6-3, 3-6, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Anett Kontaveit (32), Estonia, def. Mona Barthel, Germany, 6-3, 4-6, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Kaia Kanepi, Estonia, def. Monica Puig, Puerto Rico, 6-4, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Katerina Bondarenko, Ukraine, def. Anastasia Pavlyuchenkova (15), Russia, 6-2, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Magdalena Rybarikova (19), Slovakia, def. Kirsten Flipkens, Belgium, 6-4, 0-6, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Kiki Bertens (30), Netherlands, def. Nicole Gibbs, United States, 7-6 (3), 6-0.</p><p xmlns="">Caroline Wozniacki (2), Denmark, def. Jana Fett, Croatia, 3-6, 6-2, 7-5.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Fabio Fognini, Italy and Marcel Granollers, Spain, def. Alex Bolt, Australia and Bradley Mousley, Australia, 6-7 (6), 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Feliciano Lopez, Spain and Marc Lopez (9), Spain, def. Nenad Zimonjic, Serbia and Florin Mergea, Romania, 6-2, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Jan-Lennard Struff, Germany and Ben Mclachlan, Japan, def. Thanasi Kokkinakis, Australia and Jordan Thompson, Australia, 6-4, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Guillermo Garcia-Lopez, Spain and Pablo Carreno-Busta, Spain, def. Robin Haase, Netherlands and Matwe Middelkoop, Netherlands, 3-6, 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Benoit Paire, France and Hugo Nys, France, def. Julio Peralta, Chile and Santiago Gonzalez (13), Mexico, 6-4, 0-6, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Artem Sitak, New Zealand and Wesley Koolhof, Netherlands, def. Frederic Niemeyer, Canada and Peter Gojowczyk, Germany, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Oliver Marach, Austria and Mate Pavic (7), Croatia, def. Victor Estrella Burgos, Dominican Republic and Federico Delbonis, Argentina, 6-1, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Bruno Soares, Brazil and Jamie Murray (5), Britain, def. Donald Young, United States and Francis Tiafoe, United States, 5-7, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Alexander Peya, Austria and Nikola Mektic, Croatia, def. Julien Benneteau, France and Jonathan Eysseric, France, 6-3, 6-0.</p><p xmlns="">Robert Farah, Colombia and Juan Sebastian Cabal (11), Colombia, def. Andrew Whittington, Australia and Marc Polmans, Australia, 7-6 (5), 7-6 (4).</p><p xmlns="">Sam Querrey, United States and Steve Johnson, United States, def. Fernando Verdasco, Spain and Ivan Dodig (14), Croatia, 6-4, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Pablo Andujar, Spain and Albert Ramos-Vinolas, Spain, def. Sanchai Ratiwatana, Thailand and Sonchat Ratiwatana, Thailand, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Bob Bryan, United States and Mike Bryan (6), United States, def. Marton Fucsovics, Hungary and Yoshihito Nishioka, Japan, 5-7, 7-5, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Max Mirnyi, Belarus and Philipp Oswald, Austria, def. Dudi Sela, Israel and Thomas Fabbiano, Italy, 7-6 (5), 3-6, 7-6 (4).</p><p xmlns="">Robert Lindstedt, Sweden and Franko Skugor, Croatia, def. Roman Jebavy, Czech Republic and Jiri Vesely, Czech Republic, 7-5, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Radu Albot, Moldova and Hyeon Chung, Republic of Korea, def. Daniel Nestor, Canada and Jonathan Erlich, Israel, 7-6 (4), 6-3.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Yung-Jan Chan, Taiwan and Andrea Sestini Hlavackova (1), Czech Republic, def. Xinyun Han, China and Chen Liang, China, 6-3, 6-0.</p><p xmlns="">Varvara Lepchenko, United States and Oksana Kalashnikova, Georgia, def. Qiang Wang, China and Yafan Wang, China, 6-4, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Michaella Krajicek, Netherlands and Alla Kudryavtseva, Russia, def. Pauline Parmentier, France and Tatjana Maria, Germany, 6-4, 1-6, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Katarina Srebotnik, Slovenia and Hao-Ching Chan (14), Taiwan, def. Coco Vandeweghe, United States and Laura Robson, Britain, 7-6 (3), 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Viktorija Golubic, Switzerland and Nina Stojanovic, Serbia, def. Andreja Klepac, Slovenia and Maria Jose Martinez Sanchez (9), Spain, 6-3, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Katerina Bondarenko, Ukraine and Aleksandra Krunic, Serbia, def. Arina Rodionova, Australia and Natalia Vikhlyantseva, Russia, 6-2, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Barbora Strycova, Czech Republic and Lucie Safarova (4), Czech Republic, def. Anna Smith, Britain and Naomi Broady, Britain, 6-2, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Olga Savchuk, Ukraine and Raluca-Ioana Olaru, Romania, def. Yulia Putintseva, Kazakhstan and Kateryna Kozlova, Ukraine, 6-3, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Sorana Cirstea, Romania and Beatriz Haddad Maia, Brazil, def. Veronika Kudermetova, Russia and Aryna Sabalenka, Belarus, 6-2, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Anna-Lena Groenefeld, Germany and Raquel Atawo (12), United States, def. Astra Sharma, Australia and Belinda Woolcock, Australia, 7-6 (2), 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Lidziya Marozava, Belarus and Lesley Kerkhove, Netherlands, def. Lyudmyla Kichenok, Ukraine and Makoto Ninomiya, Japan, 7-6 (4), 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Shuai Peng, China and Su-Wei Hsieh (8), Taiwan, def. Mihaela Buzarnescu, Romania and Maria Irigoyen, Argentina, 6-3, 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Kristyna Pliskova, Czech Republic and Donna Vekic, Croatia, def. Anna-Lena Friedsam, Germany and Alison Van Uytvanck, Belgium, 5-0.</p><p xmlns="">Jessica Moore, Australia and Ellen Perez, Australia, def. Darija Jurak, Croatia and Nao Hibino, Japan, 6-4, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Monica Niculescu, Romania and Irina Begu (10), Romania, def. Andrea Petkovic, Germany and Mirjana Lucic-Baroni, Croatia, 6-7 (6), 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Anastasija Sevastova, Latvia and Ekaterina Alexandrova, Russia, def. Catherine Cartan Bellis, United States and Marketa Vondrousova, Czech Republic, 6-3, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Elena Vesnina, Russia and Ekaterina Makarova, Russia, def. Sloane Stephens, United States and Eugenie Bouchard, Canada, 6-4, 6-4.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TEN-RESULTS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>