<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="504643c8-0565-40da-ae7c-8ba71a5f4060" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2TR:825692259</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2TR:825692259</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T122651Z_825692259_L3N26G2TR_RTRMADT_0_ALTRIA-M-A-PHILIPMORRIS-UPDATE-2.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UPDATE 2-Philip Morris and Altria ditch merger talks amid vaping crackdown</title><summary>ALTRIA-M&amp;A/PHILIPMORRIS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Philip Morris and Altria ditch merger talks amid vaping crackdown</summary><xmlText><p>UPDATE 2-Philip Morris and Altria ditch merger talks amid vaping crackdown</p><p>* PMI and Altria abandon their merger talks</p><p>* E-cig maker Juul says CEO is stepping down (Adds detail)</p><p>By Siddharth Cavale and Nivedita Balu</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - Philip Morris International has scrapped merger talks with Altria Group and will instead focus on the launch of its tobacco-heating product iQOS in the United States, the company said on Wednesday.</p><p>The abandonment of the mega-merger comes at a time when e-cigarettes and vaping are facing intense regulatory scrutiny across the world, rattling the tobacco industry and the strategies of big players.</p><p>"After much deliberation, the companies have agreed to focus on launching iQOS in the U.S. as part of their mutual interest to achieve a smoke-free future," Philip Morris CEO André Calantzopoulos said. The deal would have seen the tobacco companies reuniting a decade after their split and creating an industry heavyweight.</p><p>Philip Morris's leading heat-not-burn product, iQOS, is not a typical vaping device but instead heats packages of ground-up tobacco into a nicotine-filled aerosol.</p><p>Altria, though, has a 35% stake in U.S. market-leading e-cigarette company Juul Labs Inc, whose devices vaporize a liquid containing nicotine.</p><p>Separately, Juul reported on Wednesday its CEO Kevin Burns was stepping down, and that it would suspend all broadcast, print and digital advertising in the United States.</p><p>Shares in Philip Morris rose 6.5% in premarket trading, while those of Altria MO.N were up 3.7%.</p><p>Rivals British American Tobacco and Imperial Brands rose  between 2% as 3% in afternoon trading on the announcements. (Reporting by Siddharth Cavale and Nivedita Balu in Bengaluru; Editing by Pravin Char)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>