<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0303a903-c860-4f01-b419-782ea2936910" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDZJ2T1UM0W:3</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDZJ2T1UM0W:3</followId><sourceFileName>PYDZJ2T1UM0W00000_DNMLENf-20190925120913.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Bain, Advent to Bid for Osram as Takeover Battle Escalates</title><authors>Sarah Syed, Eyk Henning and Oliver Sachgau</authors><summary>PYDZJ2T1UM0W(Bloomberg) -- Bain Capital and Advent International are preparing a fresh offer for German lighting maker Osram Licht AG, ratcheting up a bidding war with Austrian sensor maker AMS AG.The two buyout firms will spend the coming weeks conducting due diligence, before deciding on a binding proposal, Osram said in a release on Wednesday, confirming an earlier story by Bloomberg. The offer will exceed AMS’s 38.50 euros-a-share bid worth 3.7 billion euros ($4.1 billion), it...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Bain Capital and Advent International are preparing a fresh offer for German lighting maker Osram Licht AG, ratcheting up a bidding war with Austrian sensor maker AMS AG.</p><p>The two buyout firms will spend the coming weeks conducting due diligence, before deciding on a binding proposal, Osram said in a release on Wednesday, confirming an earlier story by Bloomberg. The offer will exceed AMS’s 38.50 euros-a-share bid worth 3.7 billion euros ($4.1 billion), it added.</p><p>Osram gained 2.2% to 38.79 euros as of 2:12 p.m. in Frankfurt.</p><p>Bain’s pursuit of Osram has fresh momentum after the firm teamed up with Advent as a replacement for earlier partner Carlyle Group, which backed away. The private equity firms will need to snatch the initiative away from AMS, which trumped an earlier offer and won the support of Osram’s board.</p><p>The door is open to a come back. Management of the German lighting maker expressed some reservations about AMS’s proposal and Osram’s workforce had come out in favor of Bain and Carlyle. Today’s indicative offer played to union’s concerns.</p><p>“We believe the future of Osram needs to be well aligned with all stakeholders, including unions and employee representatives,” Bain and Advent said in a letter to Osram, cited in the release.</p><p>The buyout group is prepared to “make clear commitments in this respect,” according to the release, adding that the board of Osram wants the non-binding offer from Advent and Bain to be “further concretized.”</p><p>AMS Chief Executive Officer Alexander Everke has been speaking with his investors across Europe, the U.S. and Asia to build the case for buying Osram.</p><p>He said last week that his planned takeover of the company garnered “strong support,” prompting AMS to lower the minimum acceptance rate for its offer to 62.5% from 70%. He needs the backing of shareholders to push through a capital raise to finance the deal.</p><p>(Updates with comments from Osram from first paragraph.)</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Sarah Syed in London at ssyed35@bloomberg.net;Eyk Henning in Frankfurt at ehenning1@bloomberg.net;Oliver Sachgau in Munich at osachgau@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Anthony Palazzo at apalazzo@bloomberg.net, Andrew Noël</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>