<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7d84116d-ded1-43df-8c60-42488333a4ba" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By The Associated Press</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4:00 p.m.Stocks are closing higher on Wall Street, driving several of the major indexes to new highs.Retailers and consumer goods companies led the gainers. Energy stocks fell...</summary><sourceId>13d04976-2175-4d6b-d6bb-0f9dfe749aa9</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:EEE2839%-----%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: US stocks finish higher</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates trading.</p><byline xmlns="">By The Associated Press</byline><p /><p xmlns="">The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4:00 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are closing higher on Wall Street, driving several of the major indexes to new highs.</p><p xmlns="">Retailers and consumer goods companies led the gainers. Energy stocks fell along with the price of crude oil. Utilities declined as bond yields rose.</p><p xmlns="">Lowe's rose 3.5 percent after naming three new directors.</p><p xmlns="">American Express slid 1.8 percent after the company suspended its share buy-back program for six months.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 12 points, or 0.4 percent, to 2,810.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average gained 53 points, or 0.2 percent, to 26,071. The Nasdaq composite added 40 points, or 0.6 percent, to 7,336.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.64 percent, the highest level in more than three years.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are mostly higher on Wall Street in midday trading as gains by retailers and consumer goods companies outweighed losses in other sectors.</p><p xmlns="">Technology stocks were among the biggest decliners Friday. Energy companies fell along with the price of crude oil.</p><p xmlns="">Lowe's rose 2.7 percent after naming three new directors.</p><p xmlns="">American Express sank 2.6 percent after the company suspended its share buy-back program for six months.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 3 points, or 0.1 percent, to 2,801.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average lost 47 points to 24,969, weighed down by a drop in IBM. The Nasdaq composite rose 23 points, or 0.3 percent, to 7,318.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.64 percent, the highest level in more than three years.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are opening slightly higher on Wall Street as consumer-focused companies and banks post gains.</p><p xmlns="">Lowe's rose 1.5 percent in early trading Friday after naming three new directors, and Amazon rose 1.2 percent following reports that it would raise the price of monthly Prime memberships.</p><p xmlns="">American Express sank 2.6 percent after the company suspended its share buy-back program for six months.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 6 points, or 0.2 percent, to 2,804.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average rose 4 points to 26,023. The Nasdaq composite rose 25 points, or 0.4 percent, to 7,322.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>