<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="33829381-829f-4ea9-8b66-9c3b6b17ae55" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Utah Alcohol Sales,CORRECTIVE</title><summary>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — In a story Jan. 30 about rising liquor sales in Utah, The Associated Press reported erroneously the name of a wine company. It is Kendall-Jackson Vintner's, not Kendall-Jackson Vinter's.A corrected version of the story is...</summary><sourceId>85852c62-9d64-4ebe-ebe9-6cb6f6e40b70</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL4776%limit%r%BC-US--Utah Alcohol Sales,CORRECTIVE;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Correction: Utah Alcohol Sales story</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Editors who used BC-US--Utah Alcohol Sales, sent Jan. 30 and datelined in Salt Lake City, are asked to use the following story.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — In a story Jan. 30 about rising liquor sales in Utah, The Associated Press reported erroneously the name of a wine company. It is Kendall-Jackson Vintner's, not Kendall-Jackson Vinter's.</p><p xmlns="">A corrected version of the story is below:</p><p xmlns="">Rising Utah liquor sales fueled by more non-Mormons, tourism</p><p xmlns="">In Mormon dominated Utah where alcohol is frowned upon, liquor sales keep climbing each year</p><p xmlns="">By BRADY McCOMBS</p><p xmlns="">Associated Press</p><p xmlns="">SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — In Mormon dominated Utah where alcohol is frowned upon, liquor sales keep climbing each year. State residents bought nearly $428 million in alcohol last year to set another record, continuing a two-decade trend likely fueled a steady influx of new out-of-state residents and a thriving tourism sector.</p><p xmlns="">Alcohol sales at Utah restaurants, bars and 45 state-controlled liquor stores rose 5 percent last fiscal year, shows an annual report released this month from Utah's Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control.</p><p xmlns="">Sales have increased each year going back to 1996, the first year state data is available. Sales have increased 40 percent just in the last six years.</p><p xmlns="">Demographers say a strong economy has drawn many non-Mormons to the state over the last 25 years for jobs. Combine that with flourishing tourism driven by the state's ski areas and red-rock national parks and you have more people in Utah who are not members of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, which instructs members to avoid drinking alcohol.</p><p xmlns="">"It is part of the changing demographics of the state," said Terry Wood, spokesman for Utah's Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control. "This demographic is more likely to purchase alcohol."</p><p xmlns="">Those who drink in Utah appear to be consuming more — the 2.94 average gallons of alcohol consumed per capita was up 3 percent from the year before. It was the 11th consecutive year that the measure increased, agency figures show.</p><p xmlns="">The state was among the lowest in the US in that measure as of 20ch15, the most up-to-date comparable data available, according to the National Institute of Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism.</p><p xmlns="">Wood noted that the state doesn't advertise its liquor stores, saying, "We are not encouraging alcohol use or sales, not discouraging it. It's just there. We provide that service."</p><p xmlns="">Nearly $179 million from the sales went to the state coffers, state agencies and other alcohol abuse prevention programs. That included $43 million to the state school lunch program; $4 million to state bureau of investigation for liquor enforcement; and $2 million to an underage drinking prevention program. About $23 million in sales taxes went to state, county and city governments.</p><p xmlns="">The state's net profit that goes to the state general fund — —$106 million — marked only a 2-percent increase from the year before, the lowest in seven years. That can be attributed to an across-the-board increase in operating costs that included a 4-percent raise for liquor store employees, Wood said.</p><p xmlns="">The sales figures don't include beer that contains less than 4 percent alcohol by volume, which can be purchased at grocery and convenience stores. They cover the state's fiscal year from July 2016 through June 2017.</p><p xmlns="">Once again, wine was the state's favorite kind of alcohol with about 3.6 million gallons sold.</p><p xmlns="">A category called "spirits" that includes vodka, whiskey and tequila was second with 3.15 million gallons sold, while of high-alcohol beer was third with about 2 million gallons sold.</p><p xmlns="">Malt beverage was the only category in which sales decreased. The 213,000 gallons sold were down from about 250,000 gallons each of the previous two years.</p><p xmlns="">Among wines, Cooks Brut Sparkling Wine was the top seller followed by Vendange Pinot Grigio and Kendall-Jackson Vintner's Reserve Chardonnay.</p><p xmlns="">The top-selling spirit was Barton Vodka, followed by Taaka Vodka and Fireball Cinnamon Whisky.</p><p xmlns="">Icehouse led in beer sales by a wide margin, followed by a Squatters Hop Rising Double IPA and Busch Ice Lager.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>