<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="13bf402d-0624-46ef-9d76-f0019b0412c6" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0388</summary><sourceId>f234a7df-5c3b-4b99-b99a-d871d17d7f58</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z4920%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0388</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Sunday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Eds: Deletes Mets transaction, which is not a final agreement.</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO PADRES — Agreed to terms with LHP Brad Hand on a three-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW ORLEANS PELICANS — Signed G Mike James to a two-way contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK KNICKS — Signed G Trey Burke.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">SOUTH BAY LAKERS — Waived G Ian Baker.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BILLS — Named Brian Daboll offensive coordinator.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NHL — Suspended Anaheim F Andrew Cogliano two games, without pay, for an interference penalty against Los Angeles F Adrian Kempe on Saturday night.</p><p xmlns="">BUFFALO SABRES — Assigned G Jonas Johansson from Rochester (AHL) to Cincinnati (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Placed F Jaromir Jagr on injured reserve, retroactive to Dec. 31. Recalled F Ryan Lomberg from Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Reassigned F Lucas Wallmark to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Recalled F J.C. Beaudin from Colorado (ECHL) to San Antonio (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled F Jonny Brodzinski from Ontario (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BINGHAMTON DEVILS — Returned F Phil Lane on loan to Atlanta (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Recalled F Kellen Jones and D Mike Cornell from Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">CHARLOTTE CHECKERS — Recalled F Mitchell Heard from Florida (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">PROVIDENCE BRUINS — Recalled D Ben Marshall from Atlanta (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled F Shawn St. Amant from Colorado (ECHL). Reassigned F Thomas Frazee to Norfolk (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SPRINGFIELD THUNDERBIRDS — Assigned F Francois Beauchemin to Manchester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MARLIES — Recalled F Jean Dupuy from Orlando (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">WILKES-BARRE/SCRANTON PENGUINS — Assigned F Cody Wydo to Wheeling (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ADIRONDACK THUNDER — Released G Joe Spadaccini as emergency backup. Added G T.J. Sherwood as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Signed F Tommy Kelley.</p><p xmlns="">FLORIDA EVERBLADES — Signed F Keegan Bruce.</p><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Released G Doug Melvin as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">ORLANDO SOLAR BEARS — Released G Gordon Defiel as emergency backup.&lt;</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>