<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="832e58fa-8529-8ebc-10b8-48bf7cc07e43" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Nedra Rhone</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (350 words)</title><summary>HAIR BONDOGX has brought a salon-strength hair conditioning system to the masses with OGX Restoring + Bonding Plex collection. The three-step system helps prevent damage from chemical treatments such as coloring and straightening. Cystine, a...</summary><sourceId>e7307e94-94ec-452e-52e9-9c5d7fee384d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1429%ksigt%w%BC-TS-EYECATCHERS:AT — lifestyle (350 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Eyecatchers: Salon-strength hair conditioning; Nars spring collection; boots for Winter Olympics</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(NOT INCLUDED IN YOUR TRIBUNE NEWS SERVICE SUBSCRIPTION. To subscribe to Trends and Shopping, see purchase information below.) (PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Nedra Rhone</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">HAIR BOND</p><p xmlns="">OGX has brought a salon-strength hair conditioning system to the masses with OGX Restoring + Bonding Plex collection. The three-step system helps prevent damage from chemical treatments such as coloring and straightening. Cystine, a cross-linking polymer and keratin proteins form a protective layer over the hair to repair the hair cuticle and prevent future damage. Cleanse with the shampoo, follow with the conditioner and finish with the bonding cream to lock in moisture and restore softness. All three products are available for $8.99 each at Walgreens, CVS, Walmart and other major retailers.</p><p xmlns="">SPRING IT ON</p><p xmlns="">Nars Cosmetics wants you to spring it on with the new color collection for spring 2018. The collection offers neutrals mixed with accent shades for lips and face. Get full-coverage lips with high pigmented Lip Cover lip gloss ($28) in a limited-edition peachy pink, peach beige, pink mauve or black cherry. Add metallic Velvet Shadow Sticks ($29) in pewter and light peacock to eyes and give a skin a glow with a limited-edition brick red shade of Liquid Blush ($30) and a new cool powder formula of Highlighting Blush ($30) in a limited-edition shimmering pink. The collection is available now at Nars, Shops Buckhead Atlanta, 3004 Bolling Way NE., Atlanta or online at www.narscosmetics.com.</p><p xmlns="">APRES SKI STYLE</p><p xmlns="">Get ready for the 2018 Winter Olympics and show your support for the home team with a new pair of boots. Khombu is the official supplier of après ski boots to the U.S. Ski Team through 2024. The popular Alta USA mid-calf boots from the U.S. Ski Team collection feature fleece lining and lightweight construction in red, white, blue and silver. They are stylish but will keep you warm in cold weather. Get them for $50-$70 at amazon.com or DSW.com.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Atlanta Journal-Constitution (Atlanta, Ga.) at www.ajc.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">TO SUBSCRIBE TO TRENDS AND SHOPPING</p><p xmlns="">This column/content is for subscribers only. It is sold separately and is not included in your Tribune News Service subscription. To subscribe, please contact Rick DeChantal at Tribune Content Agency, (1-312-222-8682) or rdechantal@tribpub.com, or you can purchase individual columns a la carte at www.tribunenewsservice.com.</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>