<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5e004fc8-f93e-473d-8aee-d7f0fb907092" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T125410Z:TX-PAR-EJN19:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T125410Z:TX-PAR-EJN19:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T125410Z-TX-PAR-EJN19.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>US</item><item>tobacco</item><item>merger</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Juul CEO steps down as flavored vaping faces outright ban</title><authors></authors><summary>A tobacco industry veteran will replace the current CEO of Juul, the top US e-cigarette manufacturer, as the company suspends all lobbying and advertising and responds to a mounting public backlash against its main products.Also on Wednesday, Altria Group, a major Juul stakeholder, said it had ended merger talks with Philip Morris International, scuttling a potential tie up between the world's two largest tobacco makers.Kevin Burns, co-founder of the San Francisco-based Juul, which had seen...</summary><city>Washington</city><country>USA</country><xmlText><p>A tobacco industry veteran will replace the current CEO of Juul, the top US e-cigarette manufacturer, as the company suspends all lobbying and advertising and responds to a mounting public backlash against its main products.</p><p>Also on Wednesday, Altria Group, a major Juul stakeholder, said it had ended merger talks with Philip Morris International, scuttling a potential tie up between the world's two largest tobacco makers.</p><p>Kevin Burns, co-founder of the San Francisco-based Juul, which had seen a meteoric rise in recent years, will be replaced by K.C. Crosthwaite, a top Altria executive.</p><p>With at least nine dead of causes potentially tied to vaping, e-cigarettes face heightened scrutiny in the United States and a potential ban on most flavored vaping products.</p><p>As traditional tobacco sales decline, the technology had offered old-guard cigarette manufacturers hope of transitioning into a new market.</p><p>A month ago, Altria and Philip Morris International announced merger talks, potentially allowing the two companies to diversify into a shifting consumer market.</p><p>But in a statement, Altria said efforts to reach an agreement to forge a $200 billion combined entity had failed.</p><p>"While we believed the creation of a new merged company had the potential to create incremental revenue and cost synergies, we could not reach agreement," Altria Chairman Howard Willard said in a statement.</p><p>vog-dg/jm</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>