<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7f9e024a-7053-402a-bf8f-687b62c7ca4a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4 p.m.Stocks are closing mostly higher as gains in technology companies and retailers are partly offset by losses in consumer goods makers.Netflix soared 10 percent...</summary><sourceId>af348412-bc6c-4cd7-cd7a-d6f2c7fd44e7</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:W1977%asian%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: Tech stocks send indexes mostly higher</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates with close of US trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are closing mostly higher as gains in technology companies and retailers are partly offset by losses in consumer goods makers.</p><p xmlns="">Netflix soared 10 percent Tuesday after reporting a big gain in subscribers. Amazon climbed 2.7 percent.</p><p xmlns="">U.S. solar power companies and Whirlpool rose after President Donald Trump approved tariffs on imported solar-energy and washing machine components.</p><p xmlns="">Johnson &amp; Johnson slumped 4.3 percent and Procter &amp; Gamble lost 3.1 percent after each company reported disappointing results.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 6 points, or 0.2 percent, to 2,839.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average fell 3 points, less than 0.1 percent, to 26,210. The Nasdaq rose 52 points, or 0.7 percent, to 7,460.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices rose. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note fell to 2.62 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are mostly higher in midday trading as gains in technology companies and retailers are partly offset by losses in consumer goods makers.</p><p xmlns="">Netflix soared 10 percent Tuesday after it gained more subscribers than expected in the fourth quarter. Amazon rose 1.6 percent.</p><p xmlns="">U.S. solar power companies and Whirlpool rose after President Donald Trump approved tariffs on imported solar-energy and washing machine components.</p><p xmlns="">Johnson &amp; Johnson and Procter &amp; Gamble each fell 3 percent after reporting disappointing results.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 4 points, or 0.1 percent, to 2,836.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average fell 17 points, or 0.1 percent, to 26,197. The Nasdaq rose 39 points, or 0.5 percent, to 7,446.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices rose. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note fell to 2.62 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Gains in technology and consumer-focused companies are sending stock indexes mostly higher in early trading on Wall Street.</p><p xmlns="">Netflix soared 11 percent in the first few minutes of trading Tuesday after reporting a strong quarter. Amazon rose 1 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Johnson &amp; Johnson and Procter &amp; Gamble both fell after reporting disappointing results, pulling the Dow Jones industrial average lower.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 2 points, or 0.1 percent, to 2,835.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow industrials fell 23 points, or 0.1 percent, to 26,187. The Nasdaq composite rose 21 points, or 0.3 percent, to 7,428.</p><p xmlns="">Small-company stocks were broadly lower.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices rose. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note fell to 2.63 percent.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>