<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="a2ae154f-dc84-47cb-a15b-3b0d22c5fa3d" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOJHDWRGG1:5</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOJHDWRGG1:5</followId><sourceFileName>PYDOJHDWRGG100000_DNMLENf-20190925080997.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Oil Declines as Saudi Arabia Restores Capacity Ahead of Schedule</title><authors>Alex Longley</authors><summary>PYDOJHDWRGG1(Bloomberg) -- Oil extended losses as Saudi Arabia was said to be ahead of schedule in restoring its output capacity.Futures lost as much as 1.5% in New York after dropping 2.3% on Tuesday. Saudi Aramco’s production capacity now exceeds 11 million barrels a day, beating a self-imposed deadline by about a week, according to people with knowledge of the situation. The Abqaiq processing plant has 4.92 million barrels a day of capacity available and Khurais 1.3 million, they...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Oil extended losses as Saudi Arabia was said to be ahead of schedule in restoring its output capacity.</p><p>Futures lost as much as 1.5% in New York after dropping 2.3% on Tuesday. Saudi Aramco’s production capacity now exceeds 11 million barrels a day, beating a self-imposed deadline by about a week, according to people with knowledge of the situation. The Abqaiq processing plant has 4.92 million barrels a day of capacity available and Khurais 1.3 million, they said.</p><p>Aerial strikes on the two plants on Sept. 14 disabled 5% of global crude supply, driving crude higher by the most on record. Prices have pulled back since as Aramco -- formally known as Saudi Arabian Oil Co. -- has promised it will return all lost production by the end of this month. A gloomy global economic outlook and weakening oil demand growth has also pushed oil lower.</p><p>West Texas Intermediate for November delivery dropped 79 cents, or 1.4%, to $56.50 a barrel on the New York Mercantile Exchange as of 9:18 a.m. London time. Brent for November slipped $1.04, or 1.7%, to $62.06 a barrel on the ICE Futures Europe Exchange, and traded at a $5.53 premium to WTI.</p><p>--With assistance from Heesu Lee.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Alex Longley in London at alongley@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: James Herron at jherron9@bloomberg.net, Rakteem Katakey, John Deane</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>