<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4a85f8ca-c107-4165-9362-41b52fe41afe" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1WR:1156283493</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G1WR:1156283493</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T073134Z_1156283493_L3N26G1WR_RTRMADT_0_BRITAIN-STOCKS-URGENT.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>FTSE 100 slips as Trump impeachment inquiry darkens mood</title><summary>BRITAIN-STOCKS/ (URGENT):FTSE 100 slips as Trump impeachment inquiry darkens mood</summary><xmlText><p>FTSE 100 slips as Trump impeachment inquiry darkens mood</p><p>(For a live blog on European stocks, type LIVE/ in an Eikon news window)</p><p>* FTSE 100 down 0.5%, FTSE 250 down 0.4%</p><p>* Calls for impeachment inquiry into Trump unnerves markets</p><p>* Lingering Brexit worries weigh on domestic stocks</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - London's FTSE 100 fell in tandem with global market peers on Wednesday, as investors feared that a call by U.S. lawmakers for an impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump would pile on more uncertainty to the global economy.</p><p>Trump's latest harsh comments on Beijing's trade practices also dented sentiment around Sino-U.S. proposed talks and broadly hurt blue-chip financial stocks, as well as oil majors and miners, pushing the main index down 0.5%.</p><p>The FTSE 250 shed 0.4% by 0707 GMT as more investors focused on the future course of Brexit, with the House of Commons set to reconvene after the Supreme Court ruled on Tuesday Prime Minister Boris Johnson had suspended parliament unlawfully. (Reporting by Shashwat Awasthi and Indranil Sarkar in Bengaluru; Editing by Bernard Orr)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>