<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c9810a95-3881-4a59-a3fd-8e7d9b0eb4d8" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDHSVT1UM10:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDHSVT1UM10:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDHSVT1UM1000000_DNMLENf-20190925070923.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Bain Attracts Bids for Japanese Hot Spring Operator</title><authors>Takako Taniguchi and Takahiko Hyuga</authors><summary>PYDHSVT1UM10(Bloomberg) -- Bain Capital is collecting bids for Ooedo Onsen Monogatari, an operator of about 40 hot spring inns and resorts across Japan, with SoftBank Group Corp. and investment funds submitting first-round proposals, people with knowledge of the matter said.The U.S. investor is seeking to sell the Ooedo Onsen Monogatari group for more than 100 billion yen ($932 million), said the people, who asked not to be identified because the information isn’t public. Bain Capital is...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Bain Capital is collecting bids for Ooedo Onsen Monogatari, an operator of about 40 hot spring inns and resorts across Japan, with SoftBank Group Corp. and investment funds submitting first-round proposals, people with knowledge of the matter said.</p><p>The U.S. investor is seeking to sell the Ooedo Onsen Monogatari group for more than 100 billion yen ($932 million), said the people, who asked not to be identified because the information isn’t public. Bain Capital is also considering an initial public offering for the hot-spring business, they said. The investment group bought the Japanese company in 2015 for about 50 billion yen, the Nikkei newspaper reported at the time.</p><p>Investors have shown plenty of appetite for hot-spring assets as well as real-estate investment trusts that invest in such leisure facilities. SoftBank-owned Fortress Investment Group has already snapped up about 100 hot-spring establishments and hotels, and has indicated that it will spend as much as 400 billion yen on the sector over the next four years.</p><p>Nomura Holdings Inc. is advising Bain on the sale, the people said. A representative for Bain didn’t immediately respond to a request for comment. Representatives from SoftBank and Nomura declined to comment.</p><p>Ooedo Onsen Monogatari is designed to evoke the atmosphere of Tokyo during feudal times, when it was called Edo, or sometimes Ooedo (“big Edo”). It also runs a REIT that invests in hot-spring properties, returning 8.6% since its inception in 2016.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Takako Taniguchi in Tokyo at ttaniguchi4@bloomberg.net;Takahiko Hyuga in Tokyo at thyuga@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Yuji Okada at yokada6@bloomberg.net, Reed Stevenson, Russell Ward</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>