<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7618894a-e16c-36a0-936c-f7002e183321" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Tod Leonard</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-GLF-FARMERS-WOODS:SD — sports (200 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Tiger Woods provided drama during the second round of the Farmers Insurance Open on Friday at Torrey Pines, making birdie on his final hole to move inside the cut line. If there’s no change, he will play the weekend in a full-field...</summary><sourceId>50338683-4da0-3c47-c479-5245b124929d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3416%kniht%r%BC-GLF-FARMERS-WOODS:SD — sports (200 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Late birdie allows Tiger Woods to move inside cut line at Torrey Pines</h2><byline xmlns="">By Tod Leonard</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Tiger Woods provided drama during the second round of the Farmers Insurance Open on Friday at Torrey Pines, making birdie on his final hole to move inside the cut line. If there’s no change, he will play the weekend in a full-field PGA Tour event for the first time since 2015.</p><p xmlns="">Woods needed a birdie on the ninth hole (his 18th) of the North Course to break par with a 1-under 71 and land on the cut line. A par would have meant he would not have played on the weekend at Torrey Pines for the fourth straight year.</p><p xmlns="">Woods drove the ball in the rough on the par-5 ninth, but was able to reach the green with his second shot and two-putt from at least 60 feet for the birdie. He stands at 1-under 143 after two rounds.</p><p xmlns="">The leader, at 11-under, is Ryan Palmer, who shot a 5-under 67 on the North Course. He has a one-shot advantage over defending champion Jon Rahm, who had a 66 on Friday, also on the North. First-round leader Tony Finau (70, South) and Luke List (66, South) are tied for third at 9-under.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>