<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="17916413-ea2b-43ae-a988-290075b8bf7d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0405</summary><sourceId>9b013a8e-c7ae-4a65-a658-77d84874e494</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z4782%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0405</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 16</hl2><p xmlns="">1962 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Philadelphia Warriors finished with 42 points and 24 rebounds, winning NBA honors even though his East team loses to the West 150-130 in the NBA All-Star game. The West's Bob Pettit pulls down an All-Star record 27 rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — The Dallas Cowboys dominate the Miami Dolphins, setting a Super Bowl record of 252 yards rushing en route to a 24-3 victory.</p><p xmlns="">1974 — Mickey Mantle and Whitey Ford are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame. Mantle is elected in his first year of eligibility and Ford in his second year.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Jimmy "The Greek" Snyder, the CBS NFL Today tout for 12 years, is fired for his racial comments during an interview the previous day with WRC-TV in Washington.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Kansas beats Louisville 98-77 for its 1,500th win in school history.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Michael Jordan scores 64 points, but Chicago is upended in overtime by visiting Orlando 128-124. The Magic are led by rookie center Shaquille O'Neal, who has 29 points and 24 rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Bob Knight becomes the first men's Division I coach with 900 wins when Texas Tech beats No. 10 Texas A&amp;M 68-53.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — New York Jets stun the New England Patriots 28-21. The Patriots, who had the league's best record during the regular season, are sent to their third straight postseason loss. Mark Sanchez throws three touchdown passes, Tom Brady is sacked five times and the Jets advance to their second straight AFC championship game.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — The NCAA restores 112 football wins it stripped from Penn State and Joe Paterno in the Jerry Sandusky child-molestation scandal and reinstates the venerated late coach as the winningest in major college football history. The NCAA announces the settlement with the school weeks before a scheduled trial on the legality of the sanctions imposed in 2012.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Larry Fitzgerald sets up and scores the winning touchdown on the third play of overtime, taking a 5-yard pass from Carson Palmer that lifts Arizona past Green Bay 26-20 after Aaron Rodgers' desperation 41-yard touchdown pass to Jeff Janis on the final play of regulation. Fitzgerald turns a short pass into a 75-yard gain on the first play of overtime to set up his 5-yard shovel pass reception for the winning score.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>