<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="446c4722-30de-48ad-a209-abceed6445d9" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</summary><sourceId>c3cd56af-1366-4cc8-cc89-f170f1a1b7b5</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0883%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Baseball</hl2><p xmlns="">OFFICE OF THE COMMISSIONER OF BASEBALL — Suspended Baltimore minor league LHP Tucker Baca (GCL) 60 games after testing positive for Dehydrochlormethyltestosterone, a performance-enhancing substance. Suspended Pittsburgh minor league RHP Montana Durapau (Indianapolis-IL) 50 games following a second positive test for a drug of abuse. Suspended Atlanta minor league LHP Gabriel Noguera (GCL) 50 games following a second positive test for a drug of abuse.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Traded RHP Dominic Leone and RHP Connor Greene to St. Louis for OF Randal Grichuk.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">HOUSTON ASTROS — Promoted Josh Miller to minor league pitching coordinator and Chris Holt to assistant minor league pitching coordinator. Named Josh Bonifay minor league field coordinator; Mark Bailey minor league catching coordinator; Rodney Linares manager and Ray Hernandez development coach for Fresno (PCL); Omar Lopez manager, Bill Murphy pitching coach, Troy Snitker hitting coach and Mycal Jones development coach for Corpus Christi (Texas); Morgan Ensberg manager, Drew French pitching coach, Ben Rosenthal hitting coach and Nate Shaver development coach for Buies Creek (Cal); Mickey Storey manager, Graham Johnson pitching coach, Dillon Lawson hitting coach and Rafael Pena development coach for Quad Cities (MWL); Cesar Cedenn and Rene Rojas hitting coaches for the GCL Astros; Todd Naskedov pitching coordinator and Ralph Dickenson pitching coordinator at the West Palm Beach complex; and Charlie Romero manager and Rick Aponte pitching coach for the Dominican Summer League Astros.</p><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Agreed to terms with 1B Jonathan Rodriguez on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Announced RHP Chasen Bradford was claimed off waivers by Seattle. Announced RHP Kevin McGowan cleared waivers and was sent outright to Las Vegas (PCL).</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON NATIONALS — Named Randy Knorr manager and Brad Holman pitching coach for Syracuse (IL); Mario Lisson manager and Larry Pardo pitching coach for the GCL Nationals; Michael Tejera pitching coach for Harrisburg (EL); Sam Narron pitching coach for Potomac (Carolina); Tim Redding pitching coach for Hagerstown (SAL) and Franklin Bravo pitching coach for Auburn (NYP); Freddy Guzman hitting coach for the Dominican Summer League Nationals; Billy Gardner Jr. minor league roving coordinator; Shane Hill strength and conditioning coach for Hagerstown; Will Lindholm strength and conditioning coach for Auburn and Anthony Rosario tryout assistant for the DSL Nationals. Promoted Jeff Allred to assistant medical coordinator; Eric Montague trainer for Syracuse; TD Swinford trainer for Harrisburg; Don Neidig trainer for Potomac; Darren Yoos trainer for Hagerstown and Kirby Craft trainer for Auburn.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Released INF Trey Vavra and C Mike Falsetti.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed INF Abel Nieves.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed RHP Charle Rosario.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed LHP Jose Velez, INF Josh Silver and RHP Dylan Brammer.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed RHP Aroni Nina and OF Jose R Gomez.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed 3B Cody Lenahan to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">SCHAUMBURG BOOMERS — Signed RHP Zach Morgenstern.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Signed OF Bryson Bowman.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BULLS — Assigned F/C Cristiano Felicio and F Paul Zipser to Windy City (NBAGL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES LAKERS — Signed F Nigel Hayes to a 10-day contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA CARDINALS — Signed LB Praise Martin-Oguike to a future contract for the 2018 season.</p><p xmlns="">MIAMI DOLPHINS — Named Dowell Loggains offensive coordinator and Jeremiah Washburn offensive line coach. Announced defensive backs coach Lou Anarumo, running backs coach Danny Barrett and defensive line coach Terrell Williams were not retained. Announced Shawn Jefferson will become assistant head coach/offense, Ben Johnson will become wide receivers coach, and Clyde Christensen will become director of football and player development.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Agreed to terms with QB Tyler Ferguson on a reserve/futures contract.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON REDSKINS — Signed OL Orlando Franklin to a reserve/futures contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Agreed to terms with CB Chris Randle on a two-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Recalled Fs Marek Hrivik and Andrew Mangiapane from Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Recalled G Ken Appleby from Binghamton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK ISLANDERS — Recalled F Ross Johnston from Bridgeport (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled D Tony DeAngelo and F Daniel Catenacci from Hartford (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed F Chris Langkow to a professional tryout agreement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Kansas City coach John-Scott Dickson one game and fined him an undisclosed amount for his actions during a Jan. 13 game at Toledo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED — Acquired M Ezequiel Barco from Club Atletico Independiente (Argentine Superleague).</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO FIRE — Acquired the first-round (No. 5) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft from Minnesota for the first-round (No. 15) pick and $175,000 of allocation money and player to be named. Acquired the first-round (No. 10) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft from Real Salt Lake for $85,000 of allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">DC UNITED — Acquired $200,000 in allocation money from Los Angeles FC for the first-round (No. 3) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft.</p><p xmlns="">FC DALLAS — Acquired the first-round (No. 4) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft from Montreal for $200,000 of allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">HOUSTON DYNAMO — Acquired M Darwin Ceren from San Jose for $150,000 in allocation money and future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA UNITED FC — Acquired the first-round (No. 7) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft from Montreal for $150,000 of allocation money. Acquired the first-round (No. 23) pick in the 2018 MLS SuperDraft from Toronto FC for the second-round (No. 28) pick and $50,000 of allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK CITY FC — Signed F Jo Inge Berget.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA UNION — Acquired M David Accam from Chicago for $1.2 million in allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Signed F Foster Langsdorf.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">NCAA — Placed Houston Baptist's football program two years of probation and recruiting penalties after coach Vic Shealy failed to promote an atmosphere of compliance by creating his own student host program.</p><p xmlns="">BYU — Named Preston Hadley safeties coach. Announced the resignation of linebackers coach Steve Kaufusi. Announced assistant head coach Ed Lamb will switch from coaching safeties to the linebackers and coach Kalani Sitake will assist in coaching the defense this season.</p><p xmlns="">ILLINOIS — Named Rod Smith offensive coordinator/quarterbacks coach and Cory Patterson tight ends coach.</p><p xmlns="">LOUISVILLE — Announced the resignation of defensive coordinator Peter Sirmon.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN STATE — Named Mike Tressel defensive coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">NORTH CAROLINA — Named Quinshad Davis offensive graduate football assistant.</p><p xmlns="">PURDUE — Announced the resignation of assistant football coach Tony Levine.</p><p xmlns="">WISCONSIN — Renewed the contracts of football coach Paul Chryst and volleyball coach Kelly Sheffield through January 31, 2023, and women's soccer coach Paula Wilkins and men's soccer coach John Trask through January 31, 2021.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>