<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="a16ebdfd-7e51-4899-adf7-aca3cdc3d1b5" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2MI:426313914</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2MI:426313914</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T105405Z_426313914_L3N26G2MI_RTRMADT_0_VIETNAM-SECURITY-TRIALS.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Vietnam jails former deputy labour minister for economic mismanagement</title><summary>VIETNAM-SECURITY/TRIALS:Vietnam jails former deputy labour minister for economic mismanagement</summary><xmlText><p>Vietnam jails former deputy labour minister for economic mismanagement</p><p>HANOI, Sept 25 (Reuters) - A court in Vietnam on Wednesday sentenced a former deputy labour minister to six years in prison after finding him guilty of economic mismanagement, state media reported.</p><p>Le Bach Hong, who had been deputy minister of labour, invalids and social affairs, and a former head of Vietnam Social Security, was also ordered by the People's Court of Hanoi to pay a cash fine of 150 billion dong ($6.47 million), reported An Ninh Thu Do newspaper, which is run by the Hanoi Police Department.</p><p>Reuters was unable to reach Hong's lawyer for comments.</p><p>The trial comes amid a corruption crackdown in the Southeast Asian country that has seen several senior government officials and executives of state-owned enterprises arrested and jailed.</p><p>The report said Hong and others illegally lent state money to a local financial company that went bankrupt in 2018, causing losses of nearly 1.7 trillion dong ($73.3 million) to the state budget.</p><p>The court also sentenced five other former officials of Vietnam Social Security to between two and 14 years in prison for the same charges, according to the report. ($1 = 23,200 dong) (Reporting by Khanh Vu; Editing by Toby Chopra)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>