<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4c7fe617-fd26-436a-9c6e-a0b952d9e5c8" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T074431Z:TX-PAR-EJG12:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T074431Z:TX-PAR-EJG12:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T074431Z-TX-PAR-EJG12.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>cricket</item><item>IND</item><item>betting</item><item>corruption</item><item>Ajit Singh</item><item>Singh</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>India extends cricket match-fixing crackdown</title><authors></authors><summary>India's cricket board has extended a match-fixing crackdown to regional leagues after the arrest of a team owner for making illegal bets with a Dubai-based bookie, officials said Wednesday.Ashfaq Ali Thara, owner of a team in the Karnataka Premier League -- a state-level Twenty20 competition -- was arrested in Bangalore on Tuesday, police said. Thara, who also owns a team in the Dubai T10 League, is under investigation for placing bets with a Dubai bookie, and is also being quizzed over a...</summary><city>New Delhi</city><country>IND</country><xmlText><p>India's cricket board has extended a match-fixing crackdown to regional leagues after the arrest of a team owner for making illegal bets with a Dubai-based bookie, officials said Wednesday.</p><p>Ashfaq Ali Thara, owner of a team in the Karnataka Premier League -- a state-level Twenty20 competition -- was arrested in Bangalore on Tuesday, police said. </p><p>Thara, who also owns a team in the Dubai T10 League, is under investigation for placing bets with a Dubai bookie, and is also being quizzed over a possible role in fixing matches.</p><p>"He has been arrested for betting and they are investigating other aspects," Ajit Singh, chief of the anti-corruption unit of the Board of Control for Cricket in India, told AFP.</p><p>The incident comes a week after the unit launched an inquiry into to an approach by suspected match fixers to players in this years Tamil Nadu Premier League.</p><p>A member of the Indian women's team was also approached by a bookie, and two suspects handed over to Karnataka police.</p><p>Singh, a former director-general of police, said there is now a greater focus on state-level leagues.</p><p>"The vigilance and awareness have increased and people are coming forward with it," he said.</p><p>"We have been conducting education classes for the players. We have been in touch with the associations also."</p><p>Gambling in India is illegal except in lotteries or horse racing, but thousands of bets are placed with illegal bookmakers at home and abroad on all aspects of cricket -- from the result to the number of runs in a specific over.</p><p>There is also no law to check online gambling that is making its way in to the Indian sports market, including cricket.</p><p>The Indian Premier League, the world's wealthiest national league, was hit by a spot-fixing scandal in 2013 which resulted in two-year bans on two teams.</p><p>Many Twenty20 leagues -- including the Pakistan Super League, Bangladesh Premier League and Dubai league -- have had their own fixing scandals which led to bans on players.</p><p>fk/tw/fox</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>