<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9cd748a7-aa2b-4fca-859b-81a417cd13ac" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0301</summary><sourceId>58a463da-9ef0-4b3d-b3d9-f081ff0a98c6</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6978%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0301</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">DETROIT TIGERS — Agreed to terms with LHP Travis Wood on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA DIAMONDBACKS — Agreed to terms with RHP Neftali Feliz on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO ROCKIES — Agreed to terms with INF Shawn O'Malley and RHP Brooks Pounders on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Placed LHP Nik Turley on the restricted list.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed INFs Nathaniel Maggio and Christian Ibarra.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Released OFs Brian Joynt, Daniel Rockett and Joe Dunigan.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed RHP Williams Durruthy and LHP Alex Demchak.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Named Dean Pees defensive coordinator and Matt LaFleur offensive coordinator.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED — Waived F Jacob Peterson.</p><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS CREW — Traded M Justin Meram to Orlando City SC for a 2019 international roster slot and general and targeted allocation money for the 2018-19 seasons.</p><p xmlns="">FC DALLAS — Loaned D Anibal Chala to LDU Quito (Serie A-Ecuador) for the 2018 season.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK CITY FC — Announced M Jack Harrison signed a contract with Manchester City (Premier League-England) and loaned to Middlesbrough (Championship-England).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">SKY BLUE FC — Traded the No. 1 overall selection in Tuesday's dispersal draft to Washington for the No. 2 overall selection in the dispersal draft and a 2019 conditional first-round draft pick and a second-round draft pick in the college draft.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ST. ANDREWS — Named Brandon Standridge women's soccer coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>