<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TEN-RESULTS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="1ced9b8a-919e-4014-aba9-a1f1dec6c7e0" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</title><summary>BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</summary><sourceId>2db332f4-8032-4446-446a-1e117fd09419</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z3631%-----%r%BC-TEN--Australian Open Results;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">TEN--Australian Open Results</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">MELBOURNE (AP) — Results Sunday from the Australian Open at Melbourne Park (seedings in parentheses):</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Fourth Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Rafael Nadal (1), Spain, def. Diego Schwartzman (24), Argentina, 6-3, 6-7 (4), 6-3, 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Marin Cilic (6), Croatia, def. Pablo Carreno-Busta (10), Spain, 6-7 (2), 6-3, 7-6 (0), 7-6 (3).</p><p xmlns="">Kyle Edmund, Britain, def. Andreas Seppi, Italy, 6-7 (4), 7-5, 6-2, 6-3.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Singles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Fourth Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Elise Mertens, Belgium, def. Petra Martic, Croatia, 7-6 (5), 7-5.</p><p xmlns="">Carla Suarez-Navarro, Spain, def. Anett Kontaveit (32), Estonia, 4-6, 6-4, 8-6.</p><p xmlns="">Caroline Wozniacki (2), Denmark, def. Magdalena Rybarikova (19), Slovakia, 6-3, 6-0.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Men's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Third Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Robert Farah, Colombia and Juan Sebastian Cabal (11), Colombia, def. Leander Paes, India and Purav Raja, India, 6-1, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Lleyton Hewitt, Australia and Sam Groth, Australia, def. Pablo Andujar, Spain and Albert Ramos-Vinolas, Spain, 3-3.</p><p xmlns="">Bob Bryan, United States and Mike Bryan (6), United States, def. Fabrice Martin, France and Jeremy Chardy, France, 6-7 (2), 7-6 (5), 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">Aisam-Ul-Hag Qureshi, Pakistan and Marcin Matkowski (15), Poland, def. Radu Albot, Moldova and Hyeon Chung, Republic of Korea, .</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Third Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Barbora Strycova, Czech Republic and Lucie Safarova (4), Czech Republic, def. Sorana Cirstea, Romania and Beatriz Haddad Maia, Brazil, 2-6, 6-0, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Shuai Peng, China and Su-Wei Hsieh (8), Taiwan, def. Anna-Lena Groenefeld, Germany and Raquel Atawo (12), United States, 6-4, 6-2.</p><p xmlns="">Monica Niculescu, Romania and Irina Begu (10), Romania, def. Anastassia Rodionova, Australia and Nadiia Kichenok, Ukraine, 4-1.</p><p xmlns="">Vania King, United States and Jennifer Brady, United States, def. Kveta Peschke, Czech Republic and Nicole Melichar (13), United States, 6-4, 7-6 (5).</p><hl2 xmlns="">Mixed Doubles</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">First Round</hl2><p xmlns="">Yung-Jan Chan, Taiwan and Jamie Murray, Britain, def. Rajeev Ram, United States and Andreja Klepac, Slovenia, 4-6, 7-5, 11-9.</p><p xmlns="">Michael Venus, New Zealand and Hao-Ching Chan, Taiwan, def. Aisam-Ul-Hag Qureshi, Pakistan and Zhaoxuan Yang, China, 6-3, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Henri Kontinen, Finland and Kveta Peschke, Czech Republic, def. Bradley Mousley, Australia and Zoe Hives, Australia, 6-4, 6-1.</p><p xmlns="">Juan Sebastian Cabal, Colombia and Abigail Spears, United States, def. Fabrice Martin, France and Renata Voracova, Czech Republic, 6-4, 6-7 (4), 10-6.</p><p xmlns="">Rohan Bopanna, India and Timea Babos, Hungary, def. Andrew Whittington, Australia and Ellen Perez, Australia, 6-2, 6-4.</p><p xmlns="">Marcel Granollers, Spain and Nadiia Kichenok, Ukraine, def. Artem Sitak, New Zealand and Olga Savchuk, Ukraine, 7-6 (5), 3-6, 10-7.</p><p xmlns="">Bruno Soares, Brazil and Ekaterina Makarova, Russia, def. Yi-Fan Xu, China and Marcus Daniell, New Zealand, 6-3, 5-7, 10-2.</p><p xmlns="">Casey Dellacqua, Australia and John Peers, Australia, def. Marc Lopez, Spain and Arantxa Parra Santonja, Spain, 6-4, 6-4.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TEN-RESULTS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>