<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ad31ae84-d95e-4688-8900-33211295962b" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDXD7T0AFB6:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDXD7T0AFB6:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDXD7T0AFB600000_DNMLENf-20190925110955.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Italy Is Said to Propose Fabio Panetta for ECB Executive Board</title><authors>Alessandro Speciale and John Follain</authors><summary>PYDXD7T0AFB6(Bloomberg) -- Italy has proposed veteran central banker Fabio Panetta as its candidate to replace Benoit Coeure on the European Central Bank’s Executive Board, according to a government official familiar with the matter.The Italian finance ministry sent Panetta’s candidacy to Mario Centeno, who leads the group of euro-area finance chiefs that will decide who joins the six-member board, the senior official said, asking not to be named because the nomination isn’t yet public. The...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Italy has proposed veteran central banker Fabio Panetta as its candidate to replace Benoit Coeure on the European Central Bank’s Executive Board, according to a government official familiar with the matter.</p><p>The Italian finance ministry sent Panetta’s candidacy to Mario Centeno, who leads the group of euro-area finance chiefs that will decide who joins the six-member board, the senior official said, asking not to be named because the nomination isn’t yet public. The informal deadline for submitting candidates is Wednesday, with a decision by the bloc’s finance ministers expected for Oct. 10.</p><p>Winning the board slot would restore Italy’s seat on the ECB’s powerful body for designing and implementing euro-area monetary policy, as the institution pumps up stimulus to boost growth and inflation in the bloc. The nation will be without such a post for the first time when President Mario Draghi steps down on Oct. 31.</p><p>French national Coeure’s term ends on Dec. 31, and tradition dictates that another country will be awarded the role because Draghi’s successor, Christine Lagarde, is French.</p><p>A spokeswoman for the Bank of Italy declined to comment.</p><p>Panetta, 60, is currently director general of Bank of Italy. He has been critical of the way Europe has treated the country’s troubled lenders, and as a member the ECB’s Supervisory Board has taken part in overseeing a string of crises at his country’s banks from Banca Monte dei Paschi di Siena SpA to Banca Carige SpA.</p><p>He holds a PhD in Economics and Finance and has been at Bank of Italy since 1985.</p><p>--With assistance from Nicholas Comfort and Viktoria Dendrinou.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Alessandro Speciale in Rome at aspeciale@bloomberg.net;John Follain in Rome at jfollain2@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Chad Thomas at cthomas16@bloomberg.net, Paul Gordon, Karl Maier</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>