<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="fb6bff70-98ae-30d7-86c7-f6a061ad544e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Joe Giglio</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKC-UNC-NIKE:RA — sports (450 words)</title><summary>The University of North Carolina is closing in on a contract extension with Nike, athletic director Bubba Cunningham said on Monday, and it is expected to be finalized next month.The contract extension with the Oregon sneaker giant, which has...</summary><sourceId>275f2582-c986-8dde-dde0-18a2954daf1f</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1669%knihr%r%BC-BKC-UNC-NIKE:RA — sports (450 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">UNC and Nike headed for another contract but don’t expect Ohio State or Texas-type money</h2><byline xmlns="">By Joe Giglio</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">The University of North Carolina is closing in on a contract extension with Nike, athletic director Bubba Cunningham said on Monday, and it is expected to be finalized next month.</p><p xmlns="">The contract extension with the Oregon sneaker giant, which has been UNC’s primary sneaker/uniform/apparel partner since 1994, will likely be another 10-year deal, Cunningham said.</p><p xmlns="">While Ohio State and Texas have each recently received deals with Nike worth more than $250 million, Cunningham did not anticipate UNC’s deal to be in the same financial stratosphere.</p><p xmlns="">“It will be a very good deal but not a blockbuster,” Cunningham said.</p><p xmlns="">UNC’s current deal with Nike, and its Jordan Brand subsidiary, expires in June and is worth about $36.85 million in uniforms, footwear, apparel and cash considerations.</p><p xmlns="">The total compensation does not include the separate contracts Nike has with individual coaches at UNC. The school does not disclose the value of the contracts with individual coaches.</p><p xmlns="">The previous apparel contract, negotiated by former UNC AD Dick Baddour, included $31.6 million (retail value) in products peaking at $3.4 million annually for the last two years of the deal.</p><p xmlns="">“Dick did a great job because his primary focus was to get as much product to the students as possible,” Cunningham said. “We’ll take more product and less cash. I think that’s a very good philosophy.”</p><p xmlns="">Nike paid UNC $1 million in cash considerations, up front when the deal was signed in 2008, and then another $2.25 million annually. In addition, Nike made a $2 million payment to the “Chancellor’s Academic Enhancement Fund,” according to the terms of the contract.</p><p xmlns="">Texas agreed to a reported 15-year deal worth $250 million with Nike in 2015 and Ohio State’s deal in 2016, also 15 years, is worth more than $250 million.</p><p xmlns="">The Texas contract included a $20 million cash payment up front and another $6.5 million annually in cash, according to the Texas Tribune.</p><p xmlns="">Ohio State will get $112 million in product from Nike and at least $103 million in cash, according to the Wall Street Journal.</p><p xmlns="">“The big (contract) pops are driven by football or if you step outside and go to another company,” Cunningham said.</p><p xmlns="">The Tar Heels won the national championship in basketball in 2017, their third in a 12-year span, but finished the most recent football season with a 3-9 record and hasn’t won the ACC title since 1980.</p><p xmlns="">Sneaker and apparel deals have taken off in recent years with adidas and Under Armour driving up the market value. UCLA’s 15-year, $280 million deal with Under Armour is reportedly the richest in the NCAA.</p><p xmlns="">Louisville’s 10-year deal with adidas is worth a reported $160 million is the richest among ACC schools.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000008058,t000008056,t000003183,c000212272,g000362661,g000065562,g000066164,g000065579</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>