<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e5b7fead-34db-4dfd-9a9b-3688c2bad014" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV04</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV04,4922</summary><sourceId>ecea7393-19b5-4586-5868-d55e560ba140</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9827%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV04;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV04</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV04,4922</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv04</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend, Feb. 4-5</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 4</hl2><p xmlns="">1861 — The Philadelphia Athletics beat Charter Oak 36-27 in a baseball game played on frozen Litchfield Pond in Brooklyn, N.Y., with the players wearing ice skates.</p><p xmlns="">1924 — The first Winter Olympics close in Chamonix, France. Sixteen countries competed in 17 events from seven sports.</p><p xmlns="">1932 — The Winter Olympics open in Lake Placid, N.Y., the first Winter Games in the United States.</p><p xmlns="">1957 — Joe McCarthy and Sam Crawford are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — The 24 major league owners unanimously select Bowie Kuhn as commissioner for a one-year term at a salary of $100,000.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — The Baseball Hall of Fame establishes a separate section for players from the old Negro Leagues. In July, commissioner Bowie Kuhn, along with Hall president Paul Kirk, announce a change of heart and scrap plans for the separate section.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — U.S. District Court Judge John W. Oliver upholds the ruling of arbitrator Peter Seitz that declared Andy Messersmith and Dave McNally free agents.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Stars &amp; Stripes, skippered by Dennis Conner, sweeps Kookaburra III 4-0 at Fremantle, Australia, to bring sailing's America's Cup back to the United States.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — The doors of Cooperstown are slammed shut on Pete Rose when the Hall of Fame's board of directors votes 12-0 to bar players on the permanently ineligible list from consideration.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Jaromir Jagr scores three goals, including his 500th, for his 11th career hat trick as Washington beat Tampa Bay 5-1.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Peyton Manning is 25-of-38 for 247 yards and a touchdown as he rallies Indianapolis to a 29-17 Super Bowl victory over Chicago in the South Florida rain. Tony Dungy becomes the first black coach to win the championship, beating good friend and protege Lovie Smith in a game that featured the first two black coaches in the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Lindsey Vonn captures her 50th World Cup victory, winning the downhill with temperatures plunging to minus 13 on the demanding Kandahar course in Garmisch-Partenkirchen, Germany.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim gets his 1,000th victory with a 66-62 win over No. 9 Virginia. Officially it's victory No. 899 after the NCAA stripped him of 101 victories as part of punishment handed down in 2015 after a multiyear investigation of the school's athletic department.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Gregg Popovich becomes the winningest coach with a single franchise in NBA history, leading the San Antonio Spurs to a 121-97 victory over the Denver Nuggets. Popovich earns his 1,128th victory to pass former Utah coach Jerry Sloan for the mark.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 5</hl2><p xmlns="">1913 — The New York State Athletic Commission bans boxing matches between fighters of different races.</p><p xmlns="">1919 — Charges against Cincinnati's Hal Chase of throwing games and betting against his team are dismissed by National League president John Heydler. Two weeks later, Chase is traded to the New York Giants.</p><p xmlns="">1948 — After landing the first double axel in Olympic competition, Dick Button becomes the first American to win the Olympic gold medal in figure skating. Gretchen Fraser becomes the first U.S. woman Olympic slalom champion.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Bill Russell grabs 51 rebounds in the Boston Celtics' 124-100 victory over the Syracuse Nationals. Russell is the first player in NBA history to pull in 50-or-more rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Bob Douglas is the first black elected to Basketball Hall of Fame. Known as "The Father of Black Professional Basketball," Douglas owned and coached the New York Renaissance from 1922 until 1949.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Austrian Franz Klammer wins the Olympic gold medal in the downhill at Innsbruck, Austria. Bill Koch wins a silver in the 30-kilometer cross-country race to become the first American to win a medal in a Nordic event.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Notre Dame bucks the College Football Association and becomes the first college to sell its home games to a major network, agreeing to a five-year contract with NBC beginning in 1991.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Dave Taylor of the Los Angeles Kings has two assists in a 3-2 win over the Philadelphia Flyers to become the 29th player in NHL history with 1,000 points.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Peter Bondra becomes the 10th player in NHL history to score four goals in one period, then adds another in the second period as the Washington Capitals beat Tampa Bay 6-3.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Al Scates becomes the first men's volleyball coach to reach 1,000 wins as UCLA beat Pepperdine 3-1.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Bob Knight wins his 800th game, becoming the fourth Division I men's coach to reach the mark in guiding Texas Tech past Nebraska 75-49.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Bode Miller of the United States captures his first major title, winning the gold medal in the combined at the world championships in St. Moritz, Switzerland.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Pittsburgh wins a record-tying fifth Super Bowl, but its first since 1980 with a 21-10 win over the Seattle Seahawks.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Tennessee's Pat Summitt becomes the first Division I basketball coach — man or woman — to win 1,000 career games after her Lady Vols beat Georgia 73-43.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Dejen Gebremeskel of Ethiopia wins the men's 3,000 at the Boston Indoor Grand Prix, after losing his right shoe at the start of the race. Gebremeskel stays close to the lead throughout the race and takes over on the final lap to finish in 7:35.37. Britain's Mo Farah finishes second in 7:35.81.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Eli Manning and the Giants one-up Tom Brady and the Patriots again, coming back with a last-minute score to beat New England 21-17 for New York's fourth Super Bowl title.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Tom Brady leads one of the greatest comebacks in sports, let alone Super Bowl history, lifting New England from a 25-point hole to the Patriots' fifth NFL championship in the game's first overtime finish. The Patriots score 19 points in the final quarter, including a pair of 2-point conversions, then marches relentlessly to James White's 2-yard touchdown run in overtime beating the Atlanta Falcons 34-28.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 6</hl2><p xmlns="">1943 — Montreal's Ray Getliffe scores five goals to lead the Canadiens to an 8-3 triumph over the Boston Bruins.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Ted Williams signs a contract with the Boston Red Sox for $135,000, making him the highest paid player in major league history.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Muhammad Ali successfully defends his world heavyweight title with a 15-round decision over Ernest Terrell in the Houston Astrodome.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — The NBA expands to 18 teams with the addition of franchises in Buffalo, Cleveland, Houston and Portland.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — The West beat the East, 123-111, in the ABA All-Star Game held in Salt Lake City. Willie Wise of the Utah Stars leads all scorers with 26.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Seventeen-year-old Dianne Roffe becomes the first U.S. woman to win a gold medal in a World Alpine Ski Championship race, capturing the giant slalom in 2:18.53.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Brett Hull of the St. Louis Blues scores his 50th goal, making him and his Hall of Famer father, Bobby Hull, the only father-son combination in NHL history to reach that milestone.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Randy Moss sets records with nine catches for 212 yards, and Mike Alstott scores three touchdowns in the NFC's 51-31 victory over the AFC, the highest-scoring Pro Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Pavel Bure records the 11th hat trick in All-Star history and goalie Olaf Kolzig plays a shutout third period as the World team routs North America 9-4 in the NHL's 50th All-Star game.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — The New England Patriots win their third Super Bowl in four years, 24-21 over the Philadelphia Eagles. It's their ninth straight postseason victory, equaling Vince Lombardi's Green Bay Packers.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — New England Patriots quarterback Tom Brady becomes the first unanimous choice for The Associated Press NFL Most Valuable Player Award. Brady gets all 50 votes since the AP began using a nationwide panel of media members who cover the league.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Aaron Rodgers throws three touchdown passes and Nick Collins returns an interception for another score, leading the Green Bay Packers to a 31-25 victory over the Pittsburgh Steelers in the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Germany's Tobias Wendl and Tobias Arlt claim the record for the most Luge World Cup doubles wins in history. The Olympic champions clock a combined time of 1:40.368 to move onto 35 wins, one more than compatriots Patric Leitner and Alexander Resch, who retired in 2010.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 7</hl2><p xmlns="">1882 — John L. Sullivan wins the world heavyweight bare-knuckle title by beating Paddy Ryan in a nine-round bout in Mississippi City, Miss.</p><p xmlns="">1942 — At the Millrose Games in New York, Dutch Warmerdam becomes the first man to clear 15 feet in the pole vault indoors. Warmerdam, the first to break the 15-foot mark outdoors in 1940, clears 15 feet 3/8 inch.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Joe DiMaggio signs his contract with the New York Yankees, making him the first baseball player to earn $100,000 per year.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Diana Crump becomes the first female jockey to race at a U.S. pari-mutuel track. She rode her first mount to 10th place in a field of 12 in Hialeah, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Rick Barry of the Oakland Oaks sets an ABA and professional basketball record by going 23-for-23 from the free throw line as Oakland beats the Kentucky Colonels 124-122 in overtime.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Pete Maravich scores 69 points, including 47 in the second half, to set a NCAA record, but LSU loses to Alabama 106-104.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Darryl Sittler of the Toronto Maple Leafs sets an NHL record for points in a game with six goals and four assists in an 11-4 victory over the Boston Bruins.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Michael Jordan follows his NBA slam-dunk title with a Most Valuable Player performance in the All-Star game, scoring 40 points as the East defeated the West 138-133.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Joe Mullen becomes the first American-born player to reach 1,000 points in the NHL when he assists on two of the Pittsburgh Penguins' first three goals in a 7-3 victory over Florida.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Drew Brees and the New Orleans Saints rally to beat Peyton Manning and the Indianapolis Colts 31-17 in the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — The surging Dallas Mavericks beat the Cleveland Cavaliers 99-96, making it 25 straight losses for the Cavs. Cleveland, already the record holder for the most losses in a single season, now owns the record for losses spread over two seasons.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Tyler Griffey makes an uncontested layup at the buzzer off a baseline inbound pass and Illinois beats No. 1 Indiana 74-72, the fifth straight week the nation's top-ranked team loses. The Hoosiers took over the top spot in The Associated Press' Top 25 on Feb. 4. The run of No. 1 teams to lose has been Duke, Louisville, Duke again, Michigan and Indiana.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Philadelphia University coach Herb Magee becomes the second NCAA men's basketball coach to win 1,000 games. Magee, who won 1,000 games over 48 seasons at the school, hits the milestone with the Rams' 80-60 win over Post.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Von Miller forces two fumbles to set up Denver's two touchdowns and the Broncos defense frustrates Cam Newton all game to carry Peyton Manning to his second Super Bowl title with a 24-10 victory over the Carolina Panthers.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Rachel Banham ties an NCAA women's record with 60 points — with 10 coming in the first overtime and eight in the second — to lead Minnesota to a 112-106 win over Northwestern. Banham matches the 60 points put up by Cindy Brown of Long Beach State in 1987.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 8</hl2><p xmlns="">1936 — Jay Berwanger, University of Chicago halfback and Heisman Trophy winner, is the first player ever selected in the NFL Draft. The Philadelphia Eagles make the pick and eventually trade his rights to the Chicago Bears.</p><p xmlns="">1950 — Man o' War is selected the greatest horse of the half century by The Associated Press. Man o' War, as a 2- and 3-year-old, is a winner in 20 of 21 races and holds five track records.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Philadelphia Warriors scores 59 points in a 136-120 victory over the New York Knicks and beats his own single-season scoring record of 3,033 by six points.</p><p xmlns="">1964 — Billy Kidd and James Heuga win the first men's Olympic Alpine skiing medals for the United States with a silver and bronze in the slalom.</p><p xmlns="">1975 — The New Orleans Jazz get their first road win in franchise history, ending a 28 game road losing streak. The Jazz beat the Hawks in Atlanta 106-102 to improve their record to 7-44.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Seattle's Tom Chambers, a last-minute replacement for the injured Ralph Sampson, scores a game-high 34 points to lead the West to a 154-149 overtime win over the East in the NBA All-Star Game before 34,275 at the Kingdome.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Charles Barkley becomes the 22nd NBA player to reach 20,000 points, scoring 30 in the Phoenix Suns' 107-102 victory over New Jersey.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Scotty Bowman becomes the first NHL coach to win 1,000 games as Detroit beats Pittsburgh 6-5 on Brendan Shanahan's overtime goal. Bowman, the coach of six Stanley Cup champion teams, is 1,000-452-255 in regular-season games and 162-101 in the playoffs.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Mario Lemieux becomes the 10th player in NHL history to reach 1,000 career assists. He has four in Pittsburgh' 5-2 victory in Boston.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — At the Sochi Games, Norway's Ole Einar Bjoerndalen becomes the oldest Winter Olympic gold medalist at 40 and ties Bjoern Daehlie's record for most medals (12) won at the Winter Games. Bjoerndalen wins the men's 10-kilometer biathlon sprint, breaking the record held by Canadian skeleton racer Duff Gibson, who was 39 when he won gold at the 2006 Turin Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Wichita State beats Northern Iowa 82-73 to become the first men's team to open 25-0 since Derrick Rose helped Memphis win its first 26 games in 2007-08.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Breanna Stewart has 25 points and 10 rebounds as No. 1 UConn again proves who rules the women's game, running past No. 2 South Carolina 66-54.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 9</hl2><p xmlns="">1912 — The U.S. Tennis Association amends the rules for the men's singles championship play. The defending champion is required to play through the tournament instead of waiting for the tournament to produce a challenger.</p><p xmlns="">1940 — Joe Louis beats Arturo Godoy with a split decision to defend his world heavyweight title at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — The NHL doubles in size — from six to 12 teams — when the Owners-Governors award franchises to Los Angeles, Minneapolis-St. Paul, Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, San Francisco and St. Louis.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — Detroit's Isiah Thomas scores 30 points and hands out 10 assists to lead the East to a 139-132 win in the All-Star Game in Dallas.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Mario Lemieux of the Pittsburgh Penguins scores a record six points — three goals and three assists — to lead the Wales Conference to a 6-5 victory over the Campbell Conference in the NHL All-Star game.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Terry Norris knocks down Sugar Ray Leonard twice and beats him up over 12 rounds in Leonard's Madison Square Garden debut and final fight. Norris wins a unanimous decision.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Magic Johnson, playing for the first time since announcing his retirement on Nov. 7, scores a game-high 25 points and hands out nine assists to lead the West to a 153-113 win over the East in the NBA All-Star Game at the Orlando Arena.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Glen Rice breaks two scoring records in an MVP performance and Michael Jordan has the first triple-double in NBA All-Star game history. The East rallies to beat the West 132-120. Rice, who finishes with 26 points, sets records with 20 in the third quarter and 24 in the second half.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Kevin Garnett, the MVP, scores nine of his 37 points in the second overtime as the West beat the East 155-145 in the first double overtime game in NBA All-Star history.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Lindsey Vonn wins the downhill for her second gold at the World Championships in Val D'isere, France. Vonn becomes the second American woman to win two golds at a worlds. Andrea Mead Lawrence won the slalom and giant slalom at the 1952 Oslo Olympics, which doubled as the worlds.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — The Cleveland Cavaliers' losing streak reaches 26, matching the 1976-77 NFL Tampa Bay Buccaneers' record for consecutive incompetence with a 103-94 loss to the Detroit Pistons.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Missouri All-American defensive end Michael Sam comes out to the nation. In interviews with ESPN, The New York Times and Outsports, Sam says he came out to all his teammates and coaches at Missouri in August.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — San Antonio rallies from a 14-point fourth-quarter deficit and gets an 18-foot baseline jumper from Marco Belinelli with 2.1 seconds left to give coach Greg Popovich 1,000 wins with a 95-93 victory at Indiana.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Kaleena Mosqueda-Lewis scores 23 points and Breanna Stewart adds 22 to help No. 2 UConn beat top-ranked South Carolina 87-62. This is the 54th meeting between the top two women's teams in the nation, and the 20th time that the Huskies are involved in that matchup. They are 17-3 in those games.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 10</hl2><p xmlns="">1908 — Tommy Burns knocks out Jack Palmer in the fourth round to defend his world heavyweight title in London.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Joe Fulks of Philadelphia scores 63 points in a 108-87 win over Indianapolis to set an NBA scoring record which would last for nearly a decade.</p><p xmlns="">1952 — The Baltimore Bullets play the 48-minute game without making a single substitution and beat the Fort Wayne Pistons 82-77.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Jim Beatty becomes the first American to break the 4-minute mile indoors with a 3:58.9 in Los Angeles.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Peggy Fleming wins the women's Olympic figure skating gold medal in Grenoble, France.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — LSU's Pete Maravich scores 66 points in a 110-94 loss to Tulane.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Former first baseman Bill White becomes the first black announcer in major baseball league history, signing to join the New York Yankees WPIX broadcast team.</p><p xmlns="">1989 — K.C. Jones of the Boston Celtics and Lenny Wilkens of the Cleveland Cavaliers are elected to the Basketball Hall of Fame. Also elected is William "Pop" Gates, who played during the game's barnstorming years in the 1930s and 1940s.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Charles Barkley of the Philadelphia 76ers, playing with a stress fracture in his left foot, becomes the NBA All-Star MVP with 17 points and 22 rebounds after leading the East to a 116-114 victory.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Bonnie Blair becomes the first woman to successfully defend an Olympic gold medal in 500-meter speed skating and the first American woman in any sport to win gold medals in consecutive Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Picabo Street, Alpine skiing's comeback kid, overcomes a mistake about midway through her run and charges to an Olympic gold by one-hundredth of a second in the women's super-G — the games' first Alpine medal after three days of snow-related postponements.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Detroit's Brett Hull becomes the sixth NHL player to score 700 regular-season goals. Hull beats San Jose's Evgeni Nabokov with a wrist shot in a 5-4 win over the Sharks.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Jaromir Jagr has three assists in the New York Rangers' 5-2 win over Washington and becomes the 12th player in NHL history to score 1,500 points.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Tomas Plekanec scores his second goal of the game in overtime and the Montreal Canadiens end Washington's team-record winning streak at 14 games with a 6-5 victory.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Golden State storms into the All-Star break on an 11-game winning streak with a 112-104 victory over Phoenix. At 48-4, the Warriors have the best record through 52 games in NBA history, one win better than the 1995-96 Chicago Bulls and 1966-67 Philadelphia 76ers.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Golden State's Draymond Green becomes the first player in NBA history to record a triple-double with fewer than 10 points scored. Green had 12 rebounds, 10 assists, 10 steals and 4 points in a 122-107 win over Memphis. Green also had five blocks, which made him the first player to record 10 steals and five blocks in a game since steals and blocks were first tracked in 1973-74.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 11</hl2><p xmlns="">1878 — The Boston Bicycle Club, the first bicycle club in the United States, is formed.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Willie Pep becomes the first boxer in the history of the 126-pound class to regain a lost championship with a 15-round unanimous decision over Sandy Saddler at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1957 — The NHL Players Association is formed and Ted Lindsay of the Detroit Red Wings is elected president.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — The Atlanta Hawks score 97 points, the most ever scored in the second half of an NBA game, en route to a 155-131 win at San Diego.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Montreal's Jean Beliveau scores his 500th goal in the Canadiens' 6-2 victory over the Minnesota North Stars. '1973 — The Philadelphia 76ers lose to the Los Angeles Lakers 108-90 to set an NBA record for the most consecutive losses in a season at 20.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Houston Rockets center Moses Malone grabs an NBA-record 21 offensive rebounds in a 117-100 win over Seattle.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Mike Tyson loses for the first time when James "Buster" Douglas knocks him out in the 10th round and captures the heavyweight championship in one of the biggest upsets in boxing history.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Anfissa Reztsova wins the women's 7.5-kilometer biathlon event to become the first woman to get gold medals in two different Winter Olympic sports. She skied the final 5-kilometer leg on the Soviet Union's winning 20K cross-country relay team in the 1988 Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — In the first period of a 2-2 tie between Pittsburgh and Edmonton, Martin Straka of the Penguins scores twice in seven seconds. The NHL record for quickest goals is five seconds.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Allen Iverson and Stephon Marbury lead an improbable comeback to give the Eastern Conference a thrilling 111-110 NBA All-Star victory. Iverson scores 15 of his 25 points in the final nine minutes, and Marbury hits two 3-pointers in the final 53 seconds to help the East come back from a 21-point deficit.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Anja Paerson captures the downhill, becoming the first skier to win gold medals in all five disciplines at the world championships. Paerson, who also won the super-G and combined titles earlier in the week, won gold medals in the giant slalom at the last two worlds and one in the slalom in 2001.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — The Cleveland Cavaliers stopped their NBA-record losing streak at 26 games with a 126-119 win in overtime against the Los Angeles Clippers. Antawn Jamison scores 35 points and makes the game's biggest basket, a 3-pointer with 22 seconds left in OT for the Cavs.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Henrik Lundqvist makes 32 saves for his 400th career win and the New York Rangers earned their fifth consecutive victory, beating the Colorado Avalanche 4-2.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>