<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f125f4ff-f1e5-4f50-a027-dda5d98fd30a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):11:45 a.m.Stocks are broadly lower in midday trading on Wall Street, led by declines in technology companies.Apple slid 1.4 percent Monday as investors continued to...</summary><sourceId>f6b64dc3-1fb6-4590-590b-70362a877e88</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:EEE3730%-----%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: Technology leads US stocks lower</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are broadly lower in midday trading on Wall Street, led by declines in technology companies.</p><p xmlns="">Apple slid 1.4 percent Monday as investors continued to worry that its new iPhone hasn't been that big of a hit with customers.</p><p xmlns="">Industrials companies also posted big losses. Caterpillar gave up 2 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Energy stocks declined as crude oil prices headed lower. Chesapeake Energy fell 2.9 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Dr. Pepper Snapple soared 24 percent after agreeing to be acquired by Keurig.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 8 points, or 0.3 percent, to 2,864.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average slid 64 points, or 0.2 percent, to 26,551. The Nasdaq composite lost 18 points, or 0.3 percent, to 7,486.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.72 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">The major U.S. stock indexes are down slightly in early trading Monday, as losses in technology companies outweighed gains elsewhere.</p><p xmlns="">Dr. Pepper Snapple Group jumped 29 percent in the first few minutes of trading after it agreed to be acquired by Keurig in a deal that would create a beverage giant with about $11 billion in annual sales.</p><p xmlns="">The Commerce Department said that consumer spending rose 0.4 percent in December, a solid pace but slower than the big increase in November.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 7 points, or 0.3 percent, to 2,865.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average slid 34 points, or 0.1 percent, to 26,582. The Nasdaq composite lost 27 points, or 0.4 percent, to 7,478.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.69 percent.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>