<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="688336b0-c7b8-40d9-ac5b-8892a09c6fe4" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDLZHT1UM13:3</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDLZHT1UM13:3</followId><sourceFileName>PYDLZHT1UM1300000_DNMLENf-20190925070909.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Costs Rise Again for U.K. Hinkley Point Nuclear Project</title><authors>Francois de Beaupuy</authors><summary>PYDLZHT1UM13(Bloomberg) -- Electricite de France SA raised the estimated cost of the Hinkley Point C nuclear reactors it’s building in the U.K. by as much as 2.9 billion pounds ($3.6 billion), and said there’s a higher risk of a delay to their completion. The shares slumped.It’s yet another setback for Britain’s plan to have nuclear power play a big part in reducing carbon emissions. The Hinkley Point C units, the country’s first new reactors in decades, had already been heavily criticized...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Electricite de France SA raised the estimated cost of the Hinkley Point C nuclear reactors it’s building in the U.K. by as much as 2.9 billion pounds ($3.6 billion), and said there’s a higher risk of a delay to their completion. The shares slumped.</p><p>It’s yet another setback for Britain’s plan to have nuclear power play a big part in reducing carbon emissions. The Hinkley Point C units, the country’s first new reactors in decades, had already been heavily criticized for their high cost to consumers.</p><p>The announcement also adds to EDF’s woes at home, where a power plant using the same design as Hinkley is years behind schedule and way over budget.</p><p>The project completion cost at Hinkley Point C is now estimated at between 21.5 billion and 22.5 billion pounds, the company said Wednesday in a statement. </p><p>“Cost increases reflect challenging ground conditions which made earthworks more expensive than anticipated, revised action-plan targets and extra costs needed to implement the completed functional design,” EDF said.</p><p>The company’s shares tumbled as much as 6%, the most in two weeks, and traded down 5% at 10.17 euros as of 9:28 a.m. in Paris.</p><p>(Updates with shares in first and final paragraphs)</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Francois de Beaupuy in Paris at fdebeaupuy@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: James Herron at jherron9@bloomberg.net, Amanda Jordan</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>