<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f845aac4-c9cf-4b91-baf9-4b209781ff33" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G23V:1555876568</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G23V:1555876568</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T104531Z_1555876568_L5N26G23V_RTRMADT_0_DANSKE-BANK-ESTONIA-UPDATE-1.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UPDATE 1-Former Danske Bank Estonian head found dead by police</title><summary>DANSKE BANK-ESTONIA/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Former Danske Bank Estonian head found dead by police</summary><xmlText><p>UPDATE 1-Former Danske Bank Estonian head found dead by police</p><p>(Adds details, background, quotes)</p><p>By Tarmo Virki</p><p>TALLINN, Sept 25 (Reuters) - A former head of Danske Bank's Estonian branch, who was a witness in an investigation into alleged money laundering, has been found dead by police in Estonia.</p><p>Danske Bank is under investigation in several countries, including the United States, Denmark, Britain and Estonia, over suspicious payments totalling 200 billion euros ($220 billion) moved through its tiny Estonian branch between 2007 and 2015.</p><p>Police in Estonia had been searching since Monday for Aivar Rehe, who ran Danske Bank's Estonian business during this period. They said he had not been seen since he left his home in Tallinn, Estonia's capital.</p><p>"There are no signs of violence on the corpse, and there is no indication of an accident ... There will be no investigation opened," police said in a statement on Wednesday. Rehe's body had been found near his home, they added.</p><p>A spokeswoman for Estonian prosecutor's office said Rehe was a witness, not a suspect, in a case opened in December 2018 against 10 former Danske Bank employees which involved alleged money laundering of around 300 million euros. ($1 = 0.9093 euros) (Reporting by Tarmo Virki; writing by Stine Jacobsen and Alexander Smith; Editing by Jon Boyle)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>