<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="7cbe87f7-3329-4adf-b349-3b73fcd3a104" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_FLM5knN6:1774609342</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_FLM5knN6:1774609342</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T085048Z_1774609342_FLM5KNN6_RTRMADT_0_BASEBALL-MLB-STL-ARI-RECAP.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>D-backs push past Cards in 19-inning marathon</title><summary>BASEBALL-MLB-STL-ARI: </summary><xmlText><p>D-backs push past Cards in 19-inning marathon</p><p>Ildemaro Vargas lined a walk-off single with two outs in the 19th inning to give the Arizona Diamondbacks a 3-2 victory over the St. Louis Cardinals on Tuesday night in Phoenix, breaking the Cardinals' six-game winning streak in the longest game Arizona franchise history.</p><p>Carson Kelly singled to open the 19th off John Brebbia (3-4), and Nick Ahmed singled Kelly to second. Christian Walker was intentionally walked to load the bases with two outs before Vargas lined a single to left field, his fourth hit of the game.</p><p>Kevin Ginkel (3-0) pitched the top of the 19th for the victory in a game that lasted 6 hours, 53 minutes, the longest in Chase Field history. The Diamondbacks used 30 players and 13 pitchers, both franchise records.</p><p>The Cardinals employed 24 players, including 11 pitchers, as their lead over the Milwaukee Brewers in the National League Central was trimmed to 2 1/2 games with four to play.</p><p>Dexter Fowler homered on the fourth pitch of the game, and St. Louis right-hander Jack Flaherty made that stand up through seven shutout innings of one-hit ball. Vargas' one-out homer off Andrew Miller in the last of the ninth inning tied it at 1.</p><p>The Cardinals took a 2-1 lead on Paul Goldschmidt's one-out homer in 13th inning, his 33rd of the season and second in as many games in his return to Arizona. Caleb Joseph tied the game with a pinch-hit single in the bottom of the inning, following an Ahmed leadoff triple.</p><p>St. Louis' Junior Fernandez pitched out of a two-on, no-out situation to send the game to the 14th.</p><p>Goldschmidt, Tommy Edman, Yadier Molina and Harrison Bader had two hits apiece for the Cardinals (90-68).</p><p>Flaherty had a no-hitter through six innings before Eduardo Escobar led off the seventh with a sharp single that took an abnormal hop after hitting the lip of artificial surface near first base.</p><p>Flaherty, who struck out 11 and walked two, has given up seven earned runs in his past 75 innings, an 0.84 ERA. In 14 starts since the All-Star break, he has an 0.97 ERA. Flaherty has made 12 starts this season in which he has given up two earned runs or fewer and wound up with either a no-decision or a loss.</p><p>--Field Level Media</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>