<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="96d0da79-3693-45f5-96f1-c50b3e96fd61" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOXYT0G1LE:4</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDOXYT0G1LE:4</followId><sourceFileName>PYDOXYT0G1LE00000_DNMLENf-20190925080975.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Costs Rise Again for U.K. Hinkley Point Nuclear Project</title><authors>Francois de Beaupuy</authors><summary>PYDOXYT0G1LE(Bloomberg) -- Electricite de France SA raised the estimated cost of two reactors it’s building in the U.K., making Britain’s nuclear ambitions look increasingly untenable as renewables become ever cheaper to develop.EDF said the bill for the Hinkley Point C reactors could rise by as much as 2.9 billion pounds ($3.6 billion), and warned of a delay to their completion. The project is now strikingly expensive compared with U.K. wind, for example, where power from the latest...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Electricite de France SA raised the estimated cost of two reactors it’s building in the U.K., making Britain’s nuclear ambitions look increasingly untenable as renewables become ever cheaper to develop.</p><p>EDF said the bill for the Hinkley Point C reactors could rise by as much as 2.9 billion pounds ($3.6 billion), and warned of a delay to their completion. The project is now strikingly expensive compared with U.K. wind, for example, where power from the latest offshore auction sold at less than half that from Hinkley.</p><p>Britain wants new nuclear to play a big part in reducing emissions as aging atomic plants are retired in the coming years. But EDF’s two Hinkley units, the country’s first new reactors in decades, had already been heavily criticized for their high cost to consumers. The latest setback comes after another U.K. nuclear venture -- the Wylfa project in Wales -- was scrapped by Hitachi Ltd. in January despite a generous package of support from the government.</p><p>The project completion cost at Hinkley Point C is now estimated at 21.5 billion to 22.5 billion pounds, EDF said Wednesday in a statement, citing “challenging ground conditions” among other extra expenses. The revision won’t have an impact on U.K. consumers or taxpayers, it said.</p><p>The company’s shares tumbled as much as 6.9%, the most in two weeks, and traded down 6.5% at 10.01 euros as of 10:39 a.m. in Paris.</p><p>“The cost overruns are material versus the EDF market cap,” RBC analysts said in a note. “This is likely to further boost support for renewables, and especially scaleable offshore wind, as the main decarbonization solution for electricity generation.”</p><p>Cheaper Wind</p><p>The Hinkley plant will sell power for 92.50 pounds a megawatt-hour when it starts, a rate significantly higher than the 39.65-pound price from the latest round of offshore wind projects.</p><p>The announcement also adds to EDF’s woes at home, where a power plant using the same design as Hinkley is years behind schedule and way over budget. French President Emmanuel Macron has asked EDF to prove that it can build new nuclear power stations at lower cost amid falling renewable-energy prices.</p><p>Yet EDF also cut its estimated rate of return from the Hinkley project on Wednesday, to between 7.6% and 7.8%. That’s down from 8.5% seen two years ago.</p><p>The company said it still hopes to begin generating power from the first unit at the end of 2025, though the risk of a 15-month delay for that reactor -- and a nine-month delay for the second -- has increased. If that risk were to materialize, it would entail an additional cost of about 700 million pounds, it said.</p><p>In a separate message to employees, EDF’s U.K. management said Wednesday’s announcement has no direct impact on its project to build a similar plant at Sizewell on England’s east coast, insisting that the site will benefit from the experience gained at Hinkley and will be cheaper to finance as a “follow-on copy.” It also said nuclear is the only proven technology that can supply a large amount of low-carbon electricity to supplement intermittent renewables.</p><p>--With assistance from Jeremy Hodges.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Francois de Beaupuy in Paris at fdebeaupuy@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: James Herron at jherron9@bloomberg.net, Amanda Jordan</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>