<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6fabcfee-9644-4906-b2f1-57010c808c0e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By The Associated Press</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4 p.m.Stocks are closing slightly lower on Wall Street, pulling the market below the record highs it set the day before.Losses in industrial and energy stocks contributed the most...</summary><sourceId>fdc41336-6f3e-4663-663a-bc70bbf28baf</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:EEE1484%-----%u%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: Stock indexes pull back below records</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates with close of US trading.</p><byline xmlns="">By The Associated Press</byline><p /><p xmlns="">The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are closing slightly lower on Wall Street, pulling the market below the record highs it set the day before.</p><p xmlns="">Losses in industrial and energy stocks contributed the most to the modest declines on Thursday. Boeing lost 3.1 percent while Kinder Morgan fell 2.9 percent.</p><p xmlns="">La Quinta rose 3.8 percent after Wyndham Worldwide agreed to buy its hotel franchise and management business. Wyndham gained 4.8 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 4 points, or 0.2 percent, to 2,798.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average gave up 97 points, or 0.4 percent, to 26,017. The Nasdaq composite fell 2 points, less than 0.1 percent, to 7,296.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.62 percent. That's the highest level for the benchmark yield since March.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are moving lower in midday trading, pulling the market back from the record highs it set the day before.</p><p xmlns="">Losses in health care, industrial and other sectors were outweighing gains by phone and technology companies Thursday. Energy stocks also fell.</p><p xmlns="">Boeing lost 2.9 percent and Merck gave up 2.2 percent.</p><p xmlns="">La Quinta rose 3.4 percent after Wyndham Worldwide agreed to buy its hotel franchise and management business.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 8 points, or 0.3 percent, to 2,794.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average gave up 134 points, or 0.5 percent, to 25,976. The Nasdaq composite fell 11 points, or 0.2 percent, to 7,286.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.61 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stock indexes are wavering between small gains and losses in early trading on Wall Street as gains for technology companies are offset by losses in energy and other sectors.</p><p xmlns="">Some banks were higher early Thursday after reporting earnings that were better than analysts were expecting. Morgan Stanley rose 1 percent and BB&amp;T gained 3.2 percent.</p><p xmlns="">La Quinta rose 4.5 percent after Wyndham Worldwide agreed to buy its hotel franchise and management business.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index was up 1 point at 2,804.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average was little changed at 26,123. The Nasdaq composite edged up 3 points, less than 0.1 percent, to 7,302.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.61 percent.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>