<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0974d696-ce45-40fe-9486-f18bc6d7fac9" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T074706Z:TX-PAR-EJG19:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T074706Z:TX-PAR-EJG19:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T074706Z-TX-PAR-EJG19.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>France</item><item>immigration</item><item>politics</item><item>Macron</item><item>Emmanuel Macron</item><item>Marine Le Pen</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>'France can't host everyone,' says Macron in new toughening of migration stance</title><authors></authors><summary>French President Emmanuel Macron on Wednesday said France "cannot host everyone", intensifying his tough rhetoric on immigration.Macron had last week signalled a tougher line on immigration in the second half of his mandate, arguing the government must stop voters drifting to the far-right."France cannot host everyone if it wants to host people well," Macron told Europe 1 in an interview from the United Nations in New York where he is attending the annual General Assembly.Macron noted France...</summary><city>Paris</city><country>FRA</country><xmlText><p>French President Emmanuel Macron on Wednesday said France "cannot host everyone", intensifying his tough rhetoric on immigration.</p><p>Macron had last week signalled a tougher line on immigration in the second half of his mandate, arguing the government must stop voters drifting to the far-right.</p><p>"France cannot host everyone if it wants to host people well," Macron told Europe 1 in an interview from the United Nations in New York where he is attending the annual General Assembly.</p><p>Macron noted France had seen a sharp increase in the numbers of people asking for asylum since the 2017 presidential election and said much tighter European cooperation was needed.</p><p>"There is not enough cooperation in Europe and we need to look at this migratory phenomenon and take decisions," he said.</p><p>Macron's comments come as the French parliament is set next week for a major debate on migration policy, with the lower house National Assembly discussing the issue on Monday and the Senate on Wednesday.</p><p>The French president, whose first term expires in 2022, is keenly aware that his biggest political rival remains Marine Le Pen and her far-right National Rally party which has built its popularity on a strong anti-immigration stance.</p><p>"In order to be able to welcome everyone properly, we should not be too attractive a country," said Macron.</p><p>He said he wanted to look at the basket of state medical aid offered to migrants while emphasising that getting rid of such help entirely would be "ridiculous".</p><p>"It would be an error to say that the question of migration is a taboo or just something to raise when there are crises," he said, emphasising that France had always been a country of migration.</p><p>During the 2017 presidential campaign, Macron lavished support on the open door policy of German Chancellor Angela Merkel in allowing in over a million refugees, saying it had "saved our collective dignity".</p><p>He said two priorities now had to be giving asylum as quickly as possible to those who have a right to France's protection and integrating them more effectively through more French courses and a more aggressive employment policy.</p><p>But he said those who had entered France illegally needed to be moved away "much more efficiently", and that current processes last too long.</p><p>France last year received a record 122,743 asylum requests, up 22 percent compared to 2017.</p><p>sjw/adp/bp</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>