<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="cde80762-4536-434c-8819-c706eb3b044c" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDW8P6JTSE8:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDW8P6JTSE8:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYDW8P6JTSE800000_DNMLENf-20190925110953.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Aramco Is Set to Formally Announce Listing Plan Next Month</title><authors>Matthew Martin, Dinesh Nair, Archana Narayanan and Anthony DiPaola</authors><summary>PYDW8P6JTSE8(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Aramco is set to kick off its mammoth initial public offering next month as the oil giant recovers faster than expected from the biggest terror attacks in its history, according to people with knowledge of the matter.The company aims to announce its intention to float around Oct. 20, the people said, asking not to be identified because the information is private. The firm, which is holding analyst meetings from Wednesday, is targeting a $2 trillion valuation...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Aramco is set to kick off its mammoth initial public offering next month as the oil giant recovers faster than expected from the biggest terror attacks in its history, according to people with knowledge of the matter.</p><p>The company aims to announce its intention to float around Oct. 20, the people said, asking not to be identified because the information is private. The firm, which is holding analyst meetings from Wednesday, is targeting a $2 trillion valuation -- more than double that of Apple Inc.</p><p>Aramco’s listing on the Saudi stock exchange could take place as early as November, though the timetable hasn’t been finalized, one of the people said. The IPO preparations come as the company took its production capacity back above 11 million barrels a day, beating its own target by about a week, other people said.</p><p>Banks are working flat out to get the IPO done after the drone and missile attacks on two Aramco facilities on Sept. 14 caused a record surge in oil prices. A $2 trillion valuation would make Aramco’s the world’s most valuable company.</p><p>The eventual timing and other details will depend on market conditions and investor demand, the people said. Aramco didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment.</p><p>More than 100 bankers and officials are meeting for two days of analyst presentations at Aramco’s headquarters in Dhahran in the kingdom’s Eastern Province, the people said. The company’s management are presenting to banks’ research teams, they said.</p><p>At the same time, Aramco has been working hard to restore total production capacity, while maintaining normal supplies to customers by tapping inventories and ramping up other fields. The state-run company has now restored production at the Abqaiq processing facility and Khurais oil field to levels seen before the attack, according to people with knowledge of the situation.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Matthew Martin in Dubai at mmartin128@bloomberg.net;Dinesh Nair in London at dnair5@bloomberg.net;Archana Narayanan in Dubai at anarayanan16@bloomberg.net;Anthony DiPaola in Dubai at adipaola@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Ben Scent at bscent@bloomberg.net, Stefania Bianchi, Shaji Mathew</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>