<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="75e1e52e-de6a-4238-a00b-a4a0a5d961fd" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26F01P:840155939</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26F01P:840155939</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T102701Z_840155939_L3N26F01P_RTRMADT_0_MOTOR-F1-RUSSIA.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Motor racing-Formula One statistics for the Russian Grand Prix</title><summary>MOTOR-F1-RUSSIA/:Motor racing-Formula One statistics for the Russian Grand Prix</summary><xmlText><p>Motor racing-Formula One statistics for the Russian Grand Prix</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - Statistics for Sunday's Russian Formula One Grand Prix, the 16th race of the 21-round season:</p><p>-</p><p>Lap distance: 5.848km. Total distance: 309.745km (53 laps)</p><p>2018 pole: Valtteri Bottas (Finland) Mercedes one minute 31.387 seconds.</p><p>2018 winner: Lewis Hamilton (Britain) Mercedes</p><p>Race lap record: Bottas, 1:35.861, 2018</p><p>Start time: 1110 GMT (1410 local, GMT+3)</p><p>-</p><p>RUSSIA</p><p>Mercedes are the only team to have won in Russia since the first race in Sochi in 2014.</p><p>Hamilton won in 2014, 2015 and 2018, Nico Rosberg in 2016 and Bottas in 2017.</p><p>Ferrari's Sebastian Vettel, in 2017, is the only non-Mercedes driver to have started on pole in Russia.</p><p>Mercedes and Ferrari have taken 13 of 15 podium places in Russia to date. The only exceptions were Bottas, third in 2014 for Williams, and Sergio Perez who was third for Force India in 2015.</p><p>Bottas started on the front row in Sochi in 2016, took the first race win of his F1 career there in 2017 and pole in 2018</p><p>The layout runs clockwise around the 2014 Olympic Park venues, partly on public roads, and features 12 right and six left-hand corners.</p><p>Toro Rosso's Daniil Kvyat is the only current Russian F1 driver.</p><p>-</p><p>RACE WINS</p><p>Hamilton has 81 career victories and has Michael Schumacher's record 91 in his sights. Vettel, third on the all-time list, has 53.</p><p>Ferrari have won 238 races since 1950, McLaren 182, Williams 114, Mercedes 97 and Red Bull 61. Former champions McLaren and Williams have not won since 2012.</p><p>Hamilton has won eight out of 15 races so far this season and has a 65-point lead over team mate Valtteri Bottas, who has won twice. Red Bull's Max Verstappen and Ferrari's Charles Leclerc have also won twice, Vettel once.</p><p>-</p><p>POLE POSITION</p><p>Hamilton has a record 87 career poles, Vettel 56.</p><p>Five races so far this season have been won from pole -- Bottas in Azerbaijan, Hamilton in Monaco and France and Leclerc in Belgium and Italy. Max Verstappen took the first pole of his Formula One career in Hungary on Aug. 3.</p><p>Ferrari have had 63 front row lockouts, one behind Mercedes in the list of all-time records.</p><p>Leclerc has outqualified Vettel for eight races in a row.</p><p>-</p><p>PODIUM</p><p>Hamilton has 146 career podiums. Vettel has 118.</p><p>-</p><p>RACES LED</p><p>Hamilton has led 142 grands prix, a record he shares with Schumacher.</p><p>-</p><p>POINTS</p><p>Hamilton has finished the last 27 races in the points. He holds the record of 33 successive scoring finishes.</p><p>-</p><p>MILESTONE</p><p>Alfa Romeo's Kimi Raikkonen is making his 307th start this weekend, sending him third in the all-time list ahead of Michael Schumacher and Jenson Button. Only Fernando Alonso (311) and Rubens Barrichello (322) have started more. (Reporting by Alan Baldwin, editing by Ken Ferris)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>