<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ef161859-11d3-4112-9ed3-23f9f45b477e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0447</summary><sourceId>7857d141-2162-4770-770a-fce3269715fb</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7008%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0447</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">major League Baseball</hl2><p xmlns="">OFFICE OF THE COMMISSIONER OF BASEBALL — Suspended Houston RHP Dean Deetz 80 games after testing positive for Dehydrochlormethyltestosterone, a performance-enhancing substance, in violation of Major League Baseball's Joint Drug Prevention and Treatment Program. Suspended Houston minor league 1B Jonathan Singleton (Corpus Christi-Texas) 100 games after a third positive test for a drug of abuse in violation of the Minor League Drug Prevention and Treatment Program.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Signed OF Curtis Granderson to a one-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Promoted Brian Chicklo to trainer. Named Jim Cavallini director of performance and sports science, and Joseph Golia assistant trainer. Agreed to terms with INF Ty Kelly on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">FLORENCE FREEDOM — Signed RHP Sam Brunner to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">RIVER CITY RASCALS — Signed INF Stephen Kerr.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">AGUA CALIENTE CLIPPERS — Acquired F DeAndre Daniels from the G League available player pool. Acquired the returning player rights to G Cameron Ayers and F JayVaughn Pinkston from Maine for F Vitto Brown.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">GREEN BAY PACKERS — Promoted Jason Wahlers to vice president of communications.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Signed WR Cayleb Jones to a reserve-future contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Arena Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">AFL — Announced Albany Empire as the name for the new Albany, N.Y. team.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO SABRES — Recalled D Matt Tennyson from Rochester (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Assigned D Joe Hicketts and C Dominic Turgeon to Grand Rapids (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Indy's Garrett Clarke two games and fined him an undisclosed amount for his actions during a Jan. 21 game at Kalamazoo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">COLORADO RAPIDS — Named Ena Patel director of player personnel.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Acquired the MLS Homegrown Player rights for M Eryk Williamson from D.C. United for $100,000 General Allocation Money in 2018, $100,000 Targeted Allocation Money in 2019, a 2018 international spot and a natural second-round pick in the 2020 MLS SuperDraft.</p><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SOUNDERS FC — Loaned M Aaron Kovar to Los Angeles FC.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON SPIRIT — Acquired G Aubrey Bledsoe and a 2019 first-round draft pick from Orlando for D Shelina Zadorsky.</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED 2 — Named Rob Valentino assistant coach.</p><p xmlns="">OTTAWA FURY FC — Signed D Colin Falvey.</p><hl2 xmlns="">WEIGHTLIFTING</hl2><p xmlns="">USADA — Announced weightlifter Alyssa Travis accepted a four-year sanction for an anti-doping rule violation due to her refusal to provide a sample during an out-of-competition test on December 3, 2017.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">COLONIAL ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION — Named Lynn Newton associate commissioner for finance and internal affairs.</p><p xmlns="">BROWN — Named Ahen Kim volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">CHARLESTON SOUTHERN — Named Laura Grace Belote assistant volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">CREIGHTON — Named Connie Yori assistant women's basketball coach.</p><p xmlns="">FLORIDA — Announced RB Jordan Scarlett, WR Rick Wells, LB James Houston and LB Ventrell Miller have cleared suspension and are now on active roster.</p><p xmlns="">IOWA — Named Derrick Foster assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">NYU — Named Andrew Brown women's volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">OHIO STATE — Promoted Ryan Day offensive coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">SYRACUSE — Announced RB Abdul Adams has transferred from Oklahoma.</p><p xmlns="">UCLA — Named Dana Bible quarterbacks coach, Roy Manning special teams and outside linebackers coach and Vince Oghobaase defensive line coach. Retained receivers coach Jimmie Dougherty, running backs coach DeShaun Foster, offensive line coach Hank Fraley and tight ends coach Angus McClure.</p><p xmlns="">WISCONSIN-OSHKOSH — Named Jon Ellmann women's volleyball coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>