<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e5f68abf-8f52-4ab7-8e28-2b838025f332" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T100627Z:TX-PAR-EJJ42:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T100627Z:TX-PAR-EJJ42:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T100627Z-TX-PAR-EJJ42.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>Singapore</item><item>law</item><item>gay</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Singapore activist in new challenge to gay sex ban</title><authors></authors><summary>A Singaporean gay rights activist said Wednesday he has filed a legal challenge against a law banning sex between men, the third recent bid to overturn the legislation.The law -- known as "Section 377A" of the penal code -- was inherited from the British colonial era but is rarely enforced in Singapore.Campaigners in the city-state have renewed efforts to do away with it since India's Supreme Court last year decriminalised gay sex by overturning a statute from its own period under British...</summary><city>Singapore</city><country>SGP</country><xmlText><p>A Singaporean gay rights activist said Wednesday he has filed a legal challenge against a law banning sex between men, the third recent bid to overturn the legislation.</p><p>The law -- known as "Section 377A" of the penal code -- was inherited from the British colonial era but is rarely enforced in Singapore.</p><p>Campaigners in the city-state have renewed efforts to do away with it since India's Supreme Court last year decriminalised gay sex by overturning a statute from its own period under British rule.</p><p>The latest court challenge was filed by Roy Tan, a 61-year-old retired medical doctor, who argues the law is unconstitutional. </p><p>"I am eager to see this archaic law, which has no place in modern society, struck down," Tan said in a statement.</p><p>He argued the law can lead to gay people feeling socially isolated, depressed and suicidal, and fuels negative media representation of the LGBT community.</p><p>"By institutionalising discrimination, it alienates them from having a sense of belonging and purposeful place in our society, and prevents them from taking pride in Singapore's achievements," he said.</p><p>The challenge would seek to prove that the Court of Appeal made a mistake in 2014 when it ruled that Section 377A was constitutional, according to Tan.</p><p>When it dismissed that challenge, the appeals court said it was up to parliament to repeal the law.</p><p>Tan's case was filed in the High Court last week and his lawyer, M. Ravi, had represented one of the complainants in the failed appeal in 2014.</p><p>After the Indian decision, a challenge against the law was lodged by Singaporean DJ Johnson Ong -- known as DJ Big Kid -- in September. </p><p>Another was filed in November by Bryan Choong, an LGBT rights advocate.</p><p>While affluent Singapore boasts a modern and vibrant culture, official attitudes towards being gay remain conservative, although support for same-sex rights is growing.</p><p>cla/sr/jah</p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>