<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="03aade7b-d861-493a-9d58-fe891f801a2c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0545</summary><sourceId>f6573130-d705-4eed-eedb-a437edbcb9a1</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6152%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0545</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Jan. 24</hl2><p xmlns="">1939 — Eddie Collins, Wee Willie Keeler and George Sisler are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1956 — Bob Pettit of the St. Louis Hawks captures the first of his NBA-record four All-Star MVP awards. Pettit leads the West team with 20 points and 24 rebounds in a 108-94 win over the East.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Mike Bossy of the New York Islanders scores his 50th goal in the 50th game of the season in a 7-3 victory over the Quebec Nordiques.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Ray Wersching kicks a Super Bowl record-tying four field goals to help the San Francisco 49ers beat the Cincinnati Bengals 26-21.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — Mike Bossy of the New York Islanders scores his 1,000th career point with an assist in a 7-5 victory over the Toronto Maple Leafs.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Winston-Salem State basketball coach Clarence "Big House" Gaines wins his 800th career game, 79-70 over Livingstone.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — David Duval shoots a magic number — a round of 59 that matches the best score in PGA Tour history. Duval surges from seven strokes off the pace for a one-stroke victory over Steve Pate in the Bob Hope Chrysler Classic.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Mirai Nagasu pulls off one of the biggest upsets ever at the U.S. Figure Skating Championships. The 14-year-old — in her first competition as a senior — wins the short program with a spectacular performance. Her score of 70.23 is the second-highest ever by an American woman in a short program.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Kelly Kulick becomes the first woman to win a PBA Tour title, beating Chris Barnes in the final of the 45th Tournament of Champions. Kulick outscores Barnes 265-195 to take home the $40,000 first prize and a two-year PBA Tour exemption.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Peyton Manning throws three touchdown passes and the Indianapolis Colts rally from an 11-point, first-half deficit to beat the New York Jets 30-17 in the AFC championship game.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The New Orleans Saints make it to their first Super Bowl after battering Brett Favre and the Minnesota Vikings 31-28 in overtime on unheralded Garrett Hartley's 40-yard field goal.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Carmelo Anthony scores a career-high and franchise-record 62 points, most at the current Madison Square Garden, and the New York Knicks beat the Charlotte Bobcats 125-96. Anthony, with 56 after three quarters, stays in for the first few minutes of the fourth to break Bernard King's Knicks record of 60 points and Kobe Bryant's arena record of 61, set five years ago.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Denver cornerback Bradley Roby picks off Tom Brady's pass on a 2-point try with 12 seconds left to preserve a 20-18 victory for the Broncos over the New England Patriots in the AFC title game.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Cam Newton throws two touchdowns and runs for two others, and Carolina's big-play defense stifles Arizona's top-ranked offense in a 49-15 romp for the NFC championship.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Venus Williams beats No. 24-seeded Anastasia Pavlyuchenkova 6-4, 7-6 (3) to become the oldest player to reach the Australian Open women's semifinals in the Open era. The 36-year-old posts her 50th career win at Melbourne Park to earn her a spot in the last four for the first time in 14 years.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>