<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f255284c-4bfc-4e56-b130-dbfe9ab94ca9" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2GD:2028856979</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2GD:2028856979</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T131614Z_2028856979_L3N26G2GD_RTRMADT_0_NIKE-RESULTS-CHINA-GRAPHIC.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>No tariff fears for Nike after online success</title><summary>NIKE-RESULTS/CHINA (GRAPHIC):No tariff fears for Nike after online success</summary><xmlText><p>No tariff fears for Nike after online success</p><p>By Tanvi Mehta and Nivedita Balu</p><p>Sept 25 (Reuters) - Nike Inc's online sales growth and a bullish outlook in China put it on a firm path for years to come and should help it easily ride out rises in U.S. import tariffs on its Chinese-made sneakers, Wall Street analysts said on Wednesday after a strong set of quarterly results.</p><p>Shares in the world's biggest sportswear maker surged as much as 5% in early trade after the results late on Tuesday showed its margins soaring and sales up 42% through apps and websites it has developed under its Nike Direct strategy.</p><p>That signalled an end to a rough period marked by strong competition from German rival Adidas AG and prompted at least 11 Wall Street brokerages to raise price targets on its stock far above a current $87.</p><p>Evercore ISI set a price target of $150, compared with a current Wall Street median of $100.</p><p>One big questionmark over Nike has been whether it will be hit in its biggest growth market, China, by a backlash against American-branded goods in response to President Donald Trump's rhetoric and successive rounds of import tariffs.</p><p>Instead, Nike's sales there grew 22% year-on-year, extending a run of double-digit growth that goes back five years. Analysts from another major brokerage, Credit Suisse, said China would be a source of growth for many years to come and Chief Financial Officer Andy Campion indicated the company was not experiencing any fallout with Chinese consumers.</p><p>"Nike's digital business grew over 70% in China in the first quarter," Credit Suisse analysts said. "And we'd note that this outsized digital growth was without the benefit of the Nike App launch."</p><p>Campion said the company would be launching the App in its second quarter ending in November, earlier than previously planned.</p><p>Footwear made by Nike and its peers, Adidas and Puma SE , fell under the Trump administration's latest set of tariffs imposed on Sept. 1.</p><p>But as well as the bullish results, several of the brokerages laid out a range of different tools Nike would be able to use to either avoid tariffs being applied to some goods, change sourcing or pass more costs onto suppliers and retailers.</p><p>"We remain confident that Nike can effectively manage List 4 tariffs due to its sophisticated supply chain and leverage with vendors," Telsey Advisory Group analysts said in a note. Graphic: https://tmsnrt.rs/2lFAm8x</p><p>(Additional reporting by Geetha Panchaksharam in Bengaluru; editing by Patrick Graham and Saumyadeb Chakrabarty)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>