<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="a6cc2077-f6e4-47e6-9ce7-01261d5d975b" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):11:45 a.m.U.S. stocks are rising as technology and health care companies make more gains.Chipmaker Intel jumped 9.4 percent and drugmaker AbbVie soared 9.3 percent...</summary><sourceId>08306d8b-3372-440c-40ca-b5489cd43aca</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:W1806%asian%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: Tech, health care lead gains for stocks</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">U.S. stocks are rising as technology and health care companies make more gains.</p><p xmlns="">Chipmaker Intel jumped 9.4 percent and drugmaker AbbVie soared 9.3 percent after both reported results that were far better than analysts were expecting.</p><p xmlns="">VMware rose 12 percent after The Wall Street Journal reported that Dell may pursue a full takeover of the company.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 13 points, or 0.5 percent, to 2,852.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average added 71 points, or 0.3 percent, to 26,464. The Nasdaq composite gained 41 points, or 0.6 percent, to 7,452.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.67 percent. That's the highest level for that benchmark rate since July 2014.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Solid gains in technology and health care stocks are sending major U.S. indexes higher in early trading on Wall Street.</p><p xmlns="">Intel jumped 7 percent in the first few minutes of trading Friday after reporting results for its latest quarter that easily beat analysts' forecasts. Intel also gave a strong sales outlook.</p><p xmlns="">Drugmaker AbbVie rose 6.4 percent after its results also came in ahead of expectations.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 9 points, or 0.3 percent, to 2,848.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average added 52 points, or 0.2 percent, to 26,440. The Nasdaq composite gained 31 points, or 0.4 percent, to 7,443.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.64 percent.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>