<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="db9fe841-328b-4c6f-9ee6-8315583b0d8c" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDL1UT1UM0Z:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDL1UT1UM0Z:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDL1UT1UM0Z00000_DNMLENf-20190925080921.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>BofAML Spots a Bargain Upside Bet on the U.S. Stock Market</title><authors>Joanna Ossinger</authors><summary>PYDL1UT1UM0Z(Bloomberg) -- For U.S. equity investors wary of a sell-off but loath to miss out on a stocks rally, Bank of America Merrill Lynch is pitching an options strategy known as a calendar risk reversal.Relatively muted swings and a wide price gap between bullish and bearish options bets means it is attractive to sell a medium-term put on the S&amp;P 500 Index and buy a shorter-dated call, strategists including Gonzalo Asis and Stefano Pascale wrote in a note Tuesday.Such trades generally...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- For U.S. equity investors wary of a sell-off but loath to miss out on a stocks rally, Bank of America Merrill Lynch is pitching an options strategy known as a calendar risk reversal.</p><p>Relatively muted swings and a wide price gap between bullish and bearish options bets means it is attractive to sell a medium-term put on the S&amp;P 500 Index and buy a shorter-dated call, strategists including Gonzalo Asis and Stefano Pascale wrote in a note Tuesday.</p><p>Such trades generally outperform if the underlying index breaks higher and they are cheaper than simply purchasing calls until any equity sell-off reaches about 5%, a rare occurrence, the strategists said. As of Tuesday morning, the entry point for their preferred trade was the most attractive in 18 years, they added.</p><p>“At today’s levels, we like calendar risk reversals for equity replacement to position for a breakout higher in U.S. equities while reducing exposure to moderate drawdowns,” they wrote. “It is clearly the preferred trade when the S&amp;P is flat to mildly lower.”</p><p>U.S. stocks sold off and volatility rose Tuesday as the Democrat-controlled House opened a formal impeachment inquiry against President Donald Trump. While the move added to a raft of investor concerns including trade tensions and disappointing economic data, by some measures implied volatility is above its realized counterpart.</p><p>The Bank of America team suggests investors look at selling three-month puts to buy a one-month call, and recommended closing the trade when the shorter-dated option expires. That fits with their bullish view on risk assets amid a myriad of headwinds and risks, they said.</p><p>“Our house view remains bullish risk assets, but an abundance of headwinds and risks are challenging a stronger move higher in U.S. equities,” they said. “Have your equity cake without ‘eating it’ if risks materialize.”</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Joanna Ossinger in Singapore at jossinger@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Christopher Anstey at canstey@bloomberg.net, Cormac Mullen, Ravil Shirodkar</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>