<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="1179a8b7-b3ad-45c0-810c-21c25d429ecd" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0211</summary><sourceId>951cf884-8d96-4378-378a-f7b7d9a3c2a5</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6556%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0211</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Signed SS Alcides Escobar to a one-year contract. Acquired RHPs Jesse Hahn and Heath Fillmyer from Oakland for LHP Ryan Buchter, 1B/OF Brandon Moss and cash considerations.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed LHP Ben Smith and C Brant Whiting.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY T-BONES — Traded RHP Matt Sergey to Sugar Land for OF David Harris.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX CITY EXPLORERS — Signed LHPs Hunter Ackerman and Ryan Horstman.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Signed RHP Dylan Thompson.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed RHP Jordan Cooper.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed RHP Shawn Blackwell and OF Jordan Hinshaw.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">EVANSVILLE OTTERS — Signed INF Pedro Barrios, OF Hunter Cullen and RHP Randy Wynne.</p><p xmlns="">FLORENCE FREEDOM — Signed C Ryan Dickt.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Signed INF Cletis Avery, LHP Kyle Brown, RHP Corey Sessions and INF Jack Willsey.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">DETROIT PISTONS — Acquired Fs Blake Griffin and Brice Johnson, C Willie Reed, a 2018 protected first-round draft pick and a 2019 second-round pick from the L.A. Clippers for F Tobias Harris, G Avery Bradley and C Boban Marjanovic.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">GREEN BAY PACKERS — Announced the resignation of secondary-safeties coach Darren Perry.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY CHIEFS — Announced the retirements of assistant head coach Brad Childress and special projects coach Tommy Brasher. Announced linebackers coach Gary Gibbs will not return. Promoted Mike Kafka to quarterbacks coach, Mark DeLeone to inside linebackers coach, Mike Smith to outside linebackers coach, Corey Matthaei to assistant offensive line coach, Joe Bleymaier to pass game analyst/assistant quarterbacks coach, and Terry Bradden to defensive quality control coach. Named Jay Valai (defense) and David Girardi (offense) quality control coaches.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Signed OT Storm Norton and S Jack Tocho to reserve-futures contracts.</p><p xmlns="">OAKLAND RAIDERS — Named Brain Callahan quarterbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH STEELERS — Signed WRs Trey Griffey and Tevin Jones, and RB James Summers to reserve/futures contracts.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Recalled LWs Ryan Lomberg and Andrew Mangiapane from Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Recalled F Jason Dickinson and D Dillon Heatherington and Julius Honka from Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled Fs Michael Amadio and Jonny Brodzinski, D Paul LaDue and G Jack Campbell from Ontario (AHL). Placed G Jonathan Quick on injured reserve, retroactive to Jan. 24.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Recalled G Louis Domingue from Syracuse (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">OLYMPICS</hl2><p xmlns="">INTERNATIONAL PARALYMPIC COMMITTEE — Announced Russia has been barred from the Pyeongchang Paralympics.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">MLS — Awarded an expansion franchise to Miami.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEMSON — Announced DT Jabril Robinson will transfer.</p><p xmlns="">COASTAL CAROLINA — Named Rick Mueller football executive director of player personnel.</p><p xmlns="">HIGH POINT — Named Ryan Meek volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">LOUISVILLE — Named Brian VanGorder defensive coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>