<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="fc4a351c-c664-44aa-8cc8-92b5ab233c0b" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4 p.m.The stock market slumped to its worst loss since August, giving back some of the big gains it has posted since the beginning of the year.Health care companies...</summary><sourceId>1f8e9771-5c11-4beb-beba-556231164e79</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:W1863%asian%u%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: Stocks have biggest drop since August</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates with close of US trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">The stock market slumped to its worst loss since August, giving back some of the big gains it has posted since the beginning of the year.</p><p xmlns="">Health care companies were by far the biggest losers on Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">Insurers, drugmakers and distributors slumped following news that Amazon was teaming up with JPMorgan Chase and Berkshire Hathaway on a health care venture.</p><p xmlns="">CVS Health sank 4.1 percent and UnitedHealth Group dropped 4.3 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 31 points, or 1.1 percent, to 2,822.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average slid 362 points, or 1.4 percent, to 26,076. The Nasdaq lost 64 points, or 0.9 percent, to 7,402.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices continued to fall. The yield on the 10-year Treasury rose to 2.72 percent, its highest level in almost four years.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks fell sharply in midday trading on Wall Street, extending the market's losses from a day earlier.</p><p xmlns="">Health insurers, drugmakers and distributors led the slide Tuesday following news that JPMorgan Chase, Amazon and Berkshire Hathaway are launching a health care venture.</p><p xmlns="">Express Scripts plunged 7 percent, CVS Health sank 5 percent and UnitedHealth Group dropped 3.3 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Technology stocks also retreated. Energy companies fell as crude oil prices headed lower.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 24 points, or 0.9 percent, to 2,828.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average slid 293 points, or 1.1 percent, to 26,148. The Nasdaq composite lost 47 points, or 0.6 percent, to 7,419.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.71 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Health care stocks are leading U.S. indexes broadly lower in early trading following news of a big new venture in the health care business.</p><p xmlns="">Prescription drug makers, drug distributors and health insurers posted big losses early Tuesday on fears of stiff competition from a new venture announced by JPMorgan Chase, Amazon and Berkshire Hathaway.</p><p xmlns="">Express Scripts plunged 9 percent and UnitedHealth Group sank 4.4 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 19 points, or 0.7 percent, to 2,853.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average slid 226 points, or 0.7 percent, to 26,214. The Nasdaq composite lost 58 points, or 0.8 percent, to 7,407.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.71 percent.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>