<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="58c54c71-49e6-448a-994b-048d29421a4a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC- Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC- Transactions, Writethru,0595</summary><sourceId>e3e6c00e-6b52-4ce5-ce5a-4a44caa45380</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0190%-----%r%BC- Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC- Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC- Transactions, Writethru,0595</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with RHP Matt Magill and OF Andy Wilkins on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Rhiner Cruz and Al Alburquerque on minor league contracts.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Traded OF Christian Yelich to the Milwaukee Brewers for OF Lewis Brinson, INF Isan Diaz, OF Monte Harrison and RHP Jordan Yamamoto.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Eastern League</hl2><p xmlns="">TRENTON THUNDER — Named Jay Bell manager, Tim Norton pitching coach, Ty Hawkins hitting coach, Luis Dorante bullpen coach, Raul Dominguez defensive coach, Jimmy Downam trainer and Anthony Velazquez strength coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO DOGS — Signed RHP Josh Goossen-Brown.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed SS Dan Lyons.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Signed SS Julian Russell.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WILD THINGS — Signed LHP Mike Castellani.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Fined Golden State Warriors F Kevin Durant $15,000 for public criticism of the officiating.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Assigned F Tyler Cavanaugh and G Isaiah Taylor to Erie (NBAGL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES LAKERS — Assigned Cs Thomas Bryant and Ivica Zubac to South Bay (NBAGL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON REDSKINS — Re-signed LB Mason Foster.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Recalled F Ryan Lomberg from Stockton (AHL) and G Mason McDonald from Kansas City (ECHL) to Stockton. Assigned G Tyler Parsons from Stockton to Kansas City.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Assigned D Haydn Fleury to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">EDMONTON OILERS — Assigned G Nick Ellis from Bakersfield (AHL) to Wichita (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Assigned Fs Michael Amadio and Jonny Brodzinski, and D Paul LaDue to Ontario (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE PREDATORS — Assigned G Matt O'Connor from Milwaukee (AHL) to Manchester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Placed F Marcus Johansson on injured reserve. Recalled G Mackenzie Blackwood and F Kevin Rooney from Binghamton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Assigned F Dan Catenacci to Hartford (AHL). Claimed F Cody McLeod off waivers from Nashville.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BAKERSFIELD CONDORS — Recalled F Evan Polei from Wichita (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">ROCHESTER AMERICANS — Recalled F Justin Danforth from Cincinnati (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">STOCKTON HEAT — Recalled G Mason McDonald from Kansas City (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MARLIES — Assigned F Josh Winquist to Orlando (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">WILKES-BARRE/SCRANTON PENGUINS — Returned G Charles Williams on loan to Manchester (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ADIRONDACK THUNDER — Signed G Tomas Sholl.</p><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Loaned D Matt Petgrave to Toronto (AHL). Signed D Mackenzie Braid.</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Signed F Shawn Bates.</p><p xmlns="">MANCHESTER MONARCHS — Loaned G Branden Komm to Springfield (AHL). Released G Joe Spagnoli.</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Added G Rob Lemelin as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">OLYMPIC SPORTS</hl2><p xmlns="">USADA — Imposed a four-year sanction on American cyclist Jennifer Schrumm after testing positive for a prohibited substance.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">SKY BLUE FC — Named Joe Nemzer and Lubos Ancin assistant coaches.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">SACRAMENTO REPUBLIC — Agreed to terms with D Mitchell Taintor.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALABAMA — Named Karl Scott secondary coach and Josh Gattis wide receivers coach.</p><p xmlns="">CHATTANOOGA — Named Davern Williams defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">FORDHAM — Named Peter Banas assistant women's tennis coach and Gio Grassi assistant strength and conditioning coach.</p><p xmlns="">MARYLAND — Promoted associate head volleyball coach Adam Hughes to head coach.</p><p xmlns="">NEW MEXICO — Announced junior men's basketball F Carlton Bragg is transferring from Arizona State.</p><p xmlns="">PENN STATE — Named Ja'Juan Seider running backs coach. Promoted defensive line coach Sean Spencer to associate head coach. Reassigned running backs coach David Corley to wide receivers coach.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN CAL — Fired men's basketball associate head coach Tony Bland.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON STATE — Announced women's basketball coach June Daugherty is taking an indefinite medical leave of absence. Promoted associate head coach Mike Daugherty to acting coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>