<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="42d1d2d4-dbc3-43b0-8ee8-9c38ab0e3c37" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDUP36KLVR5:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDUP36KLVR5:1</followId><sourceFileName>PYDUP36KLVR500000_DNMLENf-20190925100983.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>India’s Sensex Snaps Three-Day Winning Run</title><authors>Abhishek Vishnoi</authors><summary>PYDUP36KLVR5(Bloomberg) -- India’s equities benchmark snapped a three-day winning streak, tracking declines in global stocks, as investors assessed the potential fallout of an impeachment inquiry of U.S. President Donald Trump.The S&amp;P BSE Sensex dropped 1.3% to 38,593.52 at the 3:30 p.m. close in Mumbai, while the NSE Nifty 50 Index also fell by the same magnitude. Both gauges surged more than 8% in the three sessions through Tuesday after India’s government lowered the corporate tax...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- India’s equities benchmark snapped a three-day winning streak, tracking declines in global stocks, as investors assessed the potential fallout of an impeachment inquiry of U.S. President Donald Trump.</p><p>The S&amp;P BSE Sensex dropped 1.3% to 38,593.52 at the 3:30 p.m. close in Mumbai, while the NSE Nifty 50 Index also fell by the same magnitude. Both gauges surged more than 8% in the three sessions through Tuesday after India’s government lowered the corporate tax rate.</p><p>Global stocks fell on Wednesday after U.S. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said a formal impeachment inquiry will be opened on Trump.</p><p>India remains the most expensive market in emerging Asia even as analysts increased earnings estimates for the benchmark gauges by as much as 10% to factor in the lower tax burden, according to Bloomberg data.</p><p>Strategist View</p><p>“We prefer to remain cautious at higher levels,” Ajit Mishra, vice president of research at Religare Broking Ltd. wrote in a note on Tuesday. “Indian benchmark indices are trading near peak valuations and sustainability at this level is essential.”</p><p>The Numbers</p><p>Analyst Note/Market-Related Stories</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Abhishek Vishnoi in Singapore at avishnoi4@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Lianting Tu at ltu4@bloomberg.net, Margo Towie, Naoto Hosoda</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>