<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6e2f6dcd-e72d-c4d6-2112-80ef9fbdb64f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Tod Leonard</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-GLF-WOODS-TORREYPINES:SD — sports, itop (950 words)</title><summary>LA JOLLA, Calif. — For virtually all of Tiger Woods’ career, it was the one question that produced the shortest answer.Invariably, someone would inquire about Woods’ expectations for a certain tournament. He’d answer quickly, without a hint of a...</summary><sourceId>363d942d-2208-6b00-b007-6bc86498099d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K0827%kniht%r%BC-GLF-WOODS-TORREYPINES:SD — sports, itop (950 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Tiger Woods enters the great unknown at Torrey Pines</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Tod Leonard</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">LA JOLLA, Calif. — For virtually all of Tiger Woods’ career, it was the one question that produced the shortest answer.</p><p xmlns="">Invariably, someone would inquire about Woods’ expectations for a certain tournament. He’d answer quickly, without a hint of a smile or doubt.</p><p xmlns="">It doesn’t take long to utter a single letter.</p><p xmlns="">“W,” Woods would say.</p><p xmlns="">Next question.</p><p xmlns="">That was the guy who won 14 majors and 79 PGA Tour events in the first 18 years of his career.</p><p xmlns="">That is not the same golfer who will make his first U.S. start in a year when the Farmers Insurance Open begins Thursday, sitting on a victory drought of four years.</p><p xmlns="">He arrived at Torrey Pines — the site of eight of his wins — with fused disks in his back, some hints of optimism, but absolutely no clue how he will perform.</p><p xmlns="">That single letter has been replaced by piece of punctuation: “?”</p><p xmlns="">At a news conference Wednesday, Woods admitted his expectations have been tempered by all that he has been through since his last victory in 2013.</p><p xmlns="">“I haven’t played a full schedule since 2015. It’s been a long time,” he said. “To be honest with you, I just want to start playing on the tour and getting into a rhythm of playing a schedule again. I haven’t done that in such a long time that I don’t know what to expect.</p><p xmlns="">“I want to start feeling what it feels like to be out here and hit shots, grind out scores, and that’s something that I’ve been looking forward to.”</p><p xmlns="">Woods, 42, played 16 PGA Tour events in 2013 and won five times. He has competed in only 19 tournaments since, managing one top-10 finish.</p><p xmlns="">His 2014 season was hindered by back surgery, the ’15 campaign was abbreviated and there was another back surgery, and he lost all of ‘16 while recovering.</p><p xmlns="">When Woods tried to come back last year, he missed the cut for the first time at Torrey Pines and withdrew after one round the following week in Dubai.</p><p xmlns="">Woods announced in late April that he would undergo more surgery — this time to fuse disks in his lower back. He has said that there were times when the pain had been so bad he couldn’t get out of bed.</p><p xmlns="">His soft return came in December at the unofficial event he hosts, the Hero World Challenge in the Bahamas. More encouraging than the results — he shot a 65 in one round and finished 15th — was how sound his swing and body looked.</p><p xmlns="">Since that event, Woods said he has been playing golf at home in Florida about six days a week, which would give him about 40 rounds of work.</p><p xmlns="">“Now it’s just, ‘Hey, want to go play 18? Want to go play 36?’ Sure,” Woods said. “That, to me, is fun. I miss those days.”</p><p xmlns="">Woods said that the quality of his life is “infinitely better” than it was a year ago when he came to Torrey Pines. He spoke of a burning pain running the length of his leg to his feet, and of times when he collapsed while walking.</p><p xmlns="">“I just wanted to not feel as bad as I had felt for such a long time,” Woods said. “I just want to have the lifestyle in which I can actually participate in my kids’ life. … Golf was not on the top of that list.</p><p xmlns="">“But now that I’m able to start doing that, it feels good. It feels good to go out and practice. … I haven’t felt this good in years, so I’m excited about it.”</p><p xmlns="">Knowledgeable coaches have marveled at the swing speed Woods displayed in the Hero.</p><p xmlns="">Woods’ former instructor, Hank Haney, was interviewed Wednesday on PGA Tour Radio and predicted a top-10 finish for Woods this week.</p><p xmlns="">“My goodness, his swing looks great,” Haney said. “There is no way in the world that Tiger Woods cannot win golf tournaments with that swing.”</p><p xmlns="">Others are more skeptical.</p><p xmlns="">“The Bahamas was a nice resort golf course. It was 85 degrees,” CBS analyst Nick Faldo said on the phone this week. “Now you come to a proper golf tournament, on a proper golf course, with serious rough.</p><p xmlns="">“Does he have the stamina for tournament week? Does he have the consistency?”</p><p xmlns="">Woods played 27 holes at Torrey Pines to prepare for this event, and those questions remain unanswered. In Wednesday’s pro-am on the extremely narrow North Course, he hit only six of 14 fairways and reached only seven greens in regulation.</p><p xmlns="">But he also finished with a flurry, making a 25-foot eagle when he reached the par-five 17th in two shots and a birdie on 18 from two feet. He shot two-under 70.</p><p xmlns="">What remains clear is that the fascination with Woods has barely waned. Dozens of fans tailed him before sunlight touched the course at 6:40 a.m., and the gallery swelled to several hundred by the end.</p><p xmlns="">“The most compelling figure in golf, and maybe in all of sports,” Faldo said.</p><p xmlns="">Jim Nantz, CBS’s longtime golf host, offered that this latest comeback is akin to Tom Brady or Michael Jordan taking a couple of years off and then suiting up again.</p><p xmlns="">“We don’t know what that’s going to look like,” Nantz said, “but I know I’ve got to see it.”</p><p xmlns="">Woods wouldn’t make any predictions for the week, saying that he didn’t have a feel for some of his young competitors. He said he met Jon Rahm, the defending champion here and world No. 2, for the first time this week.</p><p xmlns="">Woods does, however, have one large goal in front of him — Augusta. He has played in only one of the last four Masters. Remarkably, he hasn’t pulled on a green jacket since 2005.</p><p xmlns="">“I’m just trying to build toward April,” he said.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>