<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2430995b-9472-4c86-a961-2ff332252f4e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):4 p.m.Stocks are closing mostly lower on Wall Street after a midday gain evaporated in the late afternoon.Consumer-focused companies like retailers led the way...</summary><sourceId>e55cc457-2145-4231-231a-11f999aa7ead</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:C7371%-----%r%BC-Financial Markets-Markets Right Now,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Markets Right Now: US stock indexes close mostly lower</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Updates with close of US trading.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NEW YORK (AP) — The latest on developments in financial markets (All times local):</p><p xmlns="">4 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are closing mostly lower on Wall Street after a midday gain evaporated in the late afternoon.</p><p xmlns="">Consumer-focused companies like retailers led the way lower Thursday. Amazon, which has been on a tear recently, dropped 4.2 percent.</p><p xmlns="">United Parcel Service slumped 6.1 percent after saying higher costs affected its business in the fourth quarter.</p><p xmlns="">Facebook rose 3.3 percent after reporting revenue that came in ahead of analysts' forecasts. Chipmaker Qorvo soared 16.1 percent.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 1 point, or 0.1 percent, to 2,821.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average climbed 37 points, or 0.1 percent, to 26,186. The Nasdaq composite fell 25 points, or 0.3 percent, to 7,385.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.78 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">11:45 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are shaking off an early wobble and moving higher in midday trading on Wall Street, led by gains in technology companies.</p><p xmlns="">Facebook rose 4 percent Thursday after reporting revenue that came in ahead of analysts' forecasts. Chipmaker Qorvo jumped 13 percent after reporting a solid quarter.</p><p xmlns="">United Parcel Service slumped 5.6 percent after saying higher costs affected its business in the fourth quarter.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index rose 9 points, or 0.3 percent, to 2,833.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average climbed 113 points, or 0.4 percent, to 26,261. The Nasdaq composite increased 15 points, or 0.2 percent, to 7,426.</p><p xmlns="">Bond prices fell. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose to 2.75 percent.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">9:35 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Stocks are opening broadly lower on Wall Street after several big companies reported disappointing quarterly results or outlooks.</p><p xmlns="">United Parcel Service slumped 6 percent in early trading Thursday after saying higher costs affected its business in the fourth quarter.</p><p xmlns="">PayPal dropped 7.7 percent after eBay said it would move to a different payment processor.</p><p xmlns="">Chipmaker Qorvo jumped 12 percent after reporting a solid quarter.</p><p xmlns="">The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index fell 3 points, or 0.1 percent, to 2,819.</p><p xmlns="">The Dow Jones industrial average fell 86 points, or 0.3 percent, to 26,071. The Nasdaq composite fell 19 points, or 0.3 percent, to 7,392.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>