<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/AFP_Texts' (id: 1788) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="03150ac4-6999-40e3-a5fa-511878adf12a" priority="medium" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>AFP</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T114535Z:TX-PAR-EJL74:1</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:afp.com:20190925T114535Z:TX-PAR-EJL74:1</followId><sourceFileName>afp.com-20190925T114535Z-TX-PAR-EJL74.xml</sourceFileName><keywords><item>France</item><item>internet</item><item>media</item><item>copyright</item></keywords><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AFP_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Google says won't pay media firms to display content</title><authors></authors><summary>Google will not pay French news companies to show excerpts of their articles, pictures or videos in search results, a top executive said Wednesday, though it will not display the excerpts without their approval.The move comes after France became in July the first EU country to adopt the bloc's wide-ranging copyright reform, aimed at ensuring media firms are paid for original content offered online by Google, Facebook and other technology giants.The new rules create a "neighbouring right" to...</summary><city>Paris</city><country>FRA</country><xmlText><p>Google will not pay French news companies to show excerpts of their articles, pictures or videos in search results, a top executive said Wednesday, though it will not display the excerpts without their approval.</p><p>The move comes after France became in July the first EU country to adopt the bloc's wide-ranging copyright reform, aimed at ensuring media firms are paid for original content offered online by Google, Facebook and other technology giants.</p><p>The new rules create a "neighbouring right" to ensure copyright protection -- and compensation -- for media firms using their content.</p><p>Richard Gingras, Google's vice president for news, told journalists in Paris that a Europe-based news publisher would now have to decide if it would allow Google to show "snippets" of content or thumbnail images alongside search results in France.</p><p>If they accept, publishers won't receive any compensation from Google, he said.</p><p>But if they don't, only a headline and link to their content will appear in the results.</p><p>That could sharply reduce online audiences for some publishers, since internet users are more likely to click on results containing excerpts and images.</p><p>The new EU directive was passed last March amid fierce resistance from tech companies which generate huge profits from advertising shown alongside search results and other content they host.</p><p>Google had warned after the European Parliament vote that it "will lead to legal uncertainty and will hurt Europe's creative and digital economies."</p><p>Critics also said the reform would effectively create a "link tax" that would restrict internet discourse, and did not strike the best balance between free circulation of information and copyright protection.</p><p>News publishers, however, said the changes were urgently needed to help them cope with plummeting revenues as their readers migrated online from traditional media outlets.</p><p>AFP was among the media organisations that lobbied for the creation of neighbouring rights.</p><p>fpo/js/rl</p><p>GOOGLE</p><p>Facebook</p><p></p><p class="credit">AFP</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>