<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="71cd28ff-0023-4f89-abfb-059c67c905b9" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDNSBT0G1KZ:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYDNSBT0G1KZ:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYDNSBT0G1KZ00000_DNMLENf-20190925080983.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Thailand Holds Interest Rate as it Downgrades Growth Outlook</title><authors>Suttinee Yuvejwattana</authors><summary>PYDNSBT0G1KZ(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars.  Sign up here. The Bank of Thailand left its benchmark interest rate unchanged and said it may consider steps to rein in the currency’s strength as economic growth weakens.The Monetary Policy Committee voted unanimously Wednesday to hold its key rate at 1.50%, pausing after last month’s surprise cut. The decision was in line with the forecasts of 21 of 29 economists surveyed by...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars.  Sign up here. </p><p>The Bank of Thailand left its benchmark interest rate unchanged and said it may consider steps to rein in the currency’s strength as economic growth weakens.</p><p>The Monetary Policy Committee voted unanimously Wednesday to hold its key rate at 1.50%, pausing after last month’s surprise cut. The decision was in line with the forecasts of 21 of 29 economists surveyed by Bloomberg, with the rest expecting a cut to 1.25%.</p><p>Thai authorities are providing monetary and fiscal support to spur growth, which the central bank now expects will be lower this year than previously forecast. Aside from global concerns, growth is also being undermined by the baht, which has gained more than 6% against the dollar so far this year, the best performer in Asia.</p><p>“With economic growth set to remain weak and concerns about the strength of the baht mounting, we think the central bank will loosen policy again before the end of the year,” Capital Economics Ltd.’s senior Asia economist Gareth Leather wrote in a research note.</p><p>The central bank cut its growth forecast for the year to 2.8% from 3.3% predicted in June, and lowered next year’s forecast to 3.3% from 3.7%. It also sees exports contracting 1% this year, compared with a previous projection of no growth.</p><p>The baht reversed earlier losses and advanced as much as 0.1% before trading little changed at 30.549 per dollar as of 2:56 p.m. in Bangkok.</p><p>Policy makers “expressed concerns” about the currency’s appreciation, “which might affect the economy to a larger degree amid heightened uncertainties pertaining to the external front,” the central bank said in a statement. The MPC will consider “additional appropriate measures if necessary,” it said.</p><p>Chang Wei Liang, a macro strategist at DBS Group Holdings Ltd., said the risk lies on the side of more policy easing from the central bank. The baht “looks overly firm despite a softening export outlook, and this could warrant a rate cut in order to reverse a tightening of monetary conditions from exchange rate appreciation,” he said.</p><p>Inflation remains benign at 0.52% in August, well below the central bank’s 1%-4% target band. The central bank expects to miss its target again this year, forecasting inflation of 0.8% for this year, down from 1% previously.</p><p>The government is also doing its bit to spur growth, launching a $10 billion stimulus package in August. Finance Minister Uttama Savanayana said earlier this month more measures may be deployed if needed.</p><p>(Updates with comment from analyst in fourth paragraph)</p><p>--With assistance from Chester Yung and Yumi Teso.</p><p>To contact the reporter on this story: Suttinee Yuvejwattana in Bangkok at suttinee1@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Sunil Jagtiani at sjagtiani@bloomberg.net, ;Nasreen Seria at nseria@bloomberg.net, Michael S. Arnold</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>