<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts' (id: 549007) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="232a23dc-08f9-463a-a701-356eabeb4a12" priority="high" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:gn4="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:lc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/LoginContext.xsd" xmlns:oc="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/OperationContext.xsd" xmlns:nav="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/ObjNav.xsd" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:edfn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/EditorialXslt"><rights><ref><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Bloomberg</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE3006VDKHS:2</sourceId><followId>urn:newsml:bloomberg.com:20190925:PYE3006VDKHS:2</followId><sourceFileName>PYE3006VDKHS00000_DNMLENf-20190925130954.xml</sourceFileName><keywords /><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Bloomberg_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Elliott Seeks to Split Marathon Petroleum Into Three Businesses</title><authors>Rachel Adams-Heard and Christine Buurma</authors><summary>PYE3006VDKHS(Bloomberg) -- Elliott Management Corp. renewed its call for Marathon Petroleum Corp. to split into three separate businesses, a move the hedge fund said would unlock more than $22 billion in value.Marathon should divide into separate retail, midstream and refining companies, the hedge fund founded by billionaire Paul Singer said Wednesday in a statement. Elliott said it owns about 2.5% of the company. Shares of the refiner jumped 6.5% in pre-market trading in New York.Carving...</summary><city></city><xmlText><p>(Bloomberg) -- Elliott Management Corp. renewed its call for Marathon Petroleum Corp. to split into three separate businesses, a move the hedge fund said would unlock more than $22 billion in value.</p><p>Marathon should divide into separate retail, midstream and refining companies, the hedge fund founded by billionaire Paul Singer said Wednesday in a statement. Elliott said it owns about 2.5% of the company. Shares of the refiner jumped 6.5% in pre-market trading in New York.</p><p>Carving Marathon into three businesses would create a path to address “the company’s chronic underperformance, to improve its businesses and to unlock significant and sustainable value for its shareholders,” Elliott said. Jamal Kheiry, a spokesman for Marathon, could not immediately comment when reached by phone Wednesday.</p><p>It’s not the first time Elliott has pushed for changes at Marathon. In 2016, it had made the same demand for splitting the company into three businesses. The Findlay, Ohio-based refiner took steps to simplify its pipeline partnership a year later at the hedge fund’s urging, but rejected a proposal to spin off its retail arm, Speedway.</p><p>Though Marathon earlier this year agreed to merge its MPLX LP and Andeavor pipeline units, Elliott says the company’s structure remains overly complex.</p><p>Stock Underperformance</p><p>Marathon shares have slid more than 35% in the past year as the energy sector struggles to attract investor capital amid volatile crude prices. CEO Gary Heminger told investors last month in the company’s quarterly earnings statement that it was continuing to focus on portfolio optimization, “which could include asset divestitures to strategically streamline our integrated asset base.”</p><p>The company has been one of the poorest performing U.S. refiners. While peers such as Phillips 66 and Valero Energy Corp. have churned out total returns of 23% and 22%, respectively, over the past two years, Marathon has delivered a gain of less than 9% to shareholders. Only PBF Energy Inc. lagged that result with a 8.1% return. These figures are based on share price performance plus reinvestment of dividends.</p><p>--With assistance from David Wethe and Joe Carroll.</p><p>To contact the reporters on this story: Rachel Adams-Heard in Houston at radamsheard@bloomberg.net;Christine Buurma in New York at cbuurma1@bloomberg.net</p><p>To contact the editors responsible for this story: Simon Casey at scasey4@bloomberg.net, Pratish Narayanan</p><p>For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com</p><p>©2019 Bloomberg L.P.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>