<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="29b2bd99-c588-a805-fd88-13b2eadbbb8d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Michael Smolens</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-SMOLENS-COLUMN:SD — op-ed (900 words)</title><summary>Before there was #MeToo, there was “test them all.”The push to analyze thousands of rape kits that have been sitting in police evidence rooms around the country has been growing for years.That effort has not gained the prominence of the recent...</summary><sourceId>b02f0e9a-a5b9-17eb-7eb6-41cc2a219eb3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K5893%kniht%r%BC-SMOLENS-COLUMN:SD — op-ed (900 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Michael Smolens: How #MeToo may bolster the case for testing all rape kits</h2><byline xmlns="">By Michael Smolens</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Before there was #MeToo, there was “test them all.”</p><p xmlns="">The push to analyze thousands of rape kits that have been sitting in police evidence rooms around the country has been growing for years.</p><p xmlns="">That effort has not gained the prominence of the recent #MeToo movement of women coming forward to reveal they have been victims of sexual assaults, sexual harassment and inappropriate behavior, in notable cases by prominent figures such as Hollywood producer Harvey Weinstein.</p><p xmlns="">But policies have shifted to expedite the analysis of untested rape kits, a change spurred by sexual assault victims, their supporters and an increasing number of elected officials.</p><p xmlns="">The two movements may not be linked, but they came together at a San Diego City Council meeting last week to discuss when the Police Department tests the kits and when it doesn’t.</p><p xmlns="">“We have the #MeToo movement, we have women speaking up,” Suzanne Morse, founder of Heartfelt Voices United, told the council.</p><p xmlns="">Morse suggested women who previously had been reluctant to pursue a case against an attacker may now be reconsidering and want to have their kits tested. “So I am encouraging this City Council to push even harder,” she added.</p><p xmlns="">While other jurisdictions have adopted a test-them-all policy — or something close to it — the San Diego Police Department has not.</p><p xmlns="">At the meeting, Chief Shelley Zimmerman and SDPD crime lab manager Jennifer Shen said the department is revising its policy to allow for the analysis of more than 550 additional kits, which are used to collect DNA samples from victims. That’s about a quarter of the untested kits held by the department.</p><p xmlns="">But they still maintain that testing all kits would lead to duplicative efforts in some cases and wouldn’t lead to solving a crime in others.</p><p xmlns="">The case they make is complex, nuanced and has solid reasoning behind it.</p><p xmlns="">The case for testing all kits, the other hand, is straightforward, easily understood and also has solid reasoning behind it.</p><p xmlns="">That’s where San Diego City Attorney Mara Elliott and District Attorney Summer Stephan stand.</p><p xmlns="">Gov. Jerry Brown also has signed legislation that seeks to ramp up testing statewide, and requires law enforcement agencies to list reasons why they haven’t analyzed individual kits.</p><p xmlns="">The federal government has recently shifted away from its position against testing all kits, which it had said would not substantially help solve crimes, according to the Union-Tribune’s Joshua Stewart.</p><p xmlns="">Now, federal officials say kits should always be tested, even beyond the expiration of statutes of limitations, because it’s possible that the statute could be extended or the information could be used for civil cases under sexual predator laws, Stewart wrote. The test results could also be used to determine prior illegal behavior and be considered in parole hearings and criminal sentencings.</p><p xmlns="">Zimmerman and Shen spent an hour on Jan. 9 giving a presentation in painstaking detail about why they believe it’s best to leave some kits untested. Their audience was a City Council whose majority had insisted more than 1,900 kits be tested and had provided $500,000 to get things moving.</p><p xmlns="">“Bringing justice to our victims is our number one priority,” said Zimmerman, a point she would make a few times.</p><p xmlns="">Shen said rape kits are not tested because they fall into one of several categories: There is no question who the suspect is and that there was sexual contact, but the issue is whether it was consensual; someone’s been arrested and police already have DNA samples; the perpetrator is already in the DNA database; a “Jane Doe” victim gave samples but did not want to proceed with a case; the alleged victim recanted; an investigation showed no crime occurred; better evidence was collected to prosecute; or the victim gave samples, filed a police report but ultimately didn’t want to pursue the case.</p><p xmlns="">Shen said the department prioritizes cases where a stranger is the suspect, which she said accounted for up to 20 percent of sexual assault cases. The crime lab quickly tests all rape kits taken from victims in those cases.</p><p xmlns="">Shen and Zimmerman said SDPD is reconsidering its policy against analyzing rape kits from victims who declined to participate in a criminal investigation after initially being cooperative. As of last week, there were 558 kits that fell into that category.</p><p xmlns="">Shen said a working group will be created to consider whether it makes sense to test for suspect DNA in all those cases — and, if the decision is to go ahead, how they would contact victims who didn’t want to pursue the case. She noted some are very old cases.</p><p xmlns="">“Do we call a victim up 25 years later, when the victim signed paperwork saying they don’t want us to go forward, to tell them we are going to go forward?” Shen asked. “Do we just go forward without telling the victims we’re going forward?”</p><p xmlns="">Shen said the working group would include victims rights advocates and added something everyone seemed to agree with: San Diego must take “a victim-centric approach.”</p><p xmlns="">“That should be first and foremost in our minds,” she told the council</p><p xmlns="">Morse, the victims’ rights advocate, not only agreed, but suggested #MeToo has changed the climate — and possibly the minds of those women who once shied away from pursuing the crime committed against them.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002458,t000027866,t000210820,t000027865,t000027879</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>