<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9a044e02-c032-4a8f-90c6-26a8e38bdcdf" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2ER:901343719</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L3N26G2ER:901343719</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T100654Z_901343719_L3N26G2ER_RTRMADT_0_AUSTRALIA-CANNABIS.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>Canberra becomes first Australian city to legalise marijuana for personal use</title><summary>AUSTRALIA-CANNABIS/:Canberra becomes first Australian city to legalise marijuana for personal use</summary><xmlText><p>Canberra becomes first Australian city to legalise marijuana for personal use</p><p>SYDNEY, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Australia's capital city of Canberra will become the first in the country to legalise the possession, use and cultivation of small amounts of cannabis following a vote on Wednesday.</p><p>Lawmakers in the Australian Capital Territory (ACT) passed a bill allowing people aged 18 or over to possess up to 50 grams per person of cannabis and a maximum of four plants per household for personal consumption.</p><p>That makes the ACT the first among Australia's six states and two main territories to legalise cannabis for personal use.</p><p>The new law is set to come into effect from Jan. 31, 2020.</p><p>Cannabis remains a prohibited substance under Australia's federal law and the new law conflicts with national drug laws which were enacted by the country's parliament that prohibits the possession of marijuana.</p><p>Neighbouring New Zealand will hold a referendum next year on legalising cannabis for personal use.</p><p>(Reporting by Swati Pandey; Editing by Jacqueline Wong)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>