<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ea32578f-dc1d-4dd1-bf8a-e9fffe430b8f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</summary><sourceId>5038bd8b-0e85-4a2d-a2d8-fa930517eddd</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8899%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0862</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Named Jim Kaat special assistant.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO CUBS — Named Jacob Cruz minor league hitting coordinator, Brendan Sagara minor league pitching coordinator, Steve Merriman assistant pitching coordinator, Jeremy Farrell minor league infield coordinator, Chuck Baughman minor league athletic training coordinator and Jonathan Fierro minor league rehab coordinator. Named Chris Valaika assistant coach and Mike McNulty and Ed Halbur athletic trainers for Iowa (PCL); Jesus Feliciano hitting coach, Ben Carhart assistant coach, Toby Williams trainer, and Jason Morriss strength coach for Tennessee (SL); Ty Wright hitting coach, Carlos Rojas assistant coach, Logan Severson trainer and Keegan Knoll strength coach; Ricardo Medina hitting coach, Paul McAnulty assistant coach and James Edwards trainer for South Bend (MWL); Steve Lerud manager, Armando Gabino pitching coach, Osmin Melendez hitting coach, Jacob Rogers assistant coach and Sean Folan trainer for Eugene (NWL); Ike Ogata trainer and Mike Megrew strength coach for Arizona1 (ASL); Jonathan Mota manager and Claudio Almonte hitting coach for Arizona2 (ASL); and Jose Zapata coach for Dominican1 (DSL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Designated RHPs Kevin McGowan and Chasen Bradford for assignment.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Agreed to terms with LHP Felipe Rivero on a four-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO PADRES — Signed RHPs Jonathan Aro, Michael Mariot and Robert Stock, C Raffy Lopez and OF Shane Peterson to minor-league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON NATIONALS — Agreed to terms with INF/OF Howie Kendrick on a two-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">FARGO-MOORHEAD REDHAWKS — Signed LHP Sebastian Kessay.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed INF Cesar Valera.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA CHAMPIONS — Signed RHP Steve Borkowski and released LHP Carlos Gil.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed INF Danny Mateo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">SCHAUMBURG BOOMERS — Signed LHP Gunnar Kines and INF Jack Parenty to contract extensions.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Signed RHP Kyle Tinius to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Signed UTL Josh Lavender.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WILD THINGS — Signed INF Brett Marr.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Suspended Orlando G Arron Afflalo two games for fighting with Minnesota F Nemanja Bjelica during a Jan. 16 game.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">OAKLAND RAIDERS — Named Derrick Ansley defensive backs coach, Edgar Bennett wide receivers coach, Tim Berbenich quality control-offense coach, Tom Cable offensive line coach, Nick Holz quality control-offense, David Lippincott linebackers coach, Jim O'Neil senior defensive assistant coach, Dave Razzano director of football research coach, Jemal Singleton running backs coach, Frank Smith tight ends coach, Travis Smith quality control-defense coach, Byron Storer assistant special teams coach and Mike Trgovac defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH STEELERS — Named Randy Fichtner offensive coordinator.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Signed QBs Josh Straughan and Philip Nelson; DL Sam Montgomery and Chris Casher; DB Zavian Bingham, WR Garry Brown and RB Zach Bauman.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned D Mirco Mueller to Binghamton (AHL) on a conditioning assignment.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Announced G Eamon McAdam was reassigned to the team from Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed F Shawn O'Donnell to a professional tryout agreement.</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled D Tommy Vannelli from Tulsa (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">MLS — Announced the Professional Referee Organization named Howard Webb general manager.</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Acquired D Emiliano Amor on a one-year loan from Velez Sarsfield (Argentina).</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA FURY FC — Signed M Kevin Oliveira.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALABAMA — Named Jeff Banks special teams coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">AUBURN — Named Allen Greene athletic director.</p><p xmlns="">COLGATE — Named Traci Vandegrift assistant volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">MEMPHIS — Named Sean Burdette volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE STATE — Named Josh Thiel deputy director of athletics for athletics advancement.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RIO GRANDE VALLEY — Announced men's junior basketball F Ndene Gueye has transferred from St. Bonaventure.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>