<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="9c7de57a-900f-4017-88f9-f22381dd6854" userId="2018248" userName="avusa\pklgn4bck" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'User avusa\pklgn4bck does not have permission to create story in folder '/Wires/Reuters_Texts' (id: 1787) (ERR1330)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="56ad063c-d867-4cb3-a7e3-12f9d8561d97" priority="medium" xmlns:rt="http://iptc.org/std/nar/2006-10-01/" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:fn="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Xslt" xmlns:x="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns=""><rights><ref><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></ref></rights><sourceRef><keyVal>Reuters</keyVal></sourceRef><sourceId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G317:988845638</sourceId><followId>tag:reuters.com,2019:newsml_L5N26G317:988845638</followId><sourceFileName>2019-09-25T114019Z_988845638_L5N26G317_RTRMADT_0_THOMAS-COOK-GRP-INVESTMENT-NORDICS-UPDATE-1-PIX.XML</sourceFileName><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/Reuters_Texts</keyVal></folderRef><title>UPDATE 1-Flights disrupted at Thomas Cook's Nordic arm as it battles to survive</title><summary>THOMAS COOK GRP-INVESTMENT/NORDICS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Flights disrupted at Thomas Cook's Nordic arm as it battles to survive</summary><xmlText><p>UPDATE 1-Flights disrupted at Thomas Cook's Nordic arm as it battles to survive</p><p>* Thomas Cook's Nordic unit is separate legal entity</p><p>* But some licences remain with parent company</p><p>* Some flights delayed, cancelled (Adds number of planes affected, background, cancelled Norwegian flight)</p><p>By Andreas Mortensen and Anne Kauranen</p><p>COPENHAGEN/HELSINKI, Sept 25 (Reuters) - Several flights operated by Thomas Cook's Nordic business have been cancelled or delayed as the subsidiary battles to survive the collapse of its parent company earlier this week.</p><p>Three planes operated by Thomas Cook Scandinavian Airlines have not been able to take off because their leasing contracts remained with the British parent, Danish subsidiary Spies said.</p><p>"When you remove a subsidiary from its parent company as brutally as it happened Sunday night, there will be some loose ends afterwards," said Spies spokeswoman Lisbeth Nedergaard.</p><p>"Right now, one loose end is the leasing contracts of some of our planes. Some were leased through our parent company and subleased to us, others were the opposite."</p><p>Nedergaard said the three aircraft without licences were based in Helsinki in Finland, Vaxjo in Sweden and Trondheim in Norway. Dialogue over leasing contracts was ongoing, she added.</p><p>Among the disruptions, a flight from Palma de Mallorca to Helsinki was cancelled on Tuesday, according to Finnish airport operator Finavia, while a flight from Helsinki to Palma de Mallorca due to leave at 1740 local time eventually flew at 2347. A flight from Finland to Croatia was also cancelled early on Wednesday, just before boarding was about to begin.</p><p>In Norway, an overnight Trondheim-Antalya flight was cancelled, though a Trondheim-Rhodes flight was scheduled to leave on Wednesday, with an 80 minute delay.</p><p>Thomas Cook's Nordic business said on Monday it would continue to operate as it is a separate legal entity from its parent, and it was looking for new owners.</p><p>Meanwhile, Thomas Cook's German tour business filed for insolvency on Wednesday in a move aimed at separating its brands and operations from its failed parent, and said it was in talks with potential new investors.</p><p>On Tuesday, the German government said it would guarantee a 380 million euro ($419 million) bridging loan Thomas Cook's German airline, Condor.</p><p>The Nordic business consists of two legal entities, Thomas Cook Northern Europe and Thomas Cook Scandinavian Airlines, and is also known as Ving Group. The business operates under several brands: Ving in Norway, Spies in Denmark, Tjareborg in Finland, as well as Ving and Globetrotter in Sweden.</p><p>Tjareborg said in a statement that "operations continue normally from Tuesday September 24 onwards. Business as usual".</p><p>Hundreds of thousands of holidaymakers were stranded by the collapse of London-based Thomas Cook, the world's oldest travel firm.</p><p>Close to 35,000 holidaymakers from the Nordics were travelling with the company at the time of the announcement.</p><p>($1 = 0.9093 euros) (Additional reporting by Tommy Lund in Gdansk; Writing by Gwladys Fouche in Oslo; Editing by Mark Potter)</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal>XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>