<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="94bfbae3-16a2-4a13-bd78-c702372792f7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0441</summary><sourceId>9112bedc-3f12-4b3e-b3e9-42825f04d94c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2916%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0441</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agreed to terms with RHP Chris Tillman on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">BOSTON RED SOX — Traded OF Bryce Brentz to Pittsburgh for cash considerations.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT TIGERS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Sandy Baez, Michael Fulmer, Eduardo Jimenez, Joe Jimenez, Gerson Moreno, Zac Reininger, Warwick Saupold and Spencer Turnbull, LHPs Chad Bell, Matthew Boyd, Jairo Labourt, Gregory Soto and Daniel Stumpf, INFs Dawel Lugo and Dixon Machado and OFs Mike Gerber and JaCoby Jones on one-year contracts.</p><p xmlns="">HOUSTON ASTROS — Named Mark Zarthar president of Fayetteville (Carolina).</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with RHP Anibal Sanchez on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY RAYS — Traded DH Corey Dickerson to Pittsburgh for RHP Daniel Hudson, INF Tristan Gray and cash.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">FARGO-MOORHEAD REDHAWKS — Traded RHP Carlos Pimentel to Cleburne for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX CITY EXPLORERS — Signed INF Nate Samson. Traded INF Tanner Vavra, INF Joel Davis and OF Jayce Ray to Sussex County (Can-Am) for INF Jay Baum.</p><p xmlns="">ST. PAUL SAINTS — Signed INF Josh Allen.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed RHP Dennis O'Grady.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">TROIS-RIVIERES AIGLES — Signed RHP Yender Caramo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">FLORENCE FREEDOM — Signed 2B Angelo Gumbs.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Traded OF Nolan Meadows to New Jersey (Can-Am) for a player to be named. Signed INF Dan Kennon.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Signed C Jake Simpson.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Signed G Antonius Cleveland to a 10-day contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">AGUA CALIENTE CLIPPERS — Acquired 2018 first- and third-round draft picks, the returning player rights to F-C Micheal Eric and G Tu Holloway from Texas for F Cory Jefferson, a 2018 fourth-round draft pick and the returning player rights to G Cameron Ayers.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">INDIANAPOLIS COLTS — Signed K Adam Vinatieri to a one-year contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Signed G Darcy Kuemper to a two-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Recalled RW Josh Jooris from Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Assigned F Dylan Sadowy and D Patrick McCarron from Grand Rapids (AHL) to Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled G Jack Campbell from Ontario (AHL). Assigned F Michael Mersch and D Paul LaDue to Ontario.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled F Vinni Lettieri from Hartford (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">AHL</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Iowa D Hunter Warner one game for a kneeing incident in a game vs. Texas on Feb. 19.</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Recalled F Dan DeSalvo from Tulsa (ECHL). Traded F Eric Selleck to Belleville for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled F Julien Nantel and D Nolan De Jong from Colorado (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED — Signed MF Oliver Shannon.</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO RAPIDS — Signed F Niki Jackson to a one year contract.</p><p xmlns="">FC DALLAS — Signed G Kyle Zobeck.</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES FC — Signed D Tristan Blackmon.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA UNITED — Acquired MF Luiz Fernando on loan from Fluminense FC (Brazil) for the 2018 season.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RED BULLS — Named Carlo Acquista assistant scout.</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Signed D/MF Brad Evans to a one-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALABAMA — Promoted Mike Locksley to offensive coordinator and Josh Tupoi to defensive coordinator. Named Dan Enos quarterbacks coach and Craig Kuligowski defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">RUTGERS — Named Noah Joseph co-defensive coordinator and safeties coach and Cory Robinston cornerbacks coach and pass game coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>