<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="cf5723d9-ffab-5cb1-e5bb-1a6c88df1758" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Mark Zeigler</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-OLY-SBD-JACOBELLIS:SD — sports, itop (700 words)</title><summary>PYEONGCHANG, South Korea — Lindsey Jacobellis flew off the final jump, landed cleanly and charged ahead. The finish line was in sight. The medals podium was in sight.Suddenly, France’s Chloe Trespeuch, to her right and slightly ahead of her,...</summary><sourceId>350b17be-1659-7ba5-ba51-e303a60599c2</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3978%kniht%r%BC-OLY-SBD-JACOBELLIS:SD — sports, itop (700 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Jacobellis doesn’t crash but she doesn’t medal, either</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Mark Zeigler</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">PYEONGCHANG, South Korea — Lindsey Jacobellis flew off the final jump, landed cleanly and charged ahead. The finish line was in sight. The medals podium was in sight.</p><p xmlns="">Suddenly, France’s Chloe Trespeuch, to her right and slightly ahead of her, twisted awkwardly in the air and wobbled when her snowboard hit the ground. And fell.</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis nimbly veered left and swerved around Trespeuch, avoiding her fate of the previous three Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">She didn’t crash. But, in a cruel twist of fate that only snowboard cross seems capable of delivering, it probably cost her a medal – finishing fourth by three-hundreds of a second and perpetuating her tortured run of Olympic failures.</p><p xmlns="">“Fourth place is fourth place,” Jacobellis said, trying (and generally succeeding) to put a happy face on the day. “It is what it is … I mean, I could be upset about it, but where is that going to get me?”</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis, you might remember, was famously leading the 2006 final by a staggering three seconds when she thought it would be fun to try a showboat method grab on the penultimate jump. She crashed, and a Swiss rider zoomed past her for the gold.</p><p xmlns="">Four years later in Vancouver, she swerved to avoid another rider and crashed through a gate. In 2014, she led the semifinal by a wide margin when she crashed on a lumpy section near the bottom and finished last.</p><p xmlns="">Here, she has no crashes … but avoiding one keeps her off the podium.</p><p xmlns="">“If I didn’t really have that, I could have snuck in for a medal,” said Jacobellis, who recently moved from Encinitas to Laguna Niguel. “But, you know, at the end of the day I want to stay safe and not blow my knee.”</p><p xmlns="">Italy’s 22-year-old Michela Moioli won, followed by France’s Julia Pereira de Sousa Mabileau and defending champion Eva Samkova of the Czech Republic. Trespeuch slid across the line in fifth.</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis got what racers call a “hole shot,” rocketing through the field at the start to take an early lead. She held it for the first half of the twisting, treacherous course but knew it was a double-edged sword.</p><p xmlns="">Knew she eventually would be passed, which she was.</p><p xmlns="">“Unfortunately, on this course you don’t really want to get the hole shot because somebody is going to draft you,” Jacobellis said. “That’s kind of the risk you take, because you (also) don’t want to be stuck in traffic. I just tried to stay in the mix and look for opportunities to pass back again, and it didn’t really pan out.</p><p xmlns="">“We kind of ran out of course.”</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis slipped to second, then third, then fourth, then fifth entering the final jump.</p><p xmlns="">But she was gaining speed off the jump and appeared to have drawn even with Samkova to her far right, maybe even edged ahead of her.</p><p xmlns="">Then Trespeuch tumbled, Jacobellis swerved, and the photo finish showed her board just inches behind Samkova’s.</p><p xmlns="">Welcome to snowboard cross.</p><p xmlns="">“I finished the best I could today,” Jacobellis said. “If we ran the race tomorrow, it could be a whole different story. It’s the winner of this day. It doesn’t define me as an athlete. I’ve been doing this sport for 20 years, and that’s a lot longer than some of these girls have been alive.”</p><p xmlns="">She is 32 now, winner of five World Championships, 10 X Games and 29 World Cup races.</p><p xmlns="">And only one Winter Games medal, and one that history remembers as maybe the greatest blunder in Olympic history.</p><p xmlns="">The question of legacy is a complicated one for everybody except Jacobellis.</p><p xmlns="">“I just view the Olympics as another (event),” Jacobellis said. “I think it’s because most of the time people jump in and they see the sport once every four years, so of course, that’s how they would define me. But it’s not how you should be defined because there are plenty of other athletes who have never acquired that Olympic gold, but still keep qualifying and still keep coming back.</p><p xmlns="">“Because what are they truly? They’re Olympic contenders, they’re Olympic athletes. They’re role models and someone who wants to give back to the sport.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000040194,t000003183,t000003669</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>