<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ebe38bcf-999d-42fe-32f2-53a9a6719dd5" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kevin Acee</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER-S-MYERS:SD — sports (350 words)</title><summary>Wil Myers readily embraced the role of team leader last season. It was something he didn’t seek but was thrust upon him by virtue of a big contract signed in January and his relative seniority among a young team’s position players.No one can...</summary><sourceId>67b32366-8fa3-d2d1-2d17-c6ad7dd7e6e6</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7155%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER-S-MYERS:SD — sports (350 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres believe Eric Hosmer’s arrival will be big for Wil Myers</h2><byline xmlns="">By Kevin Acee</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Wil Myers readily embraced the role of team leader last season. It was something he didn’t seek but was thrust upon him by virtue of a big contract signed in January and his relative seniority among a young team’s position players.</p><p xmlns="">No one can truly know the effects of shouldering the expectations Myers so badly wanted to fulfill and also the extra work he put in trying to mentor and lead by example.</p><p xmlns="">But the results on the field were not up to what Myers or the Padres anticipated.</p><p xmlns="">Myers led the team with 30 home runs and 20 stolen bases. But his .243 average and .328 on-base percentage were his lowest in three seasons with the Padres, and those numbers were .200 and .311 over a 99-game stretch from May 5 through Sept. 1.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t feel like I felt any pressure,” Myers said. “I just did not have a very good year last year.”</p><p xmlns="">Still, he appreciates what the arrival of Eric Hosmer will do. And others around the organization and inside the clubhouse, while impressed by Myers’ willingness to take on whatever the team asks of him, believe Myers is due for a big year playing within the new dynamic.</p><p xmlns="">Certainly, protection in the lineup should help. But also, Hosmer’s experience in two World Series (one ring) and embracing of the leadership role will allow Myers to take a step back, leading by example while being more attuned to his own game.</p><p xmlns="">“There’s something to that,” Myers said. “I feel like as a competitor and a professional athlete you still want as much pressure or as much on the line as possible. But any time someone else can help you out with that is a bonus. … Anytime you can have a little less pressure on you, it’s nice.</p><p xmlns="">“The other thing is, I can learn a lot from him. He’s a guy who’s played in a lot of very big games, he’s played deep into the postseason. I think everybody in here can learn from him.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>