<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="12c89cde-0f6f-03db-8cb2-5265cbeb0dfc" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kevin Acee</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER-NUMBER:SD — sports (200 words)</title><summary>PEORIA, Ariz. — Eric Hosmer knew what he wanted to do when he found out his old number was not available with his new team.With No. 35 taken — retired, actually, in honor of former Cy Young winner Randy Jones — Hosmer decided on wearing No. 30 as...</summary><sourceId>e986de39-1c29-1fcf-fcf6-2ccb8c00f5fd</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1405%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER-NUMBER:SD — sports (200 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Eric Hosmer honors former teammate Yordano Ventura with Padres number</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Kevin Acee</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">PEORIA, Ariz. — Eric Hosmer knew what he wanted to do when he found out his old number was not available with his new team.</p><p xmlns="">With No. 35 taken — retired, actually, in honor of former Cy Young winner Randy Jones — Hosmer decided on wearing No. 30 as a Padre.</p><p xmlns="">It is a tribute to former Kansas City Royals teammate Yordano Ventura. The pitcher, who signed with the Royals the same year Hosmer was drafted by that organization, died in January 2017 in an automobile accident in his native Dominican Republic.</p><p xmlns="">Hosmer arrived at the Padres complex on Monday, signed his contract, took his physical and sought out Padres third base coach Glenn Hoffman.</p><p xmlns="">“I told him that it would mean a lot to me if I could wear No. 30 and continue Yordano’s legacy,” Hosmer said Tuesday. “… All those guys in Kansas City, we all shared good moments with him and obviously shared a really tough moment with his passing. It really meant a lot to me. Hoff was more than open to let me carry on that number. Like I told him, I’ll wear it with pride each and every day.”</p><p xmlns="">Hoffman was wearing No. 26 as the Padres took the field for the first full-squad workout later Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>