<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="489fadde-bda7-4631-be12-6849dedc15f7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0572</summary><sourceId>361797a1-7b24-46a1-6a1a-81287d216a18</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0890%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0572</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 16</hl2><p xmlns="">1961 — Elgin Baylor of Los Angeles scores 57 points to lead the Lakers over the Detroit Pistons 129-106.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Rick Barry of the San Francisco Warriors scores 52 points against Chicago at Fresno for his second consecutive 50-point game.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Alex Delvecchio of the Detroit Red Wings gets his 1,000th point with an assist in a 6-3 victory over the Los Angeles Kings.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Joe Frazier retains his world heavyweight title with a fifth-round knockout of Jimmy Ellis.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Los Angeles Lakers becomes the first player in NBA history to reach the 30,000 point mark during a 110-109 loss to the Phoenix Suns.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Martina Navratilova becomes the career singles titles leader by beating Jana Novotna in three sets in the final of the Virginia Slims of Chicago. Navratilova, with her 158th career singles championship, passes Chris Evert, who retired in 1989.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Chicago's Michel Goulet becomes the 17th NHL player to score 500 goals, getting one in the first period of the Blackhawks' 5-5 tie with Calgary.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Jeff Gordon, 25, becomes the youngest winner of the Daytona 500 after Dale Earnhardt crashes 12 laps from the end to prolong his Daytona 500 jinx.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Philadelphia coach Larry Brown earns his 1,000th professional win, including his ABA record. Brown, 1,000-707 overall, ranks third on the career list behind Toronto's Lenny Wilkens and Miami's Pat Riley. Allen Iverson's 42 points leads the 76ers to a 108-93 win over the Los Angeles Clippers.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — The NHL cancels what was left of its decimated schedule after a round of last-gasp negotiations failed to resolve differences over a salary cap — the flash-point issue that led to a lockout. It's the first time a major pro sports league in North America lost an entire season to a labor dispute.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Harness driver Brian Sears drives seven winners on the Presidents Day afternoon card at the Meadowlands. The last driver to win seven races on a 10-race card at the Meadowlands was John Campbell on Feb. 3, 1983.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — American teenager Mikaela Shiffrin becomes the youngest woman in 39 years to win the slalom title at the world alpine championships held in Schladming, Austria. At the age of 17 years, 340 days, Shiffrin edges local hope Michaela Kirchgasser. The only slalom world champions younger than Shiffrin were Hanni Wenzel of Liechtenstein in 1974 and Esme Mackinnon of Britain in 1931.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Carmelo Anthony makes an All-Star record eight 3-pointers and scores 30 points, and the Eastern Conference overcame Kevin Durant, Blake Griffin and the Western Conference for a 163-155 win.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Lowell Bailey upsets the pre-race favorites in the men's individual competition to become the first American biathlete to win gold at the world championships. Bailey's gold is the fourth medal for an American biathlete at the worlds.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Pittsburgh's Sidney Crosby feeds Chris Kunitz for a first-period goal against Winnipeg to become the 86th player in NHL history to reach the 1,000-point plateau. He adds an assist on Phil Kessel's game-tying goal in the third and then puts the winner past Connor Hellebuyck with 21 seconds left in overtime as the Penguins escaped with a 4-3 victory.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>