<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4de2bd3d-34c1-4796-b919-35033fc19555" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0426</summary><sourceId>723a84bf-28ef-4fae-faea-1a259627aed0</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9287%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0426</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Suspended Washington C Raudy Read 80 games without pay after testing positive for Boldenone, a performance-enhancing substance, in violation of Major League Baseball's Joint Drug Prevention and Treatment Program.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Myles Jaye, Michael Kohn and Jake Reed; Cs Willians Astudillo, Brian Navarreto and Bobby Wilson; INFs Taylor Featherston, Nick Gordon, Gregorio Petit and Brock Stassi; and OFs Nick Buss, Ryan LaMarre and LaMonte Wade on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Traded INF Russell Wilson to the New York Yankees for future considerations. Named Josiah Igono major league director of peak performance; Brett Hayes major league advance scout; Randy Smith and Al Hargesheimer pro scouts; Casey Fox assistant, player development; Eric Gagne pitching coach for Arizona League Rangers, Don Kalkstein senior advisor and Andrew Koo analyst, baseball operations.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Agreed to terms with 3B Todd Frazier on a two-year contract. Designated INF Matt Reynolds for assignment.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">ROAD WARRIORS — Named Ellie Rodriguez manager and Rafael Montalvo pitching coach.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">EVANSVILLE OTTERS — Signed C Dillon Kelley.</p><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed RHP Ashton Bueter and RHP Kane McCall.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed RHP Louis Cohen and RHP Joe Costello.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed INF/OF Scott Dwyer and RHP Kuehl McEachern.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES CLIPPERS — Agreed in terms with G Lou Williams on a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK KNICKS — Traded C Willy Hernangomez to Charlotte for 2020 and 2021 second-round draft picks and F Johnny O'Bryant.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND BROWNS — Named Sam Shade assistant special teams coach.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT LIONS — Named David Corrao director of football research, Paul Pasqualoni defensive coordinator, Jeff Davidson offensive line coach, George Godsey quarterbacks coach, Al Golden linebackers coach, Brian Stewart defensive backs coach and Chris White tight ends coach.</p><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO 49ERS — Re-signed DL Cassius Marsh to a two-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Assigned D Kyle Capobianco to Tucson (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Announced commissioner Brain McKenna will be leaving the league this summer.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">MLS PLAYERS ASSOCIATION — Named Dan Jones chief operating officer.</p><p xmlns="">FC DALLAS — Renewed its affiliation agreement with Oklahoma City Energy FC (USL) for the 2018 season.</p><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SOUNDERS FC — Acquired $50,000 in general allocation money from D.C. United for D Oniel Fisher.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ARMADA — Agreed to terms with D Kalen Ryden, Fs Ciaran Kilduff and Derek Gebhard and MF J.C. Banks.</p><hl2 xmlns="">TENNIS</hl2><p xmlns="">ITF — Reduced the ban on Ilie Nastase by eight months and doubled his fine to $20,000 following his appeal of sanctions for foul-mouthed comments and misconduct as the Romanian Fed Cup captain.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">METRO ATLANTIC ATHLETIC CONFERENCE — Named Phil Paquette director of new media/communications.</p><p xmlns="">MOUNTAIN WEST — Suspended New Mexico senior F Joe Furstinger one game and issued a public reprimand to Boise State sophomore G Justinian Jessup for their actions in a men's basketball game Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">CLEMSON — Announced RB C.J. Fuller is transferring.</p><p xmlns="">FORDHAM — Named Paul Rice defensive coordinator, Vincent Natali offensive line coach/recruiting coordinator, and Scott Vallone defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">GEORGIA — Rehired assistant football coach Scott Fountain. Named Cortez Hankton assistant football coach</p><p xmlns="">GEORGIA TECH — Announced the resignation of men's assistant basketball coach Darryl LaBarrie.</p><p xmlns="">RUTGERS — Named Nunzio Campanile running backs coach.</p><p xmlns="">WISCONSIN — Named Bobby April III outside linebacker coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>