<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4a25b0b7-0c3f-4b4c-b511-facc1eb587d8" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0164</summary><sourceId>2d7dbe18-44bc-481a-81aa-5781ce22ff6d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1400%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0164</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with C Ryan Hanigan on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Agreed to terms with LHP Jaime Garcia on a one-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI REDS — Voided the contract of RHP Jeff Manship. Agreed to terms with INF Cliff Pennington on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Named Daniel Fumai chief financial officer. Agreed to a minor league contract with LHP Wade Miley.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Agreed to terms with OF Matt den Dekker to a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">Frontier League</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Women's National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES SPARKS — Named Michael Fischer assistant general manager.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">NFL — Announced Cincinnati Bengals' QB AJ McCarron has won his arbitration case against and will become an unrestricted free agent.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK GIANTS — Named Mike Shula offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach, Tyke Tolbert wide receivers coach, Hal Hunter offensive line coach, Ben Wilkerson assistant offensive line coach, James Bettcher defensive coordinator, Gary Emanuel defensive line coach, Lou Anarumo defensive backs coach, Deshea Townsend assistant defensive backs coach, Thomas McGaughey special teams coordiantor and Anthony Blevins assistant special teams coach. Retained Craig Johnson running backs coach, Lunda Wells tight ends coach, Ryan Roeder offensive assistant coach, Bill McGovern linebackers coach, Rob Leonard assistant linebackers coach and Bobby Blick defensive assistant coach.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Re-signed RB John White.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Recalled G Jean-Francois Berube from Rockford (AHL). Assigned G Jeff Glass to Rockford. Acquired C Chris DiDomenico from Ottawa for D Pokka and assigned DiDomenico to Rockford.</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Reassigned F Rocco Grimaldi to San Antonio (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Reassigned Fs Brady Shaw and Julien Nantel to Colorado (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">North American Soccer League</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Premier Soccer League</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ALBANY (NY)_Named Kevin Cardoza assistant volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">CHARLESTON SOUTHERN — Named Chad Scott assistant athletic director of student-athlete development and Connor Klekota men's assistant soccer coach.</p><p xmlns="">CITADEL — Named Dave Zelenock women's volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">COASTAL CAROLINA — Named T.J. Hollowell assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">FURMAN — Named Andre' Bernandi director of strength training and conditioning.</p><p xmlns="">HAMPTON — Named Scott McConnell tight ends coach and Hunter Williams director of football operations.</p><p xmlns="">NYU — Named Matt DeMichiel men's and women's assistant tennis coach.</p><p xmlns="">NORTH CAROLINA — Named Luke Paschall assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">SIENA — Named Vilis Ozols volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTH CAROLINA — Named George Wynn director of football operations and Ethan Pheister women's assistant volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS — Fired track coach Mario Sategna.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>