<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="3b0fe635-cc89-5cdc-e453-a2618aabf02e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Greg Moran</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BORDERWALL-SECURITY:SD — national, itop (850 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Warned of possibly violent protests over construction of border wall prototypes last fall, San Diego police bought an array of less than lethal weapons, newly released city records show.Weeks before the project began the city...</summary><sourceId>e9ae05a6-ad3e-5321-3216-e9a499733f04</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K9595%kniht%r%BC-BORDERWALL-SECURITY:SD — national, itop (850 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Rubber bullet grenades and pizza: How San Diego spent $50K for supplies prepping for Trump’s border wall prototypes</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Greg Moran</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Warned of possibly violent protests over construction of border wall prototypes last fall, San Diego police bought an array of less than lethal weapons, newly released city records show.</p><p xmlns="">Weeks before the project began the city purchased hundreds of rounds of pepper spray, as well as crowd-dispersing grenades and tear gas.</p><p xmlns="">In all the city spent $50,000 on supplies, most of which were not needed. There were no protests during the construction.</p><p xmlns="">From Costco pizza and brown bag lunches to dozens of exploding grenades that hurl rubber balls in a 50-foot radius, San Diego police rushed to purchase $50,000 of supplies for security in the areas near President Donald Trump’s border wall prototype project, much of it motivated by concerns for mass demonstrations that never materialized, city records show.</p><p xmlns="">The purchases were ordered and made in the weeks before and just after the Sept. 26 start of construction on eight prototype walls on a patch of federal land near the border on Otay Mesa. The project was ordered by the Trump administration, which has made building a wall on the border a centerpiece of its immigration policies.</p><p xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune reported in January that the city spent $826,354 on security, including about $227,500 in overtime and the balance in wages and supplies. The department was not providing security for the walls but patrolling and securing the area near the build — city streets in an Otay Mesa business park.</p><p xmlns="">The newspaper then requested a breakdown of the $50,000 in supplies as well as other information. Those records produced this week show the extent to which city officials believed they had to prepare — quickly — for possibly large demonstrations against the project.</p><p xmlns="">Department of Homeland Security officials had warned of large scale and potentially violent protests in a memo to local agencies before the project began.</p><p xmlns="">That memo, which has not been made public but was reported on by The Wall Street Journal, clearly drove decisions by the police and San Diego County Sheriff’s Department, which also secured and patrolled the area and spent $1.6 million in salaries, overtime and supplies</p><p xmlns="">For example, on Sept. 12, the police department requested $25,000 to purchase meals for the expected month-long project duration — an initial amount that officials said could go much higher.</p><p xmlns="">“We may need to increase this depending on how the protests go as costs could rise to $100,000 or higher,” a management analyst wrote that day.</p><p xmlns="">After a week it became apparent that there would be no protests and the city reduced manpower. In the end it ended up spending $5,778 on food, including 350 sack lunches and about two dozen pizzas one day.</p><p xmlns="">The largest expenditure category was ammunition and the records show the city bought an array of less-than-lethal tactical gear and ammunition. It included 750 rounds of pepper spray projectiles that can be fired from special launchers.</p><p xmlns="">The city also bought 100 chemical grenades that spray out CS gas, commonly known as tear gas, as well as 50 grenades that spew out rubber pellets when detonated to deter and disperse large crowds, according to the manufacturer, Defense Technologies.</p><p xmlns="">“Psychologically and physiologically maximize less-lethal force against the most stubborn of crowds,” a product description reads. “Stinger Rubber Ball Grenade offers multiple stimulus of light, sound, rubber pellets and optional CN or CS chemical agents. Grenades detonate in a 50-foot circular pattern, spraying rubber pellets with micro-pulverized chemical agent.”</p><p xmlns="">Police officials said that the equipment is used by SWAT teams and the city does not have enough on hand.</p><p xmlns="">“Our current inventory of munitions will not meet the demands of a long sustained and violent protest,” Capt. Rudy Tai of the Operational Support Division wrote in a Sept. 6 memo requesting the equipment.</p><p xmlns="">The city ended up spending $33,969 on ammunition and tactical gear, the records show.</p><p xmlns="">Concern over the protest also drove the sheriff’s department, which not only spent $764,278 for more than 10,000 hours of overtime logged by 356 employees from Sept. 7 through Dec. 15 in border wall related costs, but also installed two miles of temporary chain link fencing to block off private and some county property.</p><p xmlns="">The county got an exemption from environmental laws for installing the temporary fencing, and gave a similar reason saying the fencing would stop trampling on environmentally sensitive land “given the high likelihood a significant number of people will be demonstrating,” county officials wrote in a formal notice.</p><p xmlns="">“The construction of these mock-up, which is expected to commence imminently, is highly controversial and is expected to result in demonstrations by a significant number of individuals. The temporary fence is critical to preventing injury to persons and property during the course of these expected demonstrations, and will be removed once this imminent danger abates,” the notice says.</p><p xmlns="">Despite all the concern, there was no protest during the building, and only a small rally near the site on Dec. 9, weeks after the walls were constructed and long after construction crews had left.</p><p xmlns="">Both city and county officials have said that they will not be reimbursed by the federal government for the costs of securing the area for the prototype project.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000015420,t000002953,t000015422,t000002537,t000002676,t000032200</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>