<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6bc1b925-0ee2-833d-8071-1421be61807d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jeff Sanders</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-OUTFIELD:SD — sports (700 words)</title><summary>The weekend began with seven outfielders competing for the two outfield spots that did not belong to Manuel Margot. The arrival of a new first baseman (you heard the Eric Hosmer news, right?) changes things quite a bit for that group this...</summary><sourceId>21c46fc1-8cda-a9f0-9f0e-709b1fc7abfa</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K2779%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-OUTFIELD:SD — sports (700 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres outfield battle to intensify as Myers leaves first base to Hosmer</h2><byline xmlns="">By Jeff Sanders</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">The weekend began with seven outfielders competing for the two outfield spots that did not belong to Manuel Margot. The arrival of a new first baseman (you heard the Eric Hosmer news, right?) changes things quite a bit for that group this spring.</p><p xmlns="">Wil Myers is now a corner outfielder. A fight for the other spot is about to begin.</p><p xmlns="">And third-year Padres manager Andy Green couldn’t be more excited about that development.</p><p xmlns="">“You have a lot of guys fighting for not necessarily a ton of at-bats and I think that’s good,” Green said Sunday morning. “It’s good for our culture. It’s good for our clubhouse to know that, ‘Hey, I’ve got to perform if I want to play for the Padres. Because if not there’s someone else knocking on that door.’ I think the more competitive we can make it to get at-bats on the roster, the better we’re going to be.”</p><p xmlns="">It doesn’t get more competitive than this.</p><p xmlns="">Jose Pirela was previously viewed as the front-runner for starts in left field. With Myers likely seeing time in both left and right field, he’ll have to hold off Hunter Renfroe, Alex Dickerson, Franchy Cordero, Travis Jankowski and Matt Szczur to secure his first opening day job.</p><p xmlns="">Jankowski and Szczur are likely competing for bench jobs while the other outfielder in camp, Franmil Reyes, is here to learn as he prepares for his first year at Triple-A El Paso.</p><p xmlns="">Platoons, meanwhile, may help Green sort through everything this spring.</p><p xmlns="">The right-handed-hitting Renfroe hit a franchise rookie-record 26 homers in 2017, but his splits sagged against right-handed pitching (.636 OPS) compared to left-handers (1.077 OPS). Cordero, a left-handed hitter, posted a 1.054 OPS against right-handers last year at Triple-A El Paso. The left-handed Dickerson, who is coming off back surgery, is also traditionally better against right-handers (.806 OPS) than lefties (.694 OPS).</p><p xmlns="">Of course, Pirela is coming off the best season of all of them after pairing a .288/.347/.490 batting line with 10 homers and 40 RBIs over 83 games, his first extended playing opportunity. The right-handed hitter’s ability to play second base — where two left-handed hitters (Cory Spangenberg and Carlos Asuaje) are vying for starts — will give Green even more options to consider as he rounds out the 25-man roster.</p><p xmlns="">“Maybe take advantage of the fact,” Green said, “that maybe Hunter Renfroe crushes left-handed pitching or maybe Franchy Cordero crushes right-handed pitching. Or Alex Dickerson crushes right-handed pitching. That lets maybe Jose Pirela bounce into second base where you have two left-handed-hitting second basemen. Spring training is to iron that all out.”</p><p xmlns="">It’s also the first look at Myers in an outfield spot since 2016. He played 10 games in corner spots there after starting 2015 as the Padres’ Opening Day center fielder.</p><p xmlns="">Advanced metrics have been unkind to Myers’ profile beyond the infield (minus-16 defensive runs saved over 1,715 2/3 innings), but Green believes his athleticism will translate well there with enough reps.</p><p xmlns="">At 28.6 feet per second, Myers’ sprint speed in 2017 rated as the best of all first basemen, according to StatCast. Overall, that number ranked 53rd in the majors last year.</p><p xmlns="">“He’s as athletic as anyone in Major League Baseball,” Green said. “You don’t hit 30 home runs or steal 20 bases if you’re not. He can fly. He wants to challenge Travis Jankowski to a race again. He brings that up every single year. He wants to be the fastest guy in camp. He’s got plenty of speed to play literally anywhere on the baseball field. I don’t think anything is going to be a real challenge for him.”</p><p xmlns="">Myers certainly seems unfazed by the position change as he brings an outfield glove to camp.</p><p xmlns="">He’s bigger than last year, having gained about 20 pounds. He’s in a better state of mind after offseason time with a sports psychologist following last year’s slump-prone campaign. He’s ready to welcome Hosmer into the fold with open arms.</p><p xmlns="">“I do love first base,” Myers said. “It’s something I really enjoy playing, but I would rather have a guy like that here than to play first base. … I’m happy to move out of position to have a guy like that here.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000424479,t000007391,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>