<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="70f8e144-ff6f-47f6-8e53-eea8143874b3" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV10</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV10,3747</summary><sourceId>5f061ae4-8211-4d42-d42b-850ab7efa8e9</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1321%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV10;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV10</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV10,3747</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv10</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend, Feb. 10-11</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 11</hl2><p xmlns="">1878 — The Boston Bicycle Club, the first bicycle club in the United States, is formed.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Willie Pep becomes the first boxer in the history of the 126-pound class to regain a lost championship with a 15-round unanimous decision over Sandy Saddler at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1957 — The NHL Players Association is formed and Ted Lindsay of the Detroit Red Wings is elected president.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — The Atlanta Hawks score 97 points, the most ever scored in the second half of an NBA game, en route to a 155-131 win at San Diego.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Montreal's Jean Beliveau scores his 500th goal in the Canadiens' 6-2 victory over the Minnesota North Stars.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — The Philadelphia 76ers lose to the Los Angeles Lakers 108-90 to set an NBA record for the most consecutive losses in a season at 20.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Houston Rockets center Moses Malone grabs an NBA-record 21 offensive rebounds in a 117-100 win over Seattle.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Mike Tyson loses for the first time when James "Buster" Douglas knocks him out in the 10th round and captures the heavyweight championship in one of the biggest upsets in boxing history.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Anfissa Reztsova wins the women's 7.5-kilometer biathlon event to become the first woman to get gold medals in two different Winter Olympic sports. She skied the final 5-kilometer leg on the Soviet Union's winning 20K cross-country relay team in the 1988 Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Allen Iverson and Stephon Marbury lead an improbable comeback to give the Eastern Conference a thrilling 111-110 NBA All-Star victory. Iverson scores 15 of his 25 points in the final nine minutes, and Marbury hits two 3-pointers in the final 53 seconds to help the East come back from a 21-point deficit.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Anja Paerson captures the downhill, becoming the first skier to win gold medals in all five disciplines at the world championships. Paerson, who also won the super-G and combined titles earlier in the week, won gold medals in the giant slalom at the last two worlds and one in the slalom in 2001.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — The Cleveland Cavaliers stopped their NBA-record losing streak at 26 games with a 126-119 win in overtime against the Los Angeles Clippers. Antawn Jamison scores 35 points and makes the game's biggest basket, a 3-pointer with 22 seconds left in OT for the Cavs.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 12</hl2><p xmlns="">1937 — Cleveland is granted an NFL franchise. The Rams play in Cleveland for nine years before moving to Los Angeles. After the 1994 season, the Rams move to St. Louis.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Boston's Bill Russell scores 18 points and grabs 41 rebounds to lead the Celtics to a 119-101 victory over the Syracuse Nationals.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Jean-Claude Killy of France wins the men's giant slalom in the Winter Olympics at Grenoble, his second gold medal en route to the Alpine triple crown.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — The Soviet Union ice hockey team wins the gold medal with a 5-2 victory over Czechoslovakia at the Winter Olympics. The United States is awarded the silver because it had beaten and tied Czechoslovakia.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Loy Allen Jr. becomes the first Winston Cup rookie to win a pole in the Daytona 500. Allen is .031 seconds quicker than six-time NASCAR Winston Cup champion Dale Earnhardt.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Morocco's Hicham el Guerrouj breaks indoor track's oldest record, winning the mile in 3 minutes, 48.45 at the Flanders meet held in Ghent, Belgium. Ireland's Eamonn Coghlan ran 3:49.78 in 1983 in New York.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Allen Iverson scores 60 points, a career high, to lead the Philadelphia 76ers to a 112-99 victory over the Orlando Magic.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Duke, saddled by its first four-game losing skid in 11 years, falls out of The Associated Press men's poll for the first time since the end of the 1995-96 season. The Blue Devils had been in the media poll for 200 straight weeks — the second longest streak behind UCLA's record 221 weeks.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — American Hannah Kearney wins her 15th straight World Cup moguls event at the World Cup event in Beida Lake, China. Kearney breaks downhill great Ingemar Stenmark's all-discipline record for consecutive FIS World Cup victories. Stenmark won 14 straight giant slaloms in 1978-80. Kearney's streak began in Lake Placid, N.Y., on Jan. 22, 2011.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — LeBron James becomes the first player in NBA history to score 30 points and shoot at least 60 percent in six straight games as the Miami Heat hold off the Portland Trail Blazers 117-104. James scores 30 points on 11 for 15 shooting.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Tina Maze of Slovenia and Dominique Gisin of Switzerland tie for gold in the Olympic women's downhill. Both speed down the Rosa Khutor course in 1:41.57 seconds for the first gold-medal tie in Olympic alpine skiing history.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 13</hl2><p xmlns="">1923 — The New York Renaissance, the first all-black pro basketball team, is organized. Rens become one of the dominant basketball team of the 1920s and 1930s.</p><p xmlns="">1937 — Maribel Vinson wins her ninth and final U.S. figure skating singles championship. Robin Lee wins his third straight men's title.</p><p xmlns="">1937 — The NFL Redskins move from Boston to Washington.</p><p xmlns="">1948 — Dick Button, the Olympic gold medalist, beats Hans Gerschwiler again to win the men's World Figure Skating championship in Davos, Switzerland.</p><p xmlns="">1954 — Furman's Frank Selvey scores 100 points in a 149-95 victory over Newberry. Selvey breaks the record of 73 points, set by Temple's Bill Mlkvy in 1951, with 41 field goals and 18 free throws.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — Frank Mahovlich of the Montreal Canadiens scores his 1,000th career point with an assist in a 7-6 loss to the Philadelphia Flyers.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Julius Erving, playing in his first NBA All-Star Game, is voted MVP, despite his East team losing 125-124. Erving scores 30 points and grabs 12 rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Bryan Trottier of the New York Islanders becomes the 15th player in NHL history to reach the 500-goal mark, scoring in the second period of a 4-2 loss to the Calgary Flames.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Tommy Moe wins the men's downhill over local hero Kjetil Andre Aamodt at the Winter Olympics in Lillehammer, Norway. Moe won by .04 seconds, the closest Alpine race in Olympic history. Norwegian speed skater Johann Olav Koss has a world record-setting gold medal performance in the 5,000 meters in 6 minutes, 34.96 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Connecticut is voted No. 1 in The Associated Press Top 25 and joins the school's women's team at the top. It is the first time teams from one school were ranked No. 1 in the men's and women's college basketball polls.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Steve Jaros rolls the 13th televised 300 game in PBA history en route to winning the Chattanooga Open.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — In St. Anton, Austria, Fritz Strobl and Werner Franz finish with identical times of 1 minute, 20.72 seconds to win an icy and treacherous super-G, the second tie in World Cup history.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Teresa Phillips becomes the first woman to coach a men's Division I team, but her presence couldn't stop Tennessee State from losing for the 17th straight time, 71-56 at Austin Peay.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Ted Ligety wins the giant slalom at world championships held at Beaver Creek, Colo. Ligety defeats Austrian rival Marcel Hirscher by 0.45 seconds, to attain his third straight world giant slalom title.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Gabby Williams scores a career-high 26 points and Napheesa Collier adds 18 to help top-ranked UConn to its 100th consecutive victory with a 66-55 win over No. 6 South Carolina.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Kawhi Leonard scores 32 points and San Antonio clinches its NBA-record 20th consecutive winning season with a 110-106 victory over Indiana. The Spurs improve to 42-13 in the season following Tim Duncan's retirement. They have had a winning record every season since 1997-98, when Duncan was a rookie, and breaks a tie with the Utah Jazz, who had 19 straight winning seasons from 1985-2004.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 14</hl2><p xmlns="">1936 — Maribel Vinson wins her eighth U.S. figure skating singles championship and Robin Lee wins his second consecutive men's title.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Sugar Ray Robinson wins the middleweight title with a technical knockout in the 13th round over Jake LaMotta in Chicago.</p><p xmlns="">1953 — Bill Chambers of William &amp; Mary grabs 51 rebounds in a 105-84 victory over Virginia.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Philadelphia's Wilt Chamberlain scores 41 points in a 149-123 win over Detroit to become the NBA's all-time scoring leader, passing Bob Pettit (20,880 points).</p><p xmlns="">1975 — Julius Erving of the New York Nets scores 63 points in a 176-166 quadruple overtime loss to the San Diego Conquistadors. Erving sets an ABA record by shooting 25-for-46 from the field and the 342 points are an ABA record.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Philadelphia's Al Hill sets a record for most points in an NHL debut with five points — two goals and three assists — in a 6-4 victory over the St. Louis Blues.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Bobby Allison outduels his 26-year-old son Davey to win the Daytona 500 and becomes the first 50-year-old to win NASCAR's premier event.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Bonnie Blair becomes the first American woman in 40 years to win two gold medals in the Winter Olympics when she takes the 1,000-meter speed skating event. Toni Nieminen, 16, becomes the youngest male Winter Olympic champion ever, leading Finland to the team ski jumping title. He's a day younger than American bobsledder Bill Fiske was in 1928.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Mississippi wins on Kentucky's homecourt for the first time since 1927 with a 73-64 victory. It's the Rebels' first win in 20 games in Rupp Arena and the second in 45 contests at Kentucky.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Anaheim's Sergei Fedorov is the first Russian-born player to collect 1,000 points with an assist on Keith Carney's goal in the second period of the Ducks' 2-1 win over Vancouver.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Savannah State is 0-for-the-season, becoming the second NCAA Division I school in a half-century to go through an entire season without a win, losing to Florida A&amp;M 49-44 to finish 0-28.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — In Vancouver, British Columbia, an American breaks through the Nordic combined barrier, winning the first Olympic medal in the sport dominated since its inception by the Europeans. Jason Lamy Chappuis of France overtakes American Johnny Spillane on the final straightaway for the gold medal, winning four-tenths of a second ahead of Spillane.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The Eastern Conference edges the West 141-139 in the NBA All-Star game before the largest crowd ever to watch a basketball game. A crowd of 108,713 at Cowboys Stadium watches Dwyane Wade score 28 points and take MVP honors before Dallas native Chris Bosh makes the winning free throws with 5.0 seconds left.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Sailing's America's Cup, once again, belongs to America after Larry Ellison's space-age trimaran easily speeds ahead of two-time defending champion Alinghi of Switzerland to complete a two-race sweep in the 33rd America's Cup.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Mikaela Shiffrin becomes the third woman to win back-to-back slalom titles at world championships. She finishes in a combined time of 1:38.48, edging Frida Hansdotter of Sweden by 0.34 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — The first NBA All-Star Game outside the U.S. is the highest-scoring ever. Kobe Bryant says his NBA All-Star Game goodbye as the West wins 196-173 at the Air Canada Centre in Toronto. Russell Westbrook scores 31 points in his second straight All-Star MVP performance. Paul George finishes with 41 for the East.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 15</hl2><p xmlns="">1932 — Eddie Eagen, as a member of the four-man U.S. bobsled team, wins a gold medal at the Winter Olympics in Lake Placid, New York. He previously won a gold medal in boxing light heavyweight division at the 1920 Summer Games in Antwerp, Belgium.</p><p xmlns="">1936 — Sonja Henie of Norway, wins her third consecutive Olympics figure skating gold medal in Garmisch-Partenkirchen, Germany.</p><p xmlns="">1952 — Emmett Ashford becomes the first black umpire in organized baseball when he signs to work in the class-C Southwest International League. He later serves as a major league umpire for the American League from 1966 to 1970.</p><p xmlns="">1953 — Tenley Albright becomes the first American woman to win a world figure skating title beating Germany's Gundi Busch at the World Championships in Davos, Switzerland.</p><p xmlns="">1964 — Ken Hubbs, the 22-year-old Chicago Cubs second baseman, dies when his private plane crashes in Utah. The 1962 NL Rookie of the Year had his pilot's license for two weeks and was flying in bad weather.</p><p xmlns="">1974 — Boston's Phil Esposito scores his 1,000th point with an assist in the Bruins' 4-2 victory over the Vancouver Canucks.</p><p xmlns="">1975 — Yvan Cournoyer of the Montreal Canadiens scores five goals and gets two assists in a 12-3 win over the Chicago Blackhawks.</p><p xmlns="">1978 — Leon Spinks wins a 15-round split decision over Muhammad Ali to take the world heavyweight title at Las Vegas.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — Rookie Wayne Gretzky ties the NHL record with seven assists in a game and sets a scoring record for first-year players in Edmonton's 8-2 victory over the Washington Capitals.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Kentucky makes one of the greatest comebacks in college basketball history with a 99-95 victory over LSU after trailing by 31 points with 15:30 to play.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Freshman Ila Borders becomes the first woman to pitch in an NCAA or NAIA game. The left-hander pitches a complete-game for Southern California College, allowing five hits in the Vanguards' 12-1 win over Claremont-Mudd.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Charlie Standish sets a PBA record by rolling three perfect games in the first round of the Peoria Open bowling tournament. Standish rolls the 300s in the second, fourth and sixth games of the six-game round and at one point has 23 consecutive strikes.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Dale Earnhardt takes the Daytona 500 on his 20th try and ends a 59-race winless streak on the day NASCAR begins celebrating its 50th anniversary.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — The worst judging scandal in Winter Olympics history is resolved, with Canadian pairs figure skaters Jamie Sale and David Pelletier declared co-gold medalists with the Russian winners.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Dale Earnhardt Jr. barrels past Tony Stewart to win the Daytona 500 on the same track that claimed his father's life three years ago. Junior wins this race in his fifth try, the same race that bedeviled his later father for 19 years.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — American Seth Wescott defends his Olympic title in Vancouver, British Columbia, overtaking Canada's Mike Robertson to win the gold medal in the wild sport of men's snowboardcross. Didier Defago wins the gold in the Olympic downhill and American Bode Miller breaks his personal streak of major championship mishaps by taking the bronze.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Ted Ligety becomes the first man in 45 years to win three gold medals at a skiing world championships. French great Jean-Claude Killy took home four golds in 1968. Ligety wins the giant slalom by a massive margin for his third gold. Earlier in the championships held in Schladming, Austria, Ligety won the super-G and super-combined — both events he had never won on the World Cup circuit.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Renaud Lavillenie breaks Sergei Bubka's 21-year-old indoor pole vault world record in Donetsk, Ukraine. Lavillenie clears the bar comfortably at 6.16 meters (20 feet, 2 1/2 inches) in Bubka's home city, almost to the day the pole vault great cleared achieved 6.15 (20-2) on Feb. 21, 1993.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 16</hl2><p xmlns="">1961 — Elgin Baylor of Los Angeles scores 57 points to lead the Lakers over the Detroit Pistons 129-106.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Rick Barry of the San Francisco Warriors scores 52 points against Chicago at Fresno for his second consecutive 50-point game.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Alex Delvecchio of the Detroit Red Wings gets his 1,000th point with an assist in a 6-3 victory over the Los Angeles Kings.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Joe Frazier retains his world heavyweight title with a fifth-round knockout of Jimmy Ellis.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Los Angeles Lakers becomes the first player in NBA history to reach the 30,000 point mark during a 110-109 loss to the Phoenix Suns.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Martina Navratilova becomes the career singles titles leader by beating Jana Novotna in three sets in the final of the Virginia Slims of Chicago. Navratilova, with her 158th career singles championship, passes Chris Evert, who retired in 1989.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Chicago's Michel Goulet becomes the 17th NHL player to score 500 goals, getting one in the first period of the Blackhawks' 5-5 tie with Calgary.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Jeff Gordon, 25, becomes the youngest winner of the Daytona 500 after Dale Earnhardt crashes 12 laps from the end to prolong his Daytona 500 jinx.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Philadelphia coach Larry Brown earns his 1,000th professional win, including his ABA record. Brown, 1,000-707 overall, ranks third on the career list behind Toronto's Lenny Wilkens and Miami's Pat Riley. Allen Iverson's 42 points leads the 76ers to a 108-93 win over the Los Angeles Clippers.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — The NHL cancels what was left of its decimated schedule after a round of last-gasp negotiations failed to resolve differences over a salary cap — the flash-point issue that led to a lockout. It's the first time a major pro sports league in North America lost an entire season to a labor dispute.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Harness driver Brian Sears drives seven winners on the Presidents Day afternoon card at the Meadowlands. The last driver to win seven races on a 10-race card at the Meadowlands was John Campbell on Feb. 3, 1983.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — American teenager Mikaela Shiffrin becomes the youngest woman in 39 years to win the slalom title at the world alpine championships held in Schladming, Austria. At the age of 17 years, 340 days, Shiffrin edges local hope Michaela Kirchgasser. The only slalom world champions younger than Shiffrin were Hanni Wenzel of Liechtenstein in 1974 and Esme Mackinnon of Britain in 1931.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Carmelo Anthony makes an All-Star record eight 3-pointers and scores 30 points, and the Eastern Conference overcame Kevin Durant, Blake Griffin and the Western Conference for a 163-155 win.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Lowell Bailey upsets the pre-race favorites in the men's individual competition to become the first American biathlete to win gold at the world championships. Bailey's gold is the fourth medal for an American biathlete at the worlds.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Pittsburgh's Sidney Crosby feeds Chris Kunitz for a first-period goal against Winnipeg to become the 86th player in NHL history to reach the 1,000-point plateau. He adds an assist on Phil Kessel's game-tying goal in the third and then puts the winner past Connor Hellebuyck with 21 seconds left in overtime as the Penguins escaped with a 4-3 victory.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 17</hl2><p xmlns="">1923 — Cy Denneny of the Ottawa Senators becomes the NHL's all-time scorer. Denneny scores his 143rd goal to surpass Joe Malone in a 2-0 win over the Montreal Canadiens.</p><p xmlns="">1924 — Johnny Weissmuller sets a world record in the 100-yard freestyle swim with a time of 52.4 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">1926 — In a tournament at the Carlton Club in Cannes, France, Suzanne Lenglen beats Helen Wills 6-3, 8-6 in their only tennis match against each other.</p><p xmlns="">1928 — Sweden's Gillis Grafstrom defends his 1920 and 1924 Olympic figure skating title with Austrian Willy Bockl finishing in second place as he did four years earlier.</p><p xmlns="">1941 — Joe Louis knocks out Gus Dorazio in the second round at the Convention Hall in Philadelphia to defend his world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Philadelphia's Wilt Chamberlain hits the first of what would become an NBA record 35 consecutive field goals without a miss.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Raisa Smetanina wins a gold medal with the Unified Team in the 20-kilometer cross-country relay to set the career Winter Olympic Games medal record with 10. Smetanina, 39, also becomes the oldest champion and the first to win a medal in five straight Winter Games.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — San Antonio's David Robinson records the fourth quadruple-double in NBA history with 34 points, 10 rebounds, 10 assists and 10 blocks in the Spurs' 115-96 win over Detroit.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — The U.S. women's hockey team wins the sport's first-ever Olympic gold medal. Sandra Whyte scores on an empty-netter with 8 seconds left to give the United States a 3-1 victory over Canada.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Australia's Susie O'Neill shatters swimming's oldest record, breaking the 200-meter butterfly world mark with a time of 2:05.37 in a World Cup short-course meet at Malmo, Sweden. O'Neill broke the record of 2:05.65 set by Mary T. Meagher of the United States in 1981.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Arnold Palmer, 71, becomes the first player to shoot his age in a PGA Tour event since Sam Snead did 22 years ago. Palmer finishes the fourth round of the Bob Hope Classic with a 1-under 71. Joe Durant sets a 72-hole record of 29 under for a five-shot lead. Durant, with rounds of 65-61-67-66, breaks the 72-hole record for relation to par set by John Huston in the 1998 Hawaiian Open.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Americans Lindsey Vonn and Julia Mancuso captures gold and silver, respectively, in the women's Olympic downhill at Vancouver, British Columbia. It's the first time since 1984 that the United States captures the top two steps in a women's alpine skiing event. The second multi-podium performance of the day goes to Shani Davis who takes the gold and Chad Hedrick who grabs bronze in men's 1000-meter speedskating. Davis is the first U.S. male speedskater to successfully defend his Olympic title. Shaun White wins gold in the snowboard halfpipe to become the third American male to successfully defend an Olympic gold medal, joining Dick Button (figure skating, 1948 and 1952) and Davis.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Danica Patrick wins the Daytona 500 pole, becoming the first woman to secure the top spot for any Sprint Cup race.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Meryl Davis and Charlie White win the gold medal in ice dance, the first Olympic title in the event for the United States.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Laura Dahlmeier leads Germany to the world title in the women's 4x6-kilometer relay, becoming the first biathlete to win a medal in 10 straight world championship races. Vanessa Hinz, Maren Hammerschmidt, Franziska Hildebrandt and Dahlmeier miss a total of nine targets but avoided penalty laps before finishing in 1 hour, 11 minutes, 16.6 seconds. It's Dahlmeier's fifth medal of the championships, after winning gold in mixed relay, pursuit and individual competition, and silver in sprint. She also won five medals at last year's worlds in Oslo. The previous best mark of nine straight podiums was held by retired Norwegian great Tora Berger.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>