<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e8756ebc-9d5a-47ef-b3ed-aaba3f613e77" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Ricardo Alonso-zaldivar</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Budget Battle-Drugs-Medicare-The Latest</title><summary>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on proposals by President Donald Trump and in the Senate budget bill to lower drug prices for Medicare beneficiaries (all times local):9 p.m.President Donald Trump is proposing to lower prescription drug costs for...</summary><sourceId>3ef83083-474b-4d93-d93a-44705d53bbad</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:C4869%-----%r%BC-US--Budget Battle-Drugs-Medicare-The Latest;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">The Latest: Trump aims to reduce drug costs under Medicare</h2><byline xmlns="">By RICARDO ALONSO-ZALDIVAR</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on proposals by President Donald Trump and in the Senate budget bill to lower drug prices for Medicare beneficiaries (all times local):</p><p xmlns="">9 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">President Donald Trump is proposing to lower prescription drug costs for Medicare beneficiaries by allowing them to share in rebates that drug companies pay to insurers and other middlemen.</p><p xmlns="">A senior administration official outlined the plan on condition of anonymity Thursday ahead of the release of Trump's 2019 budget plan next week.</p><p xmlns="">Pharmaceutical companies now pay rebates to insurers and pharmacy benefit managers to help their medications gain a bigger slice of the market.</p><p xmlns="">Insurers apply savings from rebates to keep premiums more manageable.</p><p xmlns="">Under Trump's proposal, seniors covered by Medicare's "Part D" prescription benefit would be able to share in the rebates for individual drugs that they purchase at the pharmacy.</p><p xmlns="">The plan also expands Medicare's "catastrophic" drug benefit so many seniors with very high costs would not face copayments.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">6:29 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">The congressional budget deal would shift a bigger share of Medicare's medication costs to drug companies, a change that could help limit future increases in beneficiaries' premiums for prescription coverage.</p><p xmlns="">Changes to Medicare's popular "Part D" prescription plan headline a long list of budget-deal tweaks to the government's premier health insurance program, which covers about 60 million seniors and disabled people.</p><p xmlns="">Also, the drug coverage gap known as the "doughnut hole" would be eliminated one year earlier than currently scheduled, in 2019 instead of 2020.</p><p xmlns="">Another provision would raise premiums paid by the wealthiest retirees for coverage of outpatient services and prescription drugs.</p><p xmlns="">And the deal would permanently repeal current limits on outpatient rehab services, such as physical and occupational therapy. Previously, Congress had routinely waived the therapy caps</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>