<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b9742d66-5cc7-b15a-ed2e-177df3092204" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Anna Johnson</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TS-TEXTILE-RECYCLING:RA — trendsetter (400 words)</title><summary>RALEIGH, N.C. — People in Raleigh can now recycle old clothes without ever leaving their driveway.Raleigh is launching a textile recycling program this week. Residents who have curbside recycling with the city can put old clothes, shoes and other...</summary><sourceId>27347fd7-5c12-c4b0-4b05-48b185a62faf</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K8080%ksigt%w%BC-TS-TEXTILE-RECYCLING:RA — trendsetter (400 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">In Raleigh, there’s a new way to get rid of old clothes and shoes</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(NOT INCLUDED IN YOUR TRIBUNE NEWS SERVICE SUBSCRIPTION. To subscribe to Trends and Shopping, see purchase information below.) (PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Anna Johnson</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">RALEIGH, N.C. — People in Raleigh can now recycle old clothes without ever leaving their driveway.</p><p xmlns="">Raleigh is launching a textile recycling program this week. Residents who have curbside recycling with the city can put old clothes, shoes and other textiles in a special orange bag and place the bag next to their blue recycling cart.</p><p xmlns="">Simple Recycling, which is partnering with Raleigh on the project, will pick up the bags and leave a new bag tied to the recycling cart.</p><p xmlns="">Textiles that could be recycled make up about 7 percent of the waste that ends up at the South Wake Landfill. Raleigh should always look for new ways to divert waste from the landfill, and the textile recycling program is a good example, said City Council member Kay Crowder.</p><p xmlns="">“Cities do many things, many good things, but sometimes you strike on something that people know (is) important as it relates to diverting these out of the landfills,” said Crowder, who pushed for the initiative. “And this is one of those ways that the city made a positive decision and people are excited about it.”</p><p xmlns="">The program isn’t costing taxpayers money. Simple Recycling is an Ohio-based for-profit organization that takes recycled textiles to its sorting facility where “top quality materials” are resold to thrift outlets and some items are “exported to international markets.” Unusable items are processed for raw materials.</p><p xmlns="">Textile recycling includes clothing, jackets, shoes, boots, sandals, purses, backpacks, hats, stuffed animals, towels and blankets.</p><p xmlns="">The new program isn’t meant to divert donated clothes from charitable organizations, Crowder said. It’s meant to help those who are unable to transport donations themselves or who choose not to donate.</p><p xmlns="">“We in no way, as a city, want to discourage people from donating to charitable organizations,” she said.</p><p xmlns="">The program is only open to single-family residential customers, so apartment dwellers are out of luck for now.</p><p xmlns="">If you need additional orange bags or if you have a question, call Simple Recycling at 866-835-5068 or visit www.simplerecycling.com</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">TO SUBSCRIBE TO TRENDS AND SHOPPING</p><p xmlns="">This column/content is for subscribers only. It is sold separately and is not included in your Tribune News Service subscription. To subscribe, please contact Rick DeChantal at Tribune Content Agency, (1-312-222-8682) or rdechantal@tribpub.com, or you can purchase individual columns a la carte at www.tribunenewsservice.com.</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000036956,t000041170,t000030989,t000002537,t000040348,t000030990,t000030985,t000041231,g000362661,g000065598,g000225457,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>