<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="706f8702-aaab-4b96-9a3d-829b68985d02" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV17</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV17,5653</summary><sourceId>cea953a2-306c-416f-16f9-f26982c1a9d3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1012%-----%d%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV17;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV17</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV17,5653</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv17</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend editions, Feb. 17-18</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 18</hl2><p xmlns="">1924 — Theresa Weld Blanchard wins her sixth and final U.S. Figure Skating championship. Sherwin Badger wins his fifth straight and final men's title.</p><p xmlns="">1928 — At Moritz, Switzerland, Sonja Henie becomes the youngest Olympic figure skating champion. At 15 years and 315 days, easily beats Austria's Fritzi Burger and American Beatrix Loughran.</p><p xmlns="">1932 — Sonja Henie wins her sixth straight World Figure Skating title.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Manhattan District Attorney Frank S. Hogan orders the arrest of three CCNY basketball players on bribery charges, and two professional gamblers and two intermediaries in a game-fixing scandal that involves college teams across the country.</p><p xmlns="">1961 — Bob Pettit of St. Louis scores 57 points, the highest scoring game of his great career, in a 141-138 victory over the Detroit Pistons.</p><p xmlns="">1964 — Wilt Chamberlain scores 52 points against Detroit, his second consecutive 50-point game.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Randy Smith of Buffalo plays the first of what would become 906 consecutive games, an NBA record which took more than 11 full seasons to accomplish.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Edmonton's Wayne Gretzky scores five goals and adds two assists to lead the Oilers over the St. Louis Blues 9-2.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — San Antonio's Alvin Robertson records the second quadruple-double in NBA history, with 20 points, 11 rebounds, 10 assists and 10 steals in the Spurs' 120-114 win over Phoenix.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Dale Earnhardt blows a tire with one mile remaining in the Daytona 500, giving unheralded Derrike Cope the biggest upset in stock car racing history.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Italy's Alberto Tomba wins the men's giant slalom in Albertville, France, to become the first Alpine skier to win the same event at two Winter Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Utah guard John Stockton becomes the first NBA player with 10,000 assists in a 108-98 victory over the Boston Celtics.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Dale Earnhardt, the greatest stock car star of his era, is killed in a crash on the last turn of the last lap of the Daytona 500 as he tries to protect Michael Waltrip's victory.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Shani Davis becomes the first black athlete to win an individual gold medal in Winter Olympic history, capturing the men's 1,000-meter speedskating race. Joey Cheek makes it a 1-2 American finish, adding a silver to his victory in the 500 at the Turin Games.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Evan Lysacek becomes the first U.S. man to win the Olympic gold medal since Brian Boitano in 1988, shocking everyone with an upset of defending champion Evgeni Plushenko.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Shenneika Smith's 3-pointer from the wing with 8 seconds left lifts St. John's to a 57-56 win over No. 2 Connecticut, snapping the Huskies' 99-game home court winning streak. It's the Huskies' first home loss to an unranked opponent in nearly 19 years.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Brittney Griner scores 25 points, including the 3,000th of her career, to help No. 1 Baylor rally past third-ranked Connecticut 76-70.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Mikaela Shiffrin wins a third straight slalom title at the ski world championships to retain her unbeaten record at major events.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 19</hl2><p xmlns="">1928 — Canada wins the gold medal in ice hockey at the Winter Olympics in St. Moritz, Switzerland. Canada, represented by the 1926 Toronto University team receives a bye to the final round. In the final round, the Canadians beat Sweden 11-0, Britain 14-0 and Switzerland 13-0.</p><p xmlns="">1955 — Bernie Geoffrion of the Montreal Canadiens scores five goals in a 10-2 victory over the New York Rangers.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Rod Gilbert of the New York Rangers gets his 1,000th career point with a goal in a 5-2 loss to the New York Islanders.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Atlanta's 127-122 four-overtime win over Seattle equals the fourth-longest game in NBA history and the second-longest since the institution of the 24-second clock.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Phil and Steve Mahre of the United States become the first brothers to finish 1-2 in an Olympic event, the men's slalom, at the Winter Games in Sarajevo, Yugoslavia. The Soviet Union beats Czechoslovakia 2-0 to win the gold medal in hockey.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Cale Yarborough sweeps into the lead two turns before the finish to win the Daytona 500. He becomes the second driver to win consecutive Daytona 500s; Richard Petty was the other.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Wendel Suckow edges two-time world champion Georg Hackl of Germany by 0.106 seconds to capture the first world luge championship medal of any kind for the United States.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Speedskater Bonnie Blair wins the fourth gold of her Olympic career with her third consecutive 500-meter victory.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — In Salt Lake City, bobsledders Jill Bakken and Vonetta Flowers give the United States 21 medals in the Winter Games. Flowers becomes the first black athlete in history to win a gold medal at the Winter Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Lindsay Kennedy becomes the first woman to play in a Major Indoor Soccer League game. Kennedy, a St. Louis forward, participates in the final 76 seconds of Milwaukee's 7-3 win over the Steamers at Savvis Center.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Schreiner ends its NCAA-record losing streak at 83 games, beating Sul Ross State 75-69 in a women's basketball game. It's the Division III Mountaineers first win since Jan. 17, 2002, when they also beat Sul Ross.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — American star Hannah Kearney's all-discipline record for consecutive FIS World Cup victories ends at 16 with a semifinal loss in a dual moguls event at Naeba, Japan. Kearney's streak began in Lake Placid, N.Y., on Jan. 22, 2011.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Steven Holcomb and brakeman Steve Langton win the two-man bobsled in Lake Placid, N.Y., the first time the U.S. captures this event at the world championships.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Norway wins the first Olympic mixed relay in biathlon at the Sochi Games and Ole Einar Bjoerndalen becomes the most decorated Winter Olympian ever with 13 medals. Ted Ligety wins the giant slalom with a dominating performance, becoming the first American man to win two Olympic gold medals in Alpine skiing.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Laura Dahlmeier wins the world title in the women's 12.5-kilometer mass start, becoming the first athlete to win five gold medals at a single biathlon world championship.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Anthony Davis has an All-Star Game for the record books, scoring 52 points, 10 more than Wilt Chamberlain's All-Star record that had stood for 55 years, and the Western Conference beat the Eastern Conference 192-182 — the highest-scoring game in league history.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 20</hl2><p xmlns="">1887 — The International Association, the first minor league baseball association, is organized in Pittsburgh.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — In the wake of the college point-shaving scandal, Long Island University drops basketball and all other intercollegiate sports. LIU revives basketball in 1957.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — En route to a record 76-goal season, Boston's Phil Esposito becomes the first player to score his 50th goal in February, but the Bruins lose to the Los Angeles Kings 5-4.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Larry Brown of the Denver Rockets set ABA records for assists in a game (23), half (18) and quarter (10) during a 146-123 win over the Pittsburgh Condors at Denver.</p><p xmlns="">1974 — Gordie Howe, the NHL's career scoring leader, comes out of retirement and signs a $1 million, four-year contract to play with the Houston Aeros of the WHA and his two sons, Mark and Marty.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Muhammad Ali beats Jean-Pierre Coopman with a fifth-round knockout at the Roberto Clemente Coliseum in Puerto Rico to defend his world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — In Calgary, Alberta, Brian Boitano of the United States wins the men's Olympic figure skating gold medal on a technical merit tiebreaker and nearly flawless free skating performance.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Julio Cesar Chavez records a fifth-round TKO over Greg Haugen in a WBC super lightweight title bout before a record crowd of 130,000 at Mexico City's Aztec Stadium.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Tara Lipinski, 15, becomes the youngest Olympic figure skating champion in history, jumping over fellow teen and U.S. teammate Michelle Kwan to take the gold. Lipinski was two months younger than Sonja Henie was in her 1928 victory.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Tanith Belbin and partner Ben Agosto snap the U.S. medals drought in the Olympic figure skating dance competition with a silver. Belbin and Agosto win the first dance medal for the United States since the bronze won by Colleen O'Connor and James Millns in 1976.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Lindsey Van of the United States nails a perfect second jump to become the first women's ski jumping world champion. Women's ski jumping makes its debut at this year's Nordic skiing world championships in Liberec, Czech Republic. Todd Lodwick wins the opening Nordic combined event to give the United States two golds in one day. Before Van's victory, the United States had not won a gold at a Nordic skiing worlds since 2003, when Johnny Spillane took a Nordic combined sprint.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Switzerland's Simon Ammann wins the large hill at the Vancouver Games to become the first ski jumper with four individual Olympic titles.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Twenty-year-old Trevor Bayne wins the Daytona 500, NASCAR's biggest race, in only his second Sprint Cup start.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Kobe Bryant wins his record-tying fourth All-Star game MVP award in front of his hometown fans, scoring 37 points and propelling the West to a 148-143 victory over the East in the NBA All-Star game.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Lindsey Vonn clinches a record 20th World Cup crystal globe title and surpassing Swedish great Ingemar Stenmark. It's Vonn's record eighth downhill title — adding to four overall globes plus five in super-G and three in combined. Sweden's Stenmark held the previous record of 19 globes established from 1975 to 1984.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 21</hl2><p xmlns="">1931 — The Chicago White Sox meet the New York Giants in the first major league night game. The 10-inning exhibition is played in Houston.</p><p xmlns="">1952 — The Boston Celtics and the Fort Wayne Pistons tip off at midnight in a "Milkman's Special" following an Ice Follies performance at Boston Garden. Bob Cousy of the Celtics scores 24 points in front 2,368 customers in a 88-67 win.</p><p xmlns="">1952 — Dick Button performs the first triple jump in a figure skating competition.</p><p xmlns="">1953 — In the longest game in college basketball in history, Niagara beats Siena, 88-81 in six overtimes.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Philadelphia Warriors rookie Wilt Chamberlain sets an NBA record with his fourth 50-point game of the season, scoring 58 in a 129-122 victory over the New York Knicks.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Bobby Hull scores two goals, including the 500th of his career, in the Chicago Black Hawks' 4-2 win over the New York Rangers.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Pete Maravich scores 64 points but Louisiana State still loses to Kentucky, 121-105. Dan Issel scores 51 for the Wildcats.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — New York's Red Holzman becomes the second NBA coach, after Red Auerbach, to win 500 games with a 102-98 victory over New Orleans.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Kristi Yamaguchi wins America's first Olympic gold medal in women's figure skating since 1976. Midori Ito of Japan takes the silver and Nancy Kerrigan of the United States wins bronze.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — The Philadelphia 76ers have the worst NBA offensive performance in 41 years in their 66-57 loss to Miami. The 76ers tie the record for fewest points, set Feb. 27, 1955, by Milwaukee in a 62-57 loss to Boston during the first season of the 24-second clock.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — In Salt Lake City, U.S. figure skater Sarah Hughes jumps from fourth to first to win the Olympic gold after a near-flawless performance, leaving teammate Michelle Kwan to settle for a bronze. The powerful Americans lose a 3-2 gold medal game to a Canadian team that it had beaten eight consecutive times in women's ice hockey.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Michael Jordan becomes the first 40-year-old in NBA history to score 40 or more points, getting 43 in the Washington Wizards' 89-86 win over the New Jersey Nets.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Mikaela Shiffrin makes Alpine skiing history as the youngest ever winner of an Olympic slalom gold medal. The 18-year-old American finishes 0.53 seconds faster than Austrian Marlies Schild.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 22</hl2><p xmlns="">1919 — The first dog race track to use an imitation rabbit opens in Emeryville, Calif.</p><p xmlns="">1936 — Figure skater Sonja Henie wins her 10th straight world championship.</p><p xmlns="">1959 — Lee Petty, driving an Oldsmobile, wins the first Daytona 500.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Barbara Jo Rubin becomes the first female jockey to win a race at an American thoroughbred track when she rides Cohesian to a neck victory over Reely Beeg in the ninth race at Charles Town in West Virginia.</p><p xmlns="">1975 — Madison Square Garden hosts its first women's collegiate basketball game. In a rematch of the 1973 national championship game, defending national champion Immaculata beats Queens College 65-31, before a crowd of 11,969.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — The United States Olympic hockey team stuns the Soviet Union with a 4-3 victory in the medal round of the Winter Olympics in Lake Placid, N.Y. Captain Mike Eruzione scores the game-winning goal midway through the final period.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Rookies Peter and Anton Stastny each score eight points as the Quebec Nordiques beat the Washington Capitals 11-7. Peter scores four goals and four assists and Aaron has three goals and five assists.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Hersey Hawkins scores 63 points as Bradley beats Detroit 122-107. Archie Tullos scores 49 points for the Titans.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Bonnie Blair wins America's second gold medal at the Winter Olympics in world-record time, beating Christa Rothenburger of East Germany by .02 seconds in the 500-meter speed skating.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Lionel Simmons scores 27 points to move into fourth place of the NCAA Division I scoring list at 3,024 and becomes the fifth player to score 3,000 points as the Explorers beat Manhattan 100-60.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Glenn Anderson becomes the 36th NHL player with 1,000 points, picking up a goal and two assists to help the Toronto Maple Leafs beat the Vancouver Canucks 8-1.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Bjorn Dahlie, the Norwegian cross-country skiing great, extends his Winter Olympics record by picking up his 12th medal, and record eighth gold, in the last race of Nagano — the 50-kilometer.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Gene Bess becomes the first college basketball coach to win 1,000 games when Three Rivers Community College beat Forest Park 77-60.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Lindsey Vonn clinches the World Cup downhill title, becoming the first American woman to claim the crown since Picabo Street in 1996. Nadia Styger of Switzerland wins the race at Whistler, British Columbia with Vonn finishing 0.01 behind Styger.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — The Indy Racing League and the Champ Car World Series sign a deal to unify the two American open-wheel circuits, bringing them under the umbrella of the IRL.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Caltech ends its 310-game conference losing streak in men's basketball beating Occidental College 46-45 in its season finale.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The Chicago Blackhawks sets an NHL record for the best start to a season, beating the San Jose Sharks 2-1 to give them at least one point in their first 17 games.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Tennessee's 31-year run in the Women's Top 25 ends. The Lady Vols streak of 565 consecutive weeks in The Associated Press women's basketball poll is over as Tennessee falls out of the Top 25. The streak started Feb. 17, 1985.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 23</hl2><p xmlns="">1938 — Joe Louis knocks out Nathan Mann in the third round to defend his world heavyweight title at Madison Square Garden in New York.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Carol Heiss captures the first gold medal for the United States in the Winter Olympics at Squaw Valley, Calif., winning the figure skating event.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Wilt Chamberlain becomes first player to score 25,000 points in the NBA.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — Eric Heiden wins his fifth gold medal and shatters the world record by six seconds in 10,000-meter speed skating at the Winter Olympics in Lake Placid, N.Y. His time is 14:28.13.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — Mark Pavelich of the New York Rangers scores five goals in an 11-3 victory over the Hartford Whalers.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Indiana coach Bob Knight is ejected five minutes into the Hoosiers' 72-63 loss to Purdue when he throws a chair across the court. Knight, after two fouls called on his team, is hit with his first technical. While Purdue was shooting the technical, Knight picks up a chair from the bench area and throws it across the court, earning his second technical.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Seattle's Nate McMillan sets an NBA rookie record with 25 assists to lead the SuperSonics over the Los Angeles Clippers 124-112.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — North Carolina becomes the first team in NCAA basketball history to win 1,500 games with a 73-57 victory over Clemson.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Boston's Marty McSorley is suspended for the rest of the season (23 games) for hitting Vancouver's Donald Brashear in the head with his stick on Feb. 21.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Tiger Woods' winning streak on the PGA Tour, which began in July, comes to a shocking end. Woods fails to notice a ball mark in the line of his 4-foot birdie putt that would have won his third-round match against Nick O'Hern. Woods misses, then loses in 20 holes when O'Hern saves par with a 12-foot putt at the Accenture Match Play Championship.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — In Vancouver, British Columbia, Dutch skater Sven Kramer loses the Olympic gold medal when his coach Gerard Kemkers sends him the wrong way on a changeover during the 25 laps of the 10,000-meter speedskating race. Kramer had not lost a 10,000 in three years.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — National League MVP Ryan Braun's 50-game suspension is overturned by baseball arbitrator Shyam Das, the first time a baseball player successfully challenged a drug-related penalty in a grievance.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Ronda Rousey and Liz Carmouche makes history just by stepping into the UFC cage. Rousey wins the UFC's first women's bout, beating Carmouche on an armbar, her signature move, with 11 seconds left in the first round of their bantamweight title fight at UFC 157.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Canada defends its Olympic men's hockey title with a 3-0 victory over Sweden. Canada becomes the only repeat Olympic champ in the NHL era and the first team to go unbeaten through the Olympic tournament since the Soviet Union in Sarajevo in 1984.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Jason Collins becomes the first openly gay athlete in the United States four major pro leagues, playing 10 scoreless minutes with two rebounds and five fouls in the New Jersey's 108-102 victory of the Los Angeles Lakers.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 24</hl2><p xmlns="">1960 — Bill Cleary's four goals lead the United States to a 9-1 victory over West Germany in the hockey championship round of the Winter Olympics in Squaw Valley, Calif.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Wilt Chamberlain of Philadelphia shoots 18-for-18 from the field against the Baltimore Bullets, an NBA record for field goals in a game without a miss.</p><p xmlns="">1978 — Kevin Porter of the New Jersey Nets sets an NBA record with 29 assists in a 126-112 victory over the Houston Rockets.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — The United States hockey team wins the gold medal with a 4-2 victory over Finland at the Winter Olympics in Lake Placid, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Jim Kelly of the Houston Gamblers passes for a USFL-record 574 yards and five touchdowns in a 34-33 comeback-win over the Los Angeles Express. Kelly, completes 35 of 54 passes, including three for touchdowns in the final 10 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — An unprecedented winner of the 90-and 70-meter individual events, Matti Nykanen becomes the Winter Olympics' first triple gold medalist in Nordic skiing when Finland wins the new 90-meter team ski jumping event.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Steve Yzerman of the Detroit Red Wings scores his 1,000th career point with two goals and two assists in a 10-7 loss to Buffalo Sabres.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Lipscomb's John Pierce becomes college basketball's career scoring leader with 33 points in his regular-season finale, a 119-102 win over Cumberland. Pierce's 4,110 points break former roommate Phil Hutcheson's record of 4,106.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Svetlana Feofanova breaks the pole vault indoor world record for the fourth time this month, clearing 15 feet, 6 1/2 inches at the Gaz de France meet.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Joe Sakic scores two goals, including the game-winner, and two assists, and Jarome Iginla scores twice as Canada beat the United States 5-2 for the gold medal at the Winter Olympics. It's the seventh time Canada has won the gold in its national sport, but the first since 1952.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Julia Mancuso earns a stunning victory in the giant slalom to salvage a disappointing Olympics for the U.S. women in their final Alpine event of the Turin Games. Mancuso gives the American women their first Olympic Alpine medal since Picabo Street's gold in the super-G at the 1998 Nagano Games.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Tiger Woods wins the Accenture Match Play Championship, his fifth straight tournament victory. Woods overwhelms Stewart Cink with 14 birdies in 29 holes for an 8-and-7 victory, the largest margin in the final in the 10-year history of this tournament.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Syracuse beats St. John's 87-58 to give coach Jim Boeheim his record 31st 20-win season. Boeheim breaks the tie with former North Carolina coach Dean Smith for the Division I record for 20-win seasons.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Missy Parkin becomes the first woman to reach the match play finals in the 69th U.S Open at Brunswick Zone-Carolier. Shafer, a 25-year Professional Bowlers Association Tour veteran, completes the 26-game qualifying portion of the U.S. Open with a total of 5,825 pins - averaging at a 224.04 pace.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>