<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="fcd63d42-35a4-492e-9e1c-8878ed229aa1" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0406</summary><sourceId>2cc6dbb6-db95-407f-07f8-6d1f4aed9d13</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2965%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0406</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 11</hl2><p xmlns="">1878 — The Boston Bicycle Club, the first bicycle club in the United States, is formed.</p><p xmlns="">1949 — Willie Pep becomes the first boxer in the history of the 126-pound class to regain a lost championship with a 15-round unanimous decision over Sandy Saddler at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1957 — The NHL Players Association is formed, with Ted Lindsay of the Detroit Red Wings elected president.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — The Atlanta Hawks score the most points (97) in the second half of an NBA game en route to a 155-131 win at San Diego.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Montreal's Jean Beliveau scores his 500th goal in the Canadiens' 6-2 victory over the Minnesota North Stars.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — The Philadelphia 76ers lose to the Los Angeles Lakers 108-90 to set an NBA record for the most consecutive losses in a season at 20.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Houston Rockets center Moses Malone grabs an NBA-record 21 offensive rebounds in a 117-100 win over Seattle.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Mike Tyson loses for the first time when James "Buster" Douglas knocks him out in the 10th round in Tokyo and captures the heavyweight championship in one of boxing's biggest upsets. 1992 — Anfissa Reztsova wins the women's 7.5-kilometer biathlon event to become the first woman to get gold medals in different Winter Olympic sports. She skied the final 5-kilometer leg on the Soviet Union's winning 20K cross-country relay team in the 1988 Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Allen Iverson and Stephon Marbury lead an improbable comeback to give the Eastern Conference a 111-110 NBA All-Star victory. Iverson scores 15 of his 25 points in the final nine minutes, and Marbury hits two 3-pointers in the final 53 seconds to help the East come back from a 21-point deficit.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Anja Paerson captures the downhill, becoming the first skier to win gold medals in all five disciplines at the world championships. Paerson, who also won the super-G and combined titles earlier in the week, won gold medals in the giant slalom at the last two worlds and one in the slalom in 2001.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — The Cleveland Cavaliers stop their NBA-record losing streak at 26 games with a 126-119 win in overtime against the Los Angeles Clippers. Antawn Jamison scores 35 points and makes the game's biggest basket, a 3-pointer with 22 seconds left in the extra period.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>