<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="1d6496ab-51ee-4964-ba82-062bf66c2bff" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0557</summary><sourceId>b182d1eb-d980-4569-569a-a60b871b54fb</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8797%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0557</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agreed to terms with OF Alex Presley on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Heath Fillmyer, Sam Gaviglio, Jesse Hahn, Jakob Junis, Brad Keller, Andres Machado, Kevin McCarthy, Burch Smith and Kyle Zimmer; LHPs Brian Flynn, Tim Hill and Eric Stout; C Meibrys Viloria and INFs Samir Duenez, Hunter Dozier and Whit Merrifield on one-year contracts.</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES ANGELS — Agreed to terms with 1B Chris Carter on a minor league contract and OF Chris Young on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA DIAMONDBACKS — Agreed to terms with OF Jarrod Dyson on a two-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI REDS — Agreed to terms with RHP Ben Rowen on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS CARDINALS — Agreed to terms with RHP Jason Motte on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO PADRES — Agreed to terms with 1B Eric Hosmer on an eight-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO GIANTS — Agreed to terms with LHP Tony Watson on a two-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Named Todd Downing senior offensive assistant.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Reassigned F Lucas Wallmark to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Traded D Michal Kempny to Washington for a conditional 2018 third-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Acquired a 2018 conditional fourth-round draft pick and a 2019 conditional third-round draft pick from Philadelphia for G Petr Mrazek.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK ISLANDERS — Recalled G Eamon McAdam from Worcester (ECHL) to Bridgeport (AHL). Recalled G Christopher Gibson from Bridgeport on an emergency basis.</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE SHARKS — Recalled F Alex Schoenborn from Allen (ECHL) to San Jose (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Assigned D Matt Spencer from Syracuse (AHL) to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">VEGAS KNIGHTS — Recalled F Keegan Kolesar from Quad City (ECHL) to Chicago (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BELLEVILLE SENATORS — Returned D Willie Corrin to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">CHARLOTTE CHECKERS — Assigned F Spencer Smallman and G Callum Booth to Florida (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Recalled Ds David Warsofsky and Andrei Mironov and F Samuel Blais from San Antonio (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Returned D Desmond Bergin to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LAVAL ROCKET — Returned D Matt Petgrave and F Chris Leveille to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">ROCHESTER AMERICANS — Recalled F Daniel Muzito Bagenda from Cincinnati (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE BARRACUDA — Recalled F Colby McAuley from Allen (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Indy D Garrett Clarke five games, Tulsa LW Kale Kessy two games and Tulsa C Connor Bleackley, Colorado LW Ben Storm and Colorado G Joe Cannata one game.</p><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Released G Daniel Spence and F Ian Harris.</p><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ICEMEN — Signed D Chad Thibodeau.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTH CAROLINA STINGRAYS — Signed D Michael Chen.</p><p xmlns="">TULSA OILERS — Released G Ian Keserich as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">UTAH GRIZZLIES — Signed Fs Mitch Maxwell and Nate Mitton.</p><p xmlns="">WHEELING NAILERS — Released G Will King.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA THUNDER — Released G Ted Florence as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">COLORADO RAPIDS — Signed M Enzo Martinez to a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">DENVER — Named Karlton Creech vice chancellor for athletics and recreation.</p><p xmlns="">ETSU — Signed men's basketball coach Steve Forbes to a contract extension through the 2022-23 season.</p><p xmlns="">GEORGIA SOUTHERN — Agreed to a contract extension with men's basketball coach Mark Byington through the 2021-22 season.</p><p xmlns="">JOHNSON C. SMITH — Named Lamont Johnson cross country and track and field coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>