<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="318cf557-1130-f32a-1a3a-5d8dbd5801db" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Bryce Miller</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words)</title><summary>Whether you think the eight-year, $144 million gamble on first baseman Eric Hosmer is the best way to apply the future-altering scalpel during the Padres’ organizational face-lift, there’s something that has become impossible to ignore.They’re...</summary><sourceId>b4908226-b4b9-219e-19e5-df66811fca9f</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K2738%kniht%r%BC-BBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Bryce Miller: Deal with Eric Hosmer signals the end of the Padres front office of old</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Bryce Miller</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Whether you think the eight-year, $144 million gamble on first baseman Eric Hosmer is the best way to apply the future-altering scalpel during the Padres’ organizational face-lift, there’s something that has become impossible to ignore.</p><p xmlns="">They’re trying.</p><p xmlns="">The Padres, a franchise with a long-held and too-often-earned reputation as miserly caretakers of baseball along the Southern California coast, are doing what everyone has demanded for generations.</p><p xmlns="">They’ve inked a pair of record contracts … in 13 months. The Hosmer deal obliterates the former high-water mark of Wil Myers … by, potentially, $61 million. The Padres never had spent more than $5 million in the international market during a single signing period … before unloading almost $80 million from 2016-17.</p><p xmlns="">“The fact that they are willing to go out and get a premium player and pay a lot of money to get somebody like that — that just shows that there’s a commitment,” veteran third baseman Chase Headley said Sunday.</p><p xmlns="">Headley is right.</p><p xmlns="">There’s the fact that the Opening-Day payroll for the notoriously tight-fisted Friars is projected to be about $90 million, which Union-Tribune reporter Jeff Sanders rightfully explained would have landed at No. 27 among 30 clubs a season ago.</p><p xmlns="">This, though, isn’t about simply spending money like a college student clutching his or her first credit card. It’s about doing so at the right time, to leverage the bank account in the right ways in a place like San Diego — a market where every dollar remains precious.</p><p xmlns="">The Padres crowed when their payroll finally cracked $100 million in 2015. What did all those checks doled out to Justin Upton, James Shields and Matt Kemp get them? Shields was 33 at the time. Kemp was 30.</p><p xmlns="">Hosmer, at 28, is much closer to his prime in a world where a couple of years can make every bit of difference. And by all accounts, he’s exactly the kind of leader and clubhouse presence that teams crave.</p><p xmlns="">One other interesting wrinkle that also signals the times might be a-changin’: The Padres engaged in that dangerous financial game of chicken known as “negotiating with Scott Boras.”</p><p xmlns="">It’s not impossible to imagine Boras being tied in knots about such a unique, front-loaded deal for his client Hosmer, who will earn $20 million per season for the first five years of the deal. Then the salary dips to $13 million for each of the remaining seasons, if Hosmer decides against exercising an opt-out clause after the fifth season.</p><p xmlns="">I questioned the wisdom of a deal of that length for that type of money for one player at this point on the rebuilding timeline. Still do. The point, though, is that the Padres are willing to mix it up at a higher level and think creatively about how to chart a path.</p><p xmlns="">A front-loaded deal means that there potentially will be more money available at the end to start locking up this youth movement on the way before all of them are arbitration-eligible.</p><p xmlns="">In plain speak: Hosmer might not get the Padres to the finish line, but his deal is structured such that a whole bunch of other home-grown players might.</p><p xmlns="">Sculpting a deal with Boras is noteworthy, given that the Padres were unwilling to play the big-money game in 2004 when the super-agent represented amateur stars Stephen Drew and Jered Weaver. An unwillingness of ownership to cut the big check led to No. 1 draft pick Matt Bush — and we all know how that turned out.</p><p xmlns="">“Now that ownership has its feet under them and they have a process of what they’re going to do, now you’re seeing the transition into the future,” Headley said.</p><p xmlns="">“… You certainly don’t expect one person to come in and change everything around, but it’s a statement that the organization has made that ‘We’re serious about this.’ ”</p><p xmlns="">There still are plenty of arguments to make about how the franchise could have spent $144 million (or the minimum $105 million they’ll pay Hosmer if he opts out early). I’ve made them myself.</p><p xmlns="">Anyone who thinks the Padres could have bankrolled the money to position themselves for next offseason’s free-agent chaos with Bryce Harper and Manny Machado, though, needs to lay off the funny-tasting lemonade. Those types of deals will demand the kind of money that would bankrupt a few African nations.</p><p xmlns="">You — and I, for that matter — might not be wholly comfortable with the level and length of the Hosmer investment. But doing something sure beats all those milquetoast Padres seasons of doing nothing, right?</p><p xmlns="">What the Padres get immediately: There’s plate protection for Myers, which was painfully lacking since the stretch run of 2016. There’s a four-time Gold Glove winner who’s hitting better than ever. There’s a guy who seems to love National League ballparks, and Petco Park in particular. There’s a blossoming veteran who everyone insists makes a clubhouse better.</p><p xmlns="">I was asked to jump onto a SiriusXM baseball show Sunday to talk about the Hosmer deal. The host asked what the move meant. For one, I said, someone was talking about the Padres on a national radio program.</p><p xmlns="">Does all of that guarantee anything in a win-loss way? Of course not.</p><p xmlns="">It signals something meaningful, though: These Padres aren’t content being the Padres of old.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000424479,t000007391,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>