<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="32953c5a-0ed7-4121-b2ee-38db0ff0f518" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-EU--Europe-ECB-Spain,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>BRUSSELS (AP) — Ireland announced Monday that it was withdrawing its candidate for the coveted post of European Central Bank vice president, making it almost certain that Spain's finance minister would get the job.Spain is the eurozone's No. 4...</summary><sourceId>bc1bbdec-6324-43fc-3fcb-a9fbf8e1695d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:a0604%-----%r%BC-EU--Europe-ECB-Spain,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Spain set for ECB post after Ireland withdraws candidate</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Updates with Irish, French, German, Commissioner quotes, background. With AP Photos.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">BRUSSELS (AP) — Ireland announced Monday that it was withdrawing its candidate for the coveted post of European Central Bank vice president, making it almost certain that Spain's finance minister would get the job.</p><p xmlns="">Spain is the eurozone's No. 4 economy, but has been absent from the board, which is a key part of the apparatus guiding eurozone monetary policy, for almost six years. Spanish Finance Minister Luis de Guindos would take over the seat on the ECB executive board from incumbent Vitor Constancio.</p><p xmlns="">Referring to Irish central bank governor Philip Lane, Irish Finance Minister Paschal Donohoe said Monday that "I am confirming that we will not be putting his candidacy forward."</p><p xmlns="">Donohoe said it was important for finance ministers from the euro currency countries meeting Monday to decide who should get the job by consensus. He wished de Guindos "the best of luck."</p><p xmlns="">De Guindos could be anointed by the full council of EU finance ministers as soon as Tuesday. He is then likely to be named by European Union leaders at a March 22-23 summit.</p><p xmlns="">"In order to preserve the value of consensus amongst all of my colleagues, I'm looking forward to supporting finance minister de Guindos this evening," Donohoe told reporters in Brussels.</p><p xmlns="">No Spanish official holds any another senior EU post.</p><p xmlns="">France's finance minister, Bruno Le Maire, was quick to announce his country's support for de Guindos, saying that he "has all the skills to be a very good vice president."</p><p xmlns="">Standing alongside Le Maire, German Finance Minister Peter Altmaier said: "I think we have found a good candidate."</p><p xmlns="">Describing de Guindos as "an excellent colleague over several years," EU Economy Commissioner Pierre Moscovici played down concerns about the Spaniard being a politician rather than a banker, saying that "he can adapt and be a good vice president."</p><p xmlns="">ECB officials are tasked with doing what's best for the entire eurozone economy, not with representing the interests of their home countries. But that doesn't stop the member states from pushing to get their nationals into prime posts.</p><p xmlns="">The vice president sits on the six-member executive board that runs the bank day to day at its headquarters in Frankfurt, Germany. The vice president appears at news conferences alongside the ECB president and is a prominent part of the public face of the bank.</p><p xmlns="">Additionally, each executive board member has responsibility for a key area such as international relations or legal questions. Constancio's brief has been the stability of the financial system and research.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>