<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0117023a-3c6a-45e6-86d9-6483d374fced" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Redistricting-Pennsylvania-The Latest</title><summary>HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — The Latest on Republican efforts to stop new a congressional map in Pennsylvania (all times local):7:20 p.m.Pennsylvania's two highest-ranking Republican legislative leaders are asking the U.S. Supreme Court to block a new...</summary><sourceId>ce318f3a-96e2-4af5-af59-1d5afa7ba824</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL0557%limit%u%BC-US--Redistricting-Pennsylvania-The Latest;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">The Latest: Republicans ask court to block congressional map</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — The Latest on Republican efforts to stop new a congressional map in Pennsylvania (all times local):</p><p xmlns="">7:20 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Pennsylvania's two highest-ranking Republican legislative leaders are asking the U.S. Supreme Court to block a new congressional district map viewed as likely to help Democrats.</p><p xmlns="">The presiding officers of the House and the Senate on Wednesday electronically filed an emergency request to stay a state Supreme Court order issued Monday that redrew boundaries of Pennsylvania's 18 congressional districts. The request to Justice Samuel Alito (ahl-EE'-toh) says the state Supreme Court usurped legislative authority and calls the decision unprecedented.</p><p xmlns="">Democrats are hopeful the new map will be more favorable to their candidates and may help them reclaim majority control of the U.S. House this year.</p><p xmlns="">Republican leaders say a separate action in federal court in Harrisburg is also possible this week.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">10:20 a.m.</p><p xmlns="">Republican leaders of the Pennsylvania Legislature say they're about to ask the U.S. Supreme Court to halt the imposition of new congressional district maps , two days after they were announced by the state's highest court.</p><p xmlns="">House Speaker Mike Turzai says he and his Senate counterpart will request an emergency stay Wednesday of what he called a "completely partisan, ultimate gerrymander."</p><p xmlns="">The challenge adds uncertainty as candidates are preparing to circulate nominating petitions to get their names on the May primary ballot.</p><p xmlns="">The Democratic majority on the state Supreme Court in January threw out a 2011 congressional district map that had been drafted by Republicans, saying it violated the state constitution's guarantee of free and equal elections.</p><p xmlns="">Turzai says a separate action in federal court in Harrisburg is also possible.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>