<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="809109f8-b4d4-4d0b-9fb5-da4525421f5c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>Jari Tanner</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-EU--Latvia-Banks,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>HELSINKI (AP) — Latvia's anti-corruption agency says it suspects the nation's central bank chief of demanding and receiving bribes of at least 100,000 euros ($125,000) and has started a criminal investigation against him.The agency said Monday...</summary><sourceId>f2d26ef9-948d-4ad8-ad8a-953c2f6de094</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:C5710%-----%r%BC-EU--Latvia-Banks,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Latvia starts criminal probe of its central bank chief</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Adds detail. With AP Photos.</p><byline xmlns="">JARI TANNER</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">HELSINKI (AP) — Latvia's anti-corruption agency says it suspects the nation's central bank chief of demanding and receiving bribes of at least 100,000 euros ($125,000) and has started a criminal investigation against him.</p><p xmlns="">The agency said Monday that no formal charges have so far been filed against Ilmars Rimsevics, who is also on the top policymaking council of the European Central Bank.</p><p xmlns="">On Friday, the agency raided the office and a property of Rimsevics and detained him on Saturday.</p><p xmlns="">Prime Minister Maris Kucinskis said after an extraordinary Cabinet meeting Monday that the central banker will face "restrictions" to be announced later.</p><p xmlns="">He was quoted by the Baltic News Service as saying: "At the very minimum, he will be banned from continuing in office."</p><p xmlns="">Rimsevics has served as Bank of Latvia's governor since 2001. Latvia joined the euro-zone in 2014.</p><p xmlns="">Meanwhile, Latvia's financial regulator has ordered the crisis-struck ABLV Bank to cease all payments on the request of the European Central Bank amid U.S. accusations of money laundering and breaching sanctions on North Korea.</p><p xmlns="">The ECB said Monday that the Financial and Capital Markets Commission of Latvia has imposed "a prohibition of all payments by ABLV Bank on its financial liabilities" until further notice.</p><p xmlns="">The ECB noted that ABLV has seen a sharp deterioration of its financial position in recent days.</p><p xmlns="">Latvia's central bank said separately that it would loan ABLV 97.5 million euros ($121 million) against "a reliable pledge of highly liquid securities" instead of 480 million euros ABLV had requested.</p><p xmlns="">ABLV is Latvia's third largest bank by assets.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>