<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="19ecdfa7-049b-4d02-aa18-26fd2f11f2c7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0589</summary><sourceId>32d9bc23-4f1b-4377-3778-c3f3e4fe6614</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2532%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0589</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 17</hl2><p xmlns="">1923 — Cy Denneny of the Ottawa Senators becomes the NHL's all-time scorer. Denneny scores his 143rd goal to surpass Joe Malone in a 2-0 win over the Montreal Canadiens.</p><p xmlns="">1924 — Johnny Weissmuller sets a world record in the 100-yard freestyle swim with a time of 52.4 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">1926 — In a tournament at the Carlton Club in Cannes, France, Suzanne Lenglen beats Helen Wills 6-3, 8-6 in their only tennis match against each other.</p><p xmlns="">1928 — Sweden's Gillis Grafstrom defends his 1920 and 1924 Olympic figure skating title with Austrian Willy Bockl finishing in second place as he did four years earlier.</p><p xmlns="">1941 — Joe Louis knocks out Gus Dorazio in the second round at the Convention Hall in Philadelphia to defend his world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Philadelphia's Wilt Chamberlain hits the first of what would become an NBA record 35 consecutive field goals without a miss.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Raisa Smetanina wins a gold medal with the Unified Team in the 20-kilometer cross-country relay to set the career Winter Olympic Games medal record with 10. Smetanina, 39, also becomes the oldest champion and the first to win a medal in five straight Winter Games.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — San Antonio's David Robinson records the fourth quadruple-double in NBA history with 34 points, 10 rebounds, 10 assists and 10 blocks in the Spurs' 115-96 win over Detroit.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — The U.S. women's hockey team wins the sport's first-ever Olympic gold medal. Sandra Whyte scores on an empty-netter with 8 seconds left to give the United States a 3-1 victory over Canada.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Australia's Susie O'Neill shatters swimming's oldest record, breaking the 200-meter butterfly world mark with a time of 2:05.37 in a World Cup short-course meet at Malmo, Sweden. O'Neill broke the record of 2:05.65 set by Mary T. Meagher of the United States in 1981.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Arnold Palmer, 71, becomes the first player to shoot his age in a PGA Tour event since Sam Snead did 22 years ago. Palmer finishes the fourth round of the Bob Hope Classic with a 1-under 71. Joe Durant sets a 72-hole record of 29 under for a five-shot lead. Durant, with rounds of 65-61-67-66, breaks the 72-hole record for relation to par set by John Huston in the 1998 Hawaiian Open.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Americans Lindsey Vonn and Julia Mancuso captures gold and silver, respectively, in the women's Olympic downhill at Vancouver, British Columbia. It's the first time since 1984 that the United States captures the top two steps in a women's alpine skiing event. The second multi-podium performance of the day goes to Shani Davis who takes the gold and Chad Hedrick who grabs bronze in men's 1000-meter speedskating. Davis is the first U.S. male speedskater to successfully defend his Olympic title. Shaun White wins gold in the snowboard halfpipe to become the third American male to successfully defend an Olympic gold medal, joining Dick Button (figure skating, 1948 and 1952) and Davis.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Danica Patrick wins the Daytona 500 pole, becoming the first woman to secure the top spot for any Sprint Cup race.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Meryl Davis and Charlie White win the gold medal in ice dance, the first Olympic title in the event for the U.S.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Laura Dahlmeier leads Germany to the world title in the women's 4x6-kilometer relay, becoming the first biathlete to win a medal in 10 straight world championship races.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>