<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="65441f59-dd6d-0149-2d51-827cfb65ef9e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Mark Zeigler</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-OLY-ZEIGLER-COLUMN:SD — sports, itop (950 words)</title><summary>PYEONGCHANG, South Korea — Here’s the problem facing Shani Davis: He’s not fast enough any more to skate away from this.He used to be, winning two gold and two silver speedskating medals in the Olympics, winning 11 titles at World Championships,...</summary><sourceId>880f254d-66c0-1221-221c-48780a31fdb3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3372%kniht%r%BC-OLY-ZEIGLER-COLUMN:SD — sports, itop (950 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Mark Zeigler: Shani Davis might not be able to escape controversy this time</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Mark Zeigler</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">PYEONGCHANG, South Korea — Here’s the problem facing Shani Davis: He’s not fast enough any more to skate away from this.</p><p xmlns="">He used to be, winning two gold and two silver speedskating medals in the Olympics, winning 11 titles at World Championships, breaking world records nine times, breaking barriers in a sport as white as the ice it races on. But he’s 35 now, and the engine doesn’t rev like it used to when he hits the gas.</p><p xmlns="">It didn’t Tuesday in the 1,500 meters, blazing to a quick opening 300 and then, nothing. His time of 1:46.74 was nearly six seconds slower than the world record that he set in 2009 and held until last December. He finished 19th in a field of 35. In his previous three Olympic races at this distance, he was second, second and 11th.</p><p xmlns="">“The ice was super fast,” Davis said. “Unfortunately, I wasn’t.”</p><p xmlns="">And that’s a problem. Americans are obsessed with winning – I think we all can admit that – and glistening medals deflect biting criticism, or at least mute it. You get a pass, or more of one, if you stand on the podium and the flag is raised.</p><p xmlns="">Finish 19th, get blown away by the Dutch, fade badly in the back half of the race, and the microscopes come out, rightly or wrongly, fairly or unfairly. The knives come out.</p><p xmlns="">The hashtags grow fangs.</p><p xmlns="">Davis has never been a warm, fuzzy character. He’s never shied from controversy, never been afraid to speak his mind, getting into a public spat with a teammate over the relay in 2006, splitting with the sport’s national governing body and training on his own, ripping the U.S. Olympic Committee for a perceived lack of support, blaming suit manufacturer Under Armour for the team’s poor performance in Sochi.</p><p xmlns="">And that’s part of his allure, part of his complexity – a courage of his convictions, a certain nobility in his defiance, no matter how misguided the cause may seem.</p><p xmlns="">But he was winning then. He’s not now, which made extricating himself from his current hole harder even before he grabbed a shovel and kept digging.</p><p xmlns="">This is his fifth Olympic team – he left in 2002 before competing – and he no doubt reasoned that warranted the honor of carrying the U.S. flag at Opening Ceremony. Many of his U.S. teammates agreed, and it came down to him and luger Erin Hamlin in the pre-Games vote among athlete representatives from each of the eight winter sports federations.</p><p xmlns="">Davis got four votes. Hamlin got four.</p><p xmlns="">The rules, published beforehand, were clear: Any ties would be broken by a coin flip.</p><p xmlns="">The coin picked Hamlin, and Davis’ verified Twitter account soon was recounting his resume and suggesting that Team USA “dishonorably tossed a coin.” It added the hashtag: #BlackHistoryMonth.</p><p xmlns="">Out came the knives, and Davis has done nothing since to dull them.</p><p xmlns="">The afternoon of Opening Ceremony, there was word he would speak after a training session at the Gangneung Oval to clarify his radioactive tweet. Media was told to wait at the end of a hallway underneath the vast arena, and Davis would stop there.</p><p xmlns="">He turned the corner into the hallway … and blew past notebooks and tape recorders on the way to the bus. “Shani’s got training,” a handler said, forgetting, apparently, that he had just finished training.</p><p xmlns="">Where he was in such a hurry to get, we don’t know. We do know where he wasn’t going: Opening Ceremony.</p><p xmlns="">His handlers explained that he never intended to attend unless, of course, he had been selected flagbearer. It’s an empty excuse. Opening Ceremony can be a long night on your feet for athletes, but in recent Games organizers have provided a solution: You walk into the stadium, take a lap with your teammates around the infield, soak up the experience and then quietly exit through the back – get on a bus and you’re back at the village 15 minutes later.</p><p xmlns="">Tuesday, after finishing 19th in the 1,500 meters, Davis did stop in front of a gaggle of journalists. A U.S. media relations officer stated the ground rules: Skating questions only.</p><p xmlns="">After a few obligatory questions about his race, Davis was asked if he meant any disrespect toward Hamlin with his tweet. “Before we started this interview, we’re sticking to skating only questions,” he replied. “I’d like to continue focusing on skating questions.”</p><p xmlns="">(Except he hadn’t with Dutch media, saying in an interview: “You know, once every four years, my fifth Olympics, I thought it would be really special to hold the flag. I guess the USOC and the other people thought differently.”)</p><p xmlns="">The questions returned to skating. Davis spoke about how “I’ve seen people create Olympic magic in the 1,500 who have never even won World Cups before” and “it’s just that I didn’t have the snap and drive” and “I really hope this got all the cobwebs out and I can refocus.”</p><p xmlns="">He has one race left, the 1,000 meters on Feb. 23. The distance suits him better, but it’s a long way from 19th place in a race just 30 seconds longer to an Olympic medals podium. He knows that, too.</p><p xmlns="">“There are no excuses for not performing on the ice,” Davis said, “except for that I just wasn’t strong enough to compete with the high, top-level guys here.”</p><p xmlns="">The media officer asked if there were any further questions. There was one: Why didn’t he want to talk about anything else, why insist on discussing skating only given the past week?</p><p xmlns="">“I can go?” Davis asked, turning to the media officer and walking away briskly.</p><p xmlns="">Just not fast enough.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000180540,t000040194,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>