<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c0886d5d-7a8f-4687-b4da-30a47a37954c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0243</summary><sourceId>3b47663e-e3d9-49bd-9bd8-1ad64ce67d3b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z4025%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0243</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Saturday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — RHP Steve Geltz was suspended 100 games after a third positive test for a drug of abuse; Tampa Bay C Nick Ciuffo 50-game penalty for a second positive test for a drug of abuse; San Diego Padres RHP Alex Cunningham 50 games after testing positive for Amphetamine; and Pittsburgh 2B Mitchell Tolman 50-game after a second positive test for a drug of abuse.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Agreed to terms with RHP John Axford on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Designated 3B Matt Reynolds for assignment.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA PHILLIES — Agreed to terms with LHP Josh Tols on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW ORLEANS PELICANS — Waived G Rashad Vaughn and G Mike James.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK JETS — Signed DB Kacy Rodgers II to a reserve/future contract.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH STEELERS — Signed FB Roosevelt Nix to a four-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON OILERS — Recalled D Keegan Lowe from Bakersfield (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled G Alexandar Georgiev from Hartford (AHL) and G Chris Nell from Kansas City (ECHL) to Hartford.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON CAPITALS — Re-signed C Lars Eller to a five-year contract extension.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Returned D Desmond Bergin on loan to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LAVAL ROCKET — Returned F David Vallorani on loan to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE ADMIRALS — Recalled D Rick Pinkston from Atlanta (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Loaned F Luc-Olivier Blain to Laval (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY MAVERICKS — Added G Kent Nusbaum as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">TULSA OILERS — Released Jordan Neamonitis as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><p xmlns="">U.S. SOCCER — Elected Carlos Cordeiro president to a four-year term.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Released D Desmond Bergin from his professional tryout agreement.&lt;</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>