<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d705cc24-24a8-449e-8014-bd4d04525513" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Marc Levy</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Redistricting-Pennsylvania,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — Pennsylvania's high court issued a new congressional district map for the state's 2018 elections on its self-imposed deadline Monday, all but ensuring that Democratic prospects will improve in several seats and that...</summary><sourceId>254907af-4e23-48ff-8ff9-cdbc7f8fa5b8</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL0024%limit%u%BC-US--Redistricting-Pennsylvania,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Pennsylvania court issues overhauled congressional map</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Updates with details of new map. Adds background on map dispute. Will be updated.</p><byline xmlns="">By MARC LEVY</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — Pennsylvania's high court issued a new congressional district map for the state's 2018 elections on its self-imposed deadline Monday, all but ensuring that Democratic prospects will improve in several seats and that Republican lawmakers challenge it in federal court.</p><p xmlns="">The map of Pennsylvania's 18 congressional districts is to be in effect for the May 15 primary and substantially overhauls a congressional map widely viewed as among the nation's most gerrymandered. The map was approved in a 4-3 decision.</p><p xmlns="">Most significantly, the new map likely gives Democrats a better shot at winning seats in Philadelphia's heavily populated and moderate suburbs, where Republicans had held seats in bizarrely contorted districts, including one labeled "Goofy Kicking Donald Duck."</p><p xmlns="">The redrawn map could boost the Democratic Party's quest to capture control of the U.S. House and dramatically change Pennsylvania's predominantly Republican, all-male delegation.</p><p xmlns="">Meanwhile, sitting congressmen, dozens of would-be candidates and millions of voters have to sort out which district they live in barely a month before the candidates' deadline to submit paperwork to run.</p><p xmlns="">Republican lawmakers are expected to quickly challenge the map in federal court, arguing that legislatures and governors, not courts, have the constitutional responsibility to draw congressional maps.</p><p xmlns="">The Democratic-majority state Supreme Court ruled last month in a party line decision that the district boundaries unconstitutionally put partisan interests above neutral line-drawing criteria, such as keeping districts compact and eliminating municipal and county divisions.</p><p xmlns="">The decision is the first time a state court threw out congressional boundaries in a partisan gerrymandering case and handed a victory to the group of registered Democratic voters who sued last June in a lawsuit backed by the League of Women Voters.</p><p xmlns="">Candidates can start circulating petitions to run in their new district in a little over a week, Feb. 27. Pennsylvania has seen a surge in interest in running for Congress with six incumbents elected in 2016 not running again — the most in four decades — and Democrats vehemently opposing President Donald Trump.</p><p xmlns="">Pennsylvania's Republican delegation has provided a crucial pillar of support for Republican control of the U.S. House since 2010.</p><p xmlns="">Republicans who controlled the Legislature and governor's office after the 2010 census crafted it to elect Republicans and succeeded in that aim: Republicans won 13 of 18 seats in three straight elections under the now-invalidated map, even though Pennsylvania's statewide elections are often closely divided and registered Democratic voters outnumber Republicans.</p><p xmlns="">The new map will not apply to the March 13 special congressional election in southwestern Pennsylvania's 18th District between Republican Rick Saccone and Democrat Conor Lamb.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>