<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6ab6a352-0431-40b5-8be3-a53496ecc31f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Bouazza Ben Bouazza</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-EU--Tunisia-Central Bank</title><summary>TUNIS, Tunisia (AP) — Tunisia's prime minster has removed the governor of its central bank hours after the European Parliament put the North African country on a blacklist of non-EU nations amid fears it posed a risk over money laundering and...</summary><sourceId>bf16920f-6d87-417d-17d8-87bb0b49d802</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:EEE4603%-----%r%BC-EU--Tunisia-Central Bank;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Tunisia's bank governor is fired after EU blacklists nation</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow.</p><byline xmlns="">By BOUAZZA BEN BOUAZZA</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">TUNIS, Tunisia (AP) — Tunisia's prime minster has removed the governor of its central bank hours after the European Parliament put the North African country on a blacklist of non-EU nations amid fears it posed a risk over money laundering and terrorist financing.</p><p xmlns="">Prime Minister Youssef Chahed proposed Wednesday to replace Chedli Ayari with 58-year-old Marouane El Abassi, currently the representative of Tunisia and Libya to the World Bank.</p><p xmlns="">Tunisian media has accused the Central Bank of Tunisia under Ayari of turning a blind eye to "obscure transfers" received from non-governmental organizations and political parties.</p><p xmlns="">Lawmakers who opposed the inclusion of Tunisia on the EU blacklist said the burgeoning democracy needs support, not punishment, and the move discounts Tunisia's efforts to bolster its financial structures.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>