<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d9a373b0-9f97-4461-9e81-2e00c513aa3c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0677</summary><sourceId>642f3f11-4930-4ac7-ac78-db624522d18b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8022%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0677</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agreed to terms with 2B Jonathan Schoop on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA DIAMONDBACKS — Assigned OF Rey Fuentes outright to Reno (PCL).</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON NATIONALS — Signed a two-year player development contract extension with Harrisburg (EL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed OF/hitting coach Lew Ford.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed 1B Dean Green.</p><p xmlns="">OTTAWA CHAMPIONS — Sent RHP Alex Vargas to Lake Erie (Frontier) to complete an earlier trade.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Traded RHP Billy Roth to Nomal (Frontier) for a player to be named.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed RHP Kane McCall.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Traded RHP Justin Sinibaldi to Gary SouthShore (AA) for OF Cameron Newell.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Released RHPs Ben McKendall and Chance Simpson and LHP Mike Picucci.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN ILLINOIS MINERS — Named Steve Marino hitting coach.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Signed RHP Sam Burton, OF John Menken, and 2B Raul Shah.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Fined the L.A. Lakers $50,000 for violating the league's anti-tampering rule. Suspended Detroit F Willie Reed six games for a domestic violence incident.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's NBA</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES SPARKS — Re-signed G Alana Beard. Signed G Jolene Anderson and C Saicha Grant-Allen to training camp contracts.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS — Signed OL James Ferentz and Jason King, WRs Cody Hollister and Riley McCarron, DBs David Jones and Damarius Travis, CBs Ryan Lewis and Jomal Wiltz, LB Trevor Reilly and TE Will Tye.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Named Terrell Williams defensive line coach, Tony Dews running backs coach and Keith Carter offensive line coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Re-signed FB James Tuck. Signed DL DeVonte Fields and DB Monshadrik Hunter.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Re-signed DB Maurice Leggett to a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Recalled LW Nic Kerdiles from San Diego (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Reassigned F Michael Bournival to Syracuse (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Syracuse D Reid McNeill one game.</p><p xmlns="">BAKERSFIELD CONDORS — Assigned G Nick Riopel to Wichita (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LEHIGH VALLEY PHANTOMS — Returned G John Muse and Fs Alex Krushelnyski and Steven Swavely on loan to Reading (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MARLIES — Assigned F Jean Dupuy to Orlando (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TUCSON ROADRUNNERS — Assigned G Michael Houser to Fort Wayne (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">UTICA COMETS — Returned G Mitch Gillam on loan to Worcester (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Loaned D Matt Petgrave to Laval (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">FLORIDA EVERBLADES — Signed G Tyler Parks.</p><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Released G Doug Melvin as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY MAVERICKS — Signed F Garrett Klotz.</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Released G Brad Barone, D Tim Boyle and F Jack Ceglarski.</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Released G Joe Spagnoli as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">D.C. UNITED — Traded general allocation money to Toronto for targeted allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RED BULLS — Named Tom Bowden senior director/ticket sales and service, Darren Meyer senior director/marketing partnerships and premium services, Logan Smith director/strategy and analytics, Justin Baier senior manager/marketing and DJ McCaffrey senior manager/facility operations.</p><p xmlns="">SACRAMENTO REPUBLIC FC — Signed G Rafael Diaz.</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Signed M Felipe Gutierrez as designated player.</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO FC — Acquired $225,000 in general allocation money from D.C. United for $337,500 in targeted allocation money.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">METRO ATLANTIC ATHLETIC CONFERENCE — Named Phil Paquette director of new media/communications.</p><p xmlns="">BYU — Named AJ Steward running back coach.</p><p xmlns="">EARLHAM — Named Peggy Carl interim director of athletics.</p><p xmlns="">EMORY &amp; HENRY — Named Kyla King volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON — Announced junior QB Jacob Eason is transferring from Georgia.</p><p xmlns="">KENTUCKY — Suspended men's basketball F Tai Wynyard until further notice.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN CAL — Extended the contract of Clay Helton football coach through the 2023 season.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>