<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d0b5b93c-2922-4421-b344-562ff6f91d09" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-EU--Europe-Economy</title><summary>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — European Central Bank head Mario Draghi says it's too soon to declare victory over weak inflation — indicating it's too early to set a definite end date for the bank's money-printing stimulus despite a strengthening...</summary><sourceId>37dbd048-657b-48b2-8b2b-64d045d9cdd9</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:EEE1722%-----%r%BC-EU--Europe-Economy;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Draghi: too early to call time on money-printing stimulus</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — European Central Bank head Mario Draghi says it's too soon to declare victory over weak inflation — indicating it's too early to set a definite end date for the bank's money-printing stimulus despite a strengthening economy.</p><p xmlns="">Draghi's statement Monday prepared for a session of the European parliament in Strasbourg, France, called for "patience and persistence" in approaching monetary policy.</p><p xmlns="">He said that continuing economic growth means inflation will eventually tick up toward the bank's goal of just under 2 percent. Right now it is at an annual 1.3 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Draghi offered no hint of change in the bank's statement that it would continue purchasing 30 billion euros ($37 billion) per month in bonds at least through September, and longer if necessary. The purchases pump newly created money into the economy.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>