<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8f0e4e0d-2c6b-44ed-beac-9b62ca69dbcd" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0459</summary><sourceId>b4f0f764-4f87-46b2-6b2b-55fd589ef9da</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2597%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0459</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 4</hl2><p xmlns="">1861 — The Philadelphia Athletics beat Charter Oak 36-27 in a baseball game played on frozen Litchfield Pond in Brooklyn, N.Y., with the players wearing ice skates.</p><p xmlns="">1924 — The first Winter Olympics close in Chamonix, France. Sixteen countries competed in 17 events from seven sports.</p><p xmlns="">1932 — The Winter Olympics open in Lake Placid, N.Y., the first Winter Games in the United States.</p><p xmlns="">1957 — Joe McCarthy and Sam Crawford are elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — The 24 major league owners unanimously select Bowie Kuhn as commissioner for a one-year term at a salary of $100,000.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — The Baseball Hall of Fame establishes a separate section for players from the old Negro Leagues. In July, commissioner Bowie Kuhn, along with Hall president Paul Kirk, announce a change of heart and scrap plans for the separate section.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — U.S. District Court Judge John W. Oliver upholds the ruling of arbitrator Peter Seitz that declared Andy Messersmith and Dave McNally free agents.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Stars &amp; Stripes, skippered by Dennis Conner, sweeps Kookaburra III 4-0 at Fremantle, Australia, to bring sailing's America's Cup back to the United States.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — The doors of Cooperstown are slammed shut on Pete Rose when the Hall of Fame's board of directors votes 12-0 to bar players on the permanently ineligible list from consideration.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Jaromir Jagr scores three goals, including his 500th, for his 11th career hat trick as Washington beat Tampa Bay 5-1.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Peyton Manning is 25-of-38 for 247 yards and a touchdown as he rallies Indianapolis to a 29-17 Super Bowl victory over Chicago in the South Florida rain. Tony Dungy becomes the first black coach to win the championship, beating good friend and protege Lovie Smith in a game that featured the first two black coaches in the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Lindsey Vonn captures her 50th World Cup victory, winning the downhill with temperatures plunging to minus 13 on the demanding Kandahar course in Garmisch-Partenkirchen, Germany.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim gets his 1,000th victory with a 66-62 win over No. 9 Virginia. Officially it's victory No. 899 after the NCAA stripped him of 101 victories as part of punishment handed down in 2015 after a multiyear investigation of the school's athletic department.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Gregg Popovich becomes the winningest coach with a single franchise in NBA history, leading the San Antonio Spurs to a 121-97 victory over the Denver Nuggets. Popovich earns his 1,128th victory to pass former Utah coach Jerry Sloan for the mark.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>