<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ed4303df-af2c-6bdd-ecd2-01b6f8b063a5" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Joe Giglio</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKC-DUKE-UNC:RA — sports (500 words)</title><summary>CHAPEL HILL, N.C. — Turns out North Carolina is better at playing Duke’s game than Duke is theirs.With a free-flowing guard-based attack and a steady diet of 3-pointers, No. 21 UNC took the first meeting of the season between the Triangle...</summary><sourceId>7162d252-0449-296c-96c7-3ade416e2c62</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7763%knihr%r%BC-BKC-DUKE-UNC:RA — sports (500 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">UNC takes down Duke at its own game, 82-78</h2><byline xmlns="">By Joe Giglio</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">CHAPEL HILL, N.C. — Turns out North Carolina is better at playing Duke’s game than Duke is theirs.</p><p xmlns="">With a free-flowing guard-based attack and a steady diet of 3-pointers, No. 21 UNC took the first meeting of the season between the Triangle rivals.</p><p xmlns="">Senior Joel Berry scored 21 points to lead the Tar Heels to an 82-78 win over No. 9 Duke on Thursday night at the Smith Center.</p><p xmlns="">The season has been marked by a switch in traditional styles between the rivals.</p><p xmlns="">UNC (18-7, 7-5 ACC) has become the guard-based team while Duke has relied on its talented big men.</p><p xmlns="">Duke (19-5, 7-4) had its way inside in the first half but UNC used a blitz at the start of the second half to pick up its biggest win of the season.</p><p xmlns="">Junior guard Kenny Williams (20 points) made six 3-pointers and UNC finished with 11 3s. It was the first time since 2004, a span of 28 games, that the Heels outscored Duke from the 3-point line.</p><p xmlns="">UNC used a 16-2 run to start the second half to take control of the game.</p><p xmlns="">Down 49-45 at the half, the Tar Heels blasted out of the halftime gate to take a 61-51 lead after a layup by Williams at 15:49. Williams and Berry both made 3s during the run but other five baskets came in the teeth of the Duke defense.</p><p xmlns="">UNC was up 72-62 with 9:28 left before Duke made it interesting and had the ball down 74-71 with 3:30 left but Gary Trent (16 points) missed an open corner 3.</p><p xmlns="">With the window open to put the Devils away, Cam Johnson made a 3-pointer on UNC’s next trip and Berry made a pair of free throws with 2:29 left to push UNC’s margin back to 79-71.</p><p xmlns="">With the ACC regular-season all but out of reach and both teams out of sorts, there wasn’t as much anticipation for this game as usual.</p><p xmlns="">But that didn’t matter on Thursday at the Smith Center. It never does when these teams get together.</p><p xmlns="">The Blue Devils opened up by going inside and playing loose. They looked like a different team than the one that was upset by St. John’s last Saturday.</p><p xmlns="">With reserve forward Marques Bolden scoring inside and Trent knocking down outside shots, the Devils led by as many as 12 in the first half. A 3-pointer by Wendell Carter at 6:30 gave them a 40-28 advantage.</p><p xmlns="">But UNC kept it close. Johnson, who scored 32 points in last week’s loss at Clemson, had 13 points in the first half and Williams added 12.</p><p xmlns="">Williams made four of his first five 3-pointers and UNC finished the half 7 of 16 from behind the line.</p><p xmlns="">Duke never could exploit its advantage inside in the second half with Marvin Bagley scoring 15 points and Carter being held to 10.</p><p xmlns="">UNC, meanwhile, showed the Blue Devils they could beat them at their own game.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>