<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="3609e65f-69cc-495a-bb6c-228d4cee0e63" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0498</summary><sourceId>24953516-0cab-4d37-d37b-5b3a2e235df3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7831%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0498</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 20</hl2><p xmlns="">1887 — The International Association, the first minor league baseball association, is organized in Pittsburgh.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — The college point-shaving scandal prompts Long Island University to drop basketball and all other intercollegiate sports. LIU revives basketball in 1957.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — En route to a record 76-goal season, Boston's Phil Esposito becomes the first player to score his 50th goal in February, but the Bruins lose to the Los Angeles Kings 5-4.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — Larry Brown of the Denver Rockets sets ABA records for assists in a game (23), half (18) and quarter (10) during a 146-123 home win over the Pittsburgh Condors.</p><p xmlns="">1974 — Gordie Howe, the NHL's career scoring leader, comes out of retirement and signs a $1 million, four-year contract to play with the Houston Aeros of the WHA and sons Mark and Marty.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Muhammad Ali beats Jean-Pierre Coopman with a fifth-round knockout at the Roberto Clemente Coliseum in Puerto Rico to defend his world heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — In Calgary, Alberta, Brian Boitano of the U.S. wins the Olympic figure skating gold medal on a technical merit tiebreaker and nearly flawless free skate.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Julio Cesar Chavez records a fifth-round TKO over Greg Haugen in a WBC super lightweight title bout before a record crowd of 130,000 at Mexico City's Aztec Stadium.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Tara Lipinski, 15, becomes the youngest Olympic figure skating champion, beating fellow teen and U.S. teammate Michelle Kwan to take the gold. Lipinski is two months younger than Sonja Henie was in her 1928 victory.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Tanith Belbin and partner Ben Agosto end the U.S. medals drought in Olympic ice dance competition with a silver. The last to do so were Colleen O'Connor and James Millns, who won bronze in 1976.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Lindsey Van of the U.S. becomes the first female ski jumping world champion. Women's ski jumping makes its debut at this year's Nordic world championships in the Czech Republic. Todd Lodwick wins the opening Nordic combined event to give the U.S. two golds in one day. Before Van's victory, the U.S. had not won a gold at a Nordic worlds since 2003 when Johnny Spillane took a Nordic combined sprint.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Switzerland's Simon Ammann wins the large hill at the Vancouver Games to become the first ski jumper with four individual Olympic titles.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Trevor Bayne, 20, wins the Daytona 500, NASCAR's biggest race, in only his second Sprint Cup start.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Kobe Bryant wins his record-tying fourth All-Star game MVP award, scoring 37 points before his hometown fans and leading the West past the East 148-143.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Lindsey Vonn clinches a record 20th World Cup crystal globe title and surpasses Swedish great Ingemar Stenmark. It's Vonn's record eighth downhill title. Stenmark won 19 globes between 1975 and 1984.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>