<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6e4bd8c0-24d9-3172-d9ec-8550f52d8c26" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Mark Zeigler</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-OLY-ZEIGLER-COLUMN-JACOBELLIS:SD — sports, itop (850 words)</title><summary>Lindsey Jacobellis has won world championships of snowboard cross in 2005, 2007, 2011, 2015 and 2017. She has won X Games titles in 2003, 2004, 2005, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2014, 2015 and 2016. She has won 27 World Cup races.You know her for...</summary><sourceId>680eb1ef-7207-b4c9-4c9a-1c7fa447ec82</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7366%kniht%r%BC-OLY-ZEIGLER-COLUMN-JACOBELLIS:SD — sports, itop (850 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Mark Zeigler: Lindsey Jacobellis: The girl who lost gold tries to win acceptance</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Mark Zeigler</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Lindsey Jacobellis has won world championships of snowboard cross in 2005, 2007, 2011, 2015 and 2017. She has won X Games titles in 2003, 2004, 2005, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2014, 2015 and 2016. She has won 27 World Cup races.</p><p xmlns="">You know her for none of that.</p><p xmlns="">You know her as the girl who was leading the 2006 Olympic final by three seconds, by 47 yards, and decided for whatever reason — because she was so far ahead, because she was 20, because it’s snowboarding and that’s the kind of stuff you do, or maybe just because — to attempt an unnecessary, twisting, stylish method grab on the penultimate jump. She caught an edge on the landing, crashed, got up, couldn’t regain her speed and watched helplessly as Switzerland Tanja Frieden zoomed past for the gold.</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis, who recently moved to Laguna Niguel from Encinitas, knows herself as something else: history’s greatest snowboard cross racer, able to endure and dominate for more than a decade despite the continual ascent of young, hungry riders.</p><p xmlns="">“That’s true,” she says, “and I have a resume that supports that.”</p><p xmlns="">And within that dichotomy lies the beauty and the beast the Olympics, a shimmering opportunity to emerge from four years of anonymity to claim global glory or a cruel 45 minutes invalidating everything that came before it.</p><p xmlns="">The U.S. women’s hockey team understands the latter scenario. It keeps winning World Championships when no one is paying attention, and Canada keeps winning Olympic gold when everyone is.</p><p xmlns="">Complicating Jacobellis’ plight is her sport. It is an individual endeavor. It is patently unfair.</p><p xmlns="">Boardercross, as it’s sometimes called, puts six riders on the same steep, narrow, winding course with humps and jumps, and the guys in the TV production truck are hoping a couple of them end up in the side netting.</p><p xmlns="">“It’s unpredictable, it can be harsh, it’s got the crazy crashes,” says Jacobellis, 32. “It has everything spectators love, all those variables we can’t control. That’s also what makes it a frustrating sport but a very rewarding sport for an athlete. You can be training your heart out, and you’re in the first heat and somebody takes you out and you’re the top qualifier, and now you’re completely out of the race.</p><p xmlns="">“It can change on a dime like that.”</p><p xmlns="">She should know. Things were going fine in 2010 … until she suddenly swerved to avoid another rider and crashed through a gate, an automatic disqualification. Things were going fine in 2014, opening a big lead in the six-woman semifinal … until she inexplicably crashed on an innocuous roller near the bottom and finished last.</p><p xmlns="">She glides into the starting gate at an Olympics again Thursday night (San Diego time), with quarterfinal, semi and final runs held at Phoenix Snow Park over an anxious, harrowing 45 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis tries to keep calm, tries to offer perspective. What happened in 2006 doesn’t eat at her as much as the incessant questions about it, no matter how many world titles or X Games trophies she collects. The disarming smile turns frosty.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t look back at all,” she says rigidly. “Right now I’m here. What year is it? It’s 2018. We’re in Pyeongchang and I’m focusing on that.”</p><p xmlns="">Or: “There are the individuals who know the sport, and I love giving them more intimate, lengthy answers. But if somebody just comes in and doesn’t really know much about the sport, what really can I answer because they didn’t take the time to educate themselves on what I do? So I can really only connect with them on a certain level. I’m not frustrated with it. It’s just how it is.”</p><p xmlns="">For the past two years, Jacobellis has been regularly working with Denise Shull, a self-described “performance architect” (a fancy way of saying mental coach) who primarily advises financial traders in New York and hadn’t consulted with athletes before the U.S. snowboard cross coach Peter Foley connected them. Shull takes an unorthodox approach to confronting fears, and Foley figured why not — nothing else seemed to work.</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis also credits her move to Encinitas in 2010 after spending most of her life in Vermont or on the side of a frigid mountain. The warm weather, the ocean’s therapeutic powers, the zen of surfing, helped her unplug from the chaotic, capricious world of boardercross to “give my body that break it really, really needs and give more longevity to my career.”</p><p xmlns="">She is in her 15th season on the World Cup circuit now, with dozens of trophies, dozens of titles … and a single Olympic medal.</p><p xmlns="">“I know that was probably one of her biggest, hardest things to overcome in her career,” says fellow U.S. snowboard cross racer Faye Gulini, who was 13 when Jacobellis flew off that jump at the Torino Olympics, stylishly grabbed her board, crashed and lost gold more than won silver. “But in no other regard do I feel bad for her. She’s a five-time world champion. She has a pretty decorated career. And despite that mistake, she still got a silver medal.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t think that one event defines her.”</p><p xmlns="">Jacobellis is over it. But is anyone else?</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>