<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="32df5cbe-d7d1-49aa-8ecb-7a4c2c6207b1" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0328</summary><sourceId>e330487b-9479-4648-6489-9e8b2ea05ade</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0276%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0328</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Agreed to terms with LHP Hector Santiago on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA BRAVES — Agreed to terms with C Chris Stewart on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS CARDINALS — Agreed to terms with RHP Bud Norris on a one-year contract. Designated RHP Rowan Wick for assignment.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">GARY SOUTHSHORE RAILCATS — Signed LHP Lars Liguori.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed LHP Zach Dodson.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed INF Gianfranco Wawoe.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed LHP David Rollins.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed RHP Tyler Hunt and RHP Matt Oxner.</p><p xmlns="">JOLIET SLAMMERS — Signed RHP Connor Kelly.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed RHP Neil Kozikowski.</p><p xmlns="">RIVER CITY RASCALS — Signed OF Connor Oliver to a contract extension. Placed RHP Tim Koons and OF Brandon Thomas on the suspended list.</p><p xmlns="">SCHAUMBURG BOOMERS — Signed LHP James Murly and 1B/OF Ryan Rodriguez.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Women's National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES SPARKS — Signed G Cappie Pondexter.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA CARDINALS — Named Chris Achuff assistant defensive line caoch, Ray Brown offensive line coach, Alonso Escalante defensive quality control coach, Charlie Harbison assistant defensive backs coach, Don Johnson senior assistant defensive line coach, Randal McCray assistant special teams coach, David Merritt Sr. defensive backs coach, Jason Michael tight ends coach, Troy Rothenbuhler offensive quality control coach, Cameron Turner offensive assistant coach and Kirby Wilson running backs coach. Retained linebackers coach Larry Foote, wide receivers coach Kevin Garver, assistant offensive line coach Steve Heiden, quarterbacks coach Byron Leftwich, strength and conditioning coach Buddy Morris, and running backs coach Terry Allen.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA FALCONS — Named Bernie Parmalee running backs coach, Mayur Chaudhari assistant special teams coach and Chad Walker assistant offensive coach.</p><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BILLS — Named Terry Robiskie receivers coach.</p><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI BENGALS — Signed T Bobby Hart.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK JETS — Promoted quarterbacks coach Jeremy Bates to offensive coordinator. Named Rick Dennison offensive line coach/run game coordinator and Steve Jackson assistant defensive backs coach.</p><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO 49ERS — Signed C Daniel Kilgore to a three-year contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Re-signed LB Doug Parrish and WR Jamill Smith. Signed DBs Nick Taylor and Alex Gray, OLs Kwabena Asare and Mykhael Quave, DLs Kalonji Kashama and Nick Usher, WRs AJ Cruz and Devante Noil, RB Marion Grice, QB Zach Kline, LB Jon Walton and DL Darius Allen. Released DB Andrew Lue.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Signed WR Mitchell Baines to a two-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Assigned D Korbinian Holzer to San Diego (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled F Michael Mersch from Ontario (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Reassigned F Tage Thompson to San Antonio (AHL) and D Nolan De Jong to Colorado (ECHL). Announced San Antonio hae recalled F Brady Shaw from Colorado.</p><p xmlns="">VANCOUVER CANUCKS — Signed general manager Jim Benning to a multiyear contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended San Antonio F Klim Kostin one game for an illegal check to the head of an opponent in a game at Iowa on Feb. 12.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Utah F Travis Howe three games and fined him an undisclosed amount for an illegal check to the head of an opponent in a game at Rapid City on Feb. 10. Suspended Kansas City F Garrett Klotz eight games and Eric Freschi two games and fined them undisclosed amounts for their actions in a game at Toledo on Feb. 10.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RED BULLS — Acquired a 2019 fourth-round draft pick from Toronto for the right of first refusal for G Caleb Patterson-Sewell.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON SPIRIT — Elected to not retain the rights to G Stephanie Labbe for the 2018 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ARMADA FC — Transferred G Caleb Patterson-Sewell to Toronto (MLS).</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Premier Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">BOSTON CITY FC — Announced F Isaac Nana Addai is returning for the 2018 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CITADEL — Named Dave Zelenock volleyball coach.</p><p xmlns="">HAMPTON — Named Bobby Blizzard wide receivers coach and Kenyon Blue cornerbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">RADFORD — Named Scott Davis associate athletics director for advancement.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE — Announced Robert Gillespie, running backs coach, will not return next season.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>