<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Parkersburg (West Virginia) News and Sentinel' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="01cd2228-9ffb-45b6-a487-76ca9fb152b1" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Paul Lapann</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Parkersburg (West Virginia) News and Sentinel</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-WV--Exchange-Director-Local Film Festival,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>MARIETTA, Ohio (AP) — A former Vienna, West Virginia, resident has once again had a film selected for the Colony Short Film Festival at Peoples Bank Theatre in Marietta on March 1-3.Kevin Wines, a 1987 graduate of Parkersburg High School, now...</summary><sourceId>c284a1b4-2cb0-4949-949a-075480436aba</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:e2838%tntn-%r%BC-WV--Exchange-Director-Local Film Festival,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Vienna native's film selected for Marietta festival</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: An AP Member Exchange. Corrects dateline to Ohio instead of West Virginia</p><byline xmlns="">By PAUL LAPANN</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Parkersburg (West Virginia) News and Sentinel</bycr></p><p xmlns="">MARIETTA, Ohio (AP) — A former Vienna, West Virginia, resident has once again had a film selected for the Colony Short Film Festival at Peoples Bank Theatre in Marietta on March 1-3.</p><p xmlns="">Kevin Wines, a 1987 graduate of Parkersburg High School, now living in Knoxville, Tennessee, is the director of his film "The Designer," set for showing at the 12th annual local film festival. Wines also is the main character in the seven-minute film.</p><p xmlns="">Wines had films in the Marietta film festival in 2015 and 2016.</p><p xmlns="">"The Designer" was created as part of the seven-day shootout competition in the 2017 Knoxville Film Festival, Wines said.</p><p xmlns="">"My team drew the genre of mystery and we were required to have three elements: an actor over 50 (I had five actors over 50), a character who is happy and a character who is sad," Wines said.</p><p xmlns="">Wines said of his film, "Tom Godett suffers from needing a life. Spend a day with him to find out what a little mystery can bring him."</p><p xmlns="">"The Designer" won Best of Genre: Mystery in the Knoxville film competition and was nominated for Best Production Design and Best Supporting Actress — Rachel Stacy.</p><p xmlns="">Wines is not sure when "The Designer" will be shown at the Marietta film festival.</p><p xmlns="">Judges selected 20 films for this year's festival, which is sponsored by the Hippodrome/Colony Historical Theatre Association.</p><p xmlns="">Wines spent a month in Parkersburg in 2005 when he worked as a production assistant on the movie "Bubble," directed by Steven Soderbergh. "Bubble," filmed in Parkersburg and Belpre, involves a murder becoming the focal point of three people who work in a doll factory.</p><p xmlns="">Submitting movies into the Colony Short Film Festival gives Wines a reason to visit his hometown, he said.</p><p xmlns="">The film festival in Marietta occurs right before Wines' birthday on March 4.</p><p xmlns="">Last year on his birthday, when he turned 48 years old, Wines celebrated by making a movie in 48 hours. He turned that movie, "The Egg &amp; I," into a web series, which can be seen at www.tinyurl.com/y7yhwbg3 . Wines is the technical arts assistant at Cedar Springs Presbyterian Church in Knoxville.</p><p xmlns="">The film festival opens on Thursday, March 1 at 6 p.m. with a reception featuring hors d'oeuvres and a cash bar. A special screening of "Loving Vincent," a one-hour and 35-minute film, begins at 7 p.m. Artwork by Jolene Powell will be in the auditorium gallery.</p><p xmlns="">On Friday, March 2, festival screenings begin at 7 p.m. Festival screenings, workshops, filmmakers panels and awards will be from 1 p.m. to 11 p.m. on Saturday, March 3.</p><p xmlns="">The film festival is a showcase for independent films from across the United States and foreign countries, with a focus on featuring local and regional talent from the Ohio Valley, festival officials said.</p><p xmlns="">"The Colony Short Film Festival features selections from emerging and established short filmmakers that have ranged from innovative to off-the-wall and quirky to provocative," the festival said.</p><p xmlns="">Tickets and VIP passes for the Colony Short Film Festival are available at Peoples Bank Theatre website or by calling 740-371-5152.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>