<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="527c2e08-3da0-4407-a110-80117ec3b28d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0478</summary><sourceId>892d4e70-51e0-45c6-5c6a-35d7307f1af0</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9550%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0478</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BOSTON RED SOX — Traded OF Bryce Brentz to Pittsburgh for cash.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Placed RHP Trevor May on the 60-day DL. Agreed to terms with RHP Anibal Sanchez on a one-year contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA DIAMONDBACKS — Placed RHP Shelby Miller on the 60-day DL.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA BRAVES — Designated RHP Mauricio Cabrera for assignment. Agreed to terms with RHP Peter Moylan.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Placed RHP Nick Burdi on the 60-day DL.</p><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO GIANTS — Designated RHP Joan Gregorio for assignment.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed RHP Tyler Herron.</p><p xmlns="">ST. PAUL SAINTS — Signed INF Brady Shoemaker.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX CITY EXPLORERS — Signed INF Nelson Ward.</p><p xmlns="">WICHITA WINGNUTS — Signed 1B Luis Jimenez and OF Stephen Aluko. Traded OF Richard Prigatano to Sugar Land (Atlantic) for a player to be named.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed LHP Kevin McGovern.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed LHP Bennett Parry.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">ROCKLAND BOULDERS — Signed RHP Markus Solbach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">CHARLOTTE HORNETS — Fired general manager Rich Cho.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE JAGUARS — Exercised their 2018 options on TE Marcedes Lewis and OL Tyler Shatley and Josh Wells.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY BUCCANEERS — Released RB Doug Martin.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Re-signed DB Aaron Grymes to a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Signed DB Tevin Homer and WR Corey Washington.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Reassigned F Morgan Klimchuk to Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Recalled G Jared Coreau from Grand Rapids (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Traded D Nick Holden to Boston for D Rob O'Gara and a 2018 third-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">VANCOUVER CANUCKS — Signed D Erik Gudbranson to a three-year contract extension.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Syracuse F Alex Gallant two games.</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed D Joey Leach to a professional tryout agreement.</p><p xmlns="">LEHIGH VALLEY PHANTOMS — Recalled F Alex Krushelnyski on loan from Reading (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SOUNDERS — Signed M/F Lamar Neagle and G Calle Brown.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">NCAA — Upheld sanctions on Louisville's men's basketball program, which include vacating its 2013 NCAA championship and 123 victories between 2012-15.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN — Named Jim McElwain wide receivers coach.</p><p xmlns="">MISSISSIPPI STATE — Announced the resignation of baseball coach Andy Cannizaro. Promoted pitching coach Gary Henderson to interim head coach.</p><p xmlns="">PENN STATE — Promoted trainer Renee Messina to assistant athletic director for athletic training services.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>