<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9a9d1de7-7a9d-5662-b08b-6f76a7296414" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kevin Acee</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER:SD — sports (450 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — The Padres got their man.The team and free agent first baseman Eric Hosmer have agreed to a deal, two sources said Saturday night.Terms were not available, but this will certainly be the largest monetary commitment in Padres...</summary><sourceId>a51e73c9-c085-7666-666e-a8d85581ed62</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K0867%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-HOSMER:SD — sports (450 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres, Eric Hosmer agree to terms</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Kevin Acee</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — The Padres got their man.</p><p xmlns="">The team and free agent first baseman Eric Hosmer have agreed to a deal, two sources said Saturday night.</p><p xmlns="">Terms were not available, but this will certainly be the largest monetary commitment in Padres history.</p><p xmlns="">According to John Morosi of MLB.com, Hosmer received an eight-year deal with an opt-out clause after the fifth season.</p><p xmlns="">This will push first baseman Wil Myers, whose six-year, $83 million deal signed in 2017 was the team’s biggest contract ever, to the outfield. Myers, who played with Hosmer briefly in Single-A while in the Royals’ system, has said he would be happy to move if it meant the Padres got Hosmer.</p><p xmlns="">The 28-year-old hit .318 with a .385 on-base percentage in 2017, both career highs. He hit 25 home runs for the second season in a row.</p><p xmlns="">The Padres coveted Hosmer for his ability to get on base and the leadership they believe he can provide their young team.</p><p xmlns="">Several people in the organization have said in recent days they believed his presence would make them a contender in the National League.</p><p xmlns="">However, this acquisition is also about the long term.</p><p xmlns="">The Padres’ background work talking with several dozen coaches, players and others who know Hosmer has turned up exclusively positive reports regarding his work ethic and leadership abilities. Additionally, Hosmer is bilingual, which would be a commodity in connecting in an increasingly Latin-infused clubhouse.</p><p xmlns="">“Hos is a great teammate,” said Padres pitcher Chris Young, a member of the Royals’ 2015 World Series championship team. “One of my favorites. He shows up every day. He’s energetic. He knows how to work. He takes care of himself. He’s competitive between the line but knows how to have fun in a clubhouse. The ultimate teammate and competitor. I love him.”</p><p xmlns="">Hosmer was a hero of that championship team.</p><p xmlns="">His ninth-inning double scored the Royals’ first run in Game 5 of the 2015 World Series against the New York Mets, and his dash home on a ground ball tied the game, which the Royals won in 11 innings for their first championship in 30 years.</p><p xmlns="">Hosmer batted just .190 that series but drove in six runs in the five games. In the Royals’ 2014 World Series loss to the San Francisco Giants, he batted .250 and drove in four runs.</p><p xmlns="">He played in all 162 games last season and has averaged 153 games over the past six seasons.</p><p xmlns="">He has a career batting average of .284, career on-base percentage of .342 and career slugging percentage of .439. He has won four Gold Gloves in his seven seasons and was an All-Star in 2016.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000424479,t000007391,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>