<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="83fe6104-bc85-5004-9169-8a295b3aa513" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Mark Zeigler</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-OLY-FIGSKATE-KNIERIM:SD — sports, itop (800 words)</title><summary>GANGNEUNG, South Korea — “Jailbreak” is a song by Australian rock band AC/DC, from its 1976 album “Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap.” The music video shows guitarist Angus Young and two other band members doing hard labor in a prison camp, then...</summary><sourceId>ec239a15-c435-9e3f-e3f2-0e0ae1685016</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K5430%kniht%r%BC-OLY-FIGSKATE-KNIERIM:SD — sports, itop (800 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Ramona’s Chris Knierim moves closer to Olympic figure skating medal</h2><byline xmlns="">By Mark Zeigler</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">GANGNEUNG, South Korea — “Jailbreak” is a song by Australian rock band AC/DC, from its 1976 album “Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap.” The music video shows guitarist Angus Young and two other band members doing hard labor in a prison camp, then blowing the gates and breaking out. Lead singer Bon Scott gets shot, though, trying to escape.</p><p xmlns="">This is what U.S. figure skater Bradie Tennell, born 22 years later, was listening to in headphones before taking the ice for the ladies short program Saturday night (San Diego time) in the Olympic team event at the Gangneung Ice Arena.</p><p xmlns="">Whatever works. American hopes for a medal escaped without getting shot.</p><p xmlns="">Tennell delivered a clean if conservative program, followed by a good-enough effort by Chris Knierim and wife Alexa in the pairs free program — the two supposed weak links — to put Team USA in third place with one day remaining.</p><p xmlns="">“We did what we needed to do for the team,” Chris Knierim said. “It’s a team effort. Everybody has to put in their work, and I think that we did a good job for our part of the team.”</p><p xmlns="">The team event concludes Sunday night with free programs in men’s, ladies and dance. The field is cut from 10 to five after the short programs, and all five remain in contention for medals.</p><p xmlns="">Russia vaulted to first with 43 points after a world-record short program score from Evgenia Medvedeva, erasing any doubts about the cracked bone in her foot that sidelined her for the Grand Prix season. Next was Canada (41), followed by the United States (36), Italy (35) and Japan (32) in a tight battle for the bronze.</p><p xmlns="">With that in mind, U.S. coaches asked the Knierims to play it safe and replace their signature move — a quadruple twist (Alexa makes four revolutions above Chris’ head, horizontal to the ground, before he catches her) — with a more routine triple twist. And they obliged.</p><p xmlns="">The quad twist had become symbolic of Alexa’s return to the ice after three abdominal surgeries in late 2016 to repair a rare intestinal disorder that nearly ended her career. They re-inserted it into their programs for the U.S. championships last month and vowed to “go for it” at the Olympics.</p><p xmlns="">“True, but because we have the two free programs (in the team and individual pairs events) we weren’t super pressured on fighting back about it,” Chris said. “We’re going to be doing it in the free skate in the next event.</p><p xmlns="">“In the individual event, it can change the placements a lot heavier than in this event, because there are so many more teams and a lot of teams are bunched up point-wise. If we do the quad, we have to do it well. Otherwise, our triple twist is worth more than our quad. So you weigh your options.”</p><p xmlns="">In the end, it probably didn’t matter. Italy’s Ondrej Hotarek and Valentina Marchei, who finished ninth to the Knierim’s 10th at the World Championships last year, had the skate of their life and scored a career-best 138.44. The Knierims got 126.56 after Chris fell on the first half of their side-by-side combination jumps.</p><p xmlns="">That put them fourth out of the five pairs but, importantly, ahead of the Japanese pairs — extending the lead against the team that figures to be the biggest threat to preserving a bronze medal.</p><p xmlns="">And much-maligned U.S. pairs skating, remember, was supposed to drag down the rest of team here.</p><p xmlns="">Instead, the Knierims bailed out the U.S. after Nathan Chen inexplicably bombed in the men’s short. And then held it together after a shaky start to their free program.</p><p xmlns="">“I’ve kind of blocked out and stopped listening to the negativity of American pairs,” Alexa said. “It’s kind of obnoxious, in my opinion. We’re doing our best. To be the one (U.S.) team here, we need all the support we can get. We try our best to ignore it.”</p><p xmlns="">Earlier in the day, as expected, Americans Maia and Alex Shibutani were second in the dance short program behind Canada’s Tessa Virtue and Scott Moir.</p><p xmlns="">The Russian team — Olympic Athletes from Russia — literally jumped into first after a record performance in the ladies short by two-time defending world champion Medvedeva.</p><p xmlns="">Her score of 81.06 is a world record for a ladies short program, breaking her own mark set last year. She was the first, and still only, woman to crack the 80-point barrier.</p><p xmlns="">“At this point I am happy with my result, but the performance was a bit tough, probably because it was my first time on the Olympic ice,” Medvedeva said. “I know what I can do better. On a scale of five, I’d give myself a four, maybe a bit less — a four minus a quarter. I know how I can skate in practice and I know that I can be more confident in myself.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000418078,t000040194,t000003183,t000003669</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>