<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9862fb15-2fd9-411e-ac47-e137a62f9c6d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0731</summary><sourceId>43295908-4014-4d62-d629-e9ba4de141cb</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z4389%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0731</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">COMMISSIONER'S OFFICE — Suspended Baltimore 3B Jaime Estrada (GCL Orioles) and L.A. Angels RHP Andrew Vinson (Burlington-MWL) 50 games for violations of the Minor League Drug Prevention and Treatment Program.</p><p xmlns="">MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL — Named Stu Scheurwater full-time umpire. Promoted umpire Mark Wegner to crew chief.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Agreed to terms with LHPs Aaron Bummer, Ian Clarkin and Jace Fry; RHPs Carson Fulmer, Lucas Giolito, Gregory Infante, Reynaldo Lopez, Juan Minaya, Jose Ruiz and Thyago Vieira; Cs Omar Narvaez and Kevan Smith; INFs Matt Davidson, Casey Gillaspie, Yoan Moncada, Jose Rondon and Tyler Saladino; and OFs Micker Adolfo, Luis Alexander Basabe, Ryan Cordell, Nicky Delmonico, Adam Engel, Willy Garcia, Eloy Jimenez, Daniel Palka and Charlie Tilson on one-year contracts.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with RHP Carlos Torres on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT TIGERS — Designated LHP Jairo Labourt for assignment. Agreed to terms with LHP Francisco Liriano on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK YANKEES — Agreed to terms with OF Shane Robinson on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Placed LHP Joe Palumbo on the 60-day DL. Agreed to terms with RHP Jesse Chavez on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES DODGERS — Placed LHP Julio Urias on the 60-day DL. Claimed RHP J.T. Chargois off waivers from Minnesota.</p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO PADRES — Released C Rocky Gale.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">ROCKLAND BOULDERS — Signed INF Cody Regis.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WIZARDS — Signed G Ramon Sessions to a 10-day contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE JAGUARS — Signed coach Doug Marrone, executive vice president Tom Coughlin and general manager Dave Caldwell to two-year contract extensions through the 2021 season.</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS COWBOYS — Named Kellen Moore quarterbacks coach, Sanjay Lal receivers coach, Paul Alexander offensive line coach, Ken Amato defensive assistant, Doug Colman assistant special teams coach, Doug Nussmeier tight ends coach, Makus Paul assistant strength coach and Kris Richard passing game coordinator/defensive backs coach. Promoted Ben Bloom to linebackers coach and Keith O'Quinn to special teams coach.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SEAHAWKS — Named Jethro Franklin assistant defensive line coach, Larry Izzo assistant special teams coach and Steve Shimko offensive assistant coach.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Activated D Jan Rutta from injured reserve.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Assigned F Dylan Sadowy from Grand Rapids (AHL) to Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">EDMONTON OILERS — Assigned G Shane Starrett from Bakersfield (AHL) to Wichita (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK ISLANDERS — Agreed to terms with F Josh Bailey on a six-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">GRAND RAPIDS GRIFFINS — Assigned D Patrick McCarron to Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">MANITOBA MOOSE — Returned G Austin Lotz to Jacksonville (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SYRACUSE CRUNCH — Returned F Pierre-Luc Mercier to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Quad City LW Triston Grant five games and Idaho F Justin Parizek two games.</p><p xmlns="">ALLEN AMERICANS — Added G Thomas Hodges as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Signed D Sean Escobedo.</p><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Signed D Alex Vazquez.</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Signed F Guillaume Naud.</p><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Signed F Michael Neville.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY MAVERICKS — Released F Nick Miglio.</p><p xmlns="">QUAD CITY MALLARDS — Loaned F Gergo Nagy to Chicago (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">TULSA OILERS — Signed F Bobby Watson.</p><hl2 xmlns="">OLYMPIC SPORTS</hl2><p xmlns="">USA SWIMMING — Announced the resignation of senior director of Safe Sport Susan Woessner.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS CREW — Signed Graham Ellix and Nenad Stojkovic.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON SPIRIT — Signed Ds Whitney Church and Estelle Johnson.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">ILLINOIS — Named Gill Byrd defensive passing game coordinator and safeties coach. Promoted defensive coordinator/linebackers coach Hardy Nickerson to assistant head coach in addition to his other duties.</p><p xmlns="">SYRACUSE — Named Tim McAuliffe graduate assistant offensive football coach, Travis Greene offensive quality control coach, John Gunter recruiting quality control assistant and David Scorzelli and Sean Teter assistant strength and conditioning coaches.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>