<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="d80969ce-3654-4fb7-96b9-409cb3ca63eb" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0530</summary><sourceId>3e0fbbaa-9d1f-433b-33bb-eeb9a55299ff</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z3748%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0530</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 24</hl2><p xmlns="">1960 — Bill Cleary's four goals lead the United States to a 9-1 victory over West Germany in the hockey championship round of the Winter Olympics in Squaw Valley, Calif.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Wilt Chamberlain of Philadelphia shoots 18-for-18 from the field against the Baltimore Bullets, an NBA record for field goals in a game without a miss.</p><p xmlns="">1978 — Kevin Porter of the New Jersey Nets sets an NBA record with 29 assists in a 126-112 victory over the Houston Rockets.</p><p xmlns="">1980 — The United States hockey team wins the gold medal with a 4-2 victory over Finland at the Winter Olympics in Lake Placid, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Jim Kelly of the Houston Gamblers passes for a USFL-record 574 yards and five touchdowns in a 34-33 comeback-win over the Los Angeles Express. Kelly, completes 35 of 54 passes, including three for touchdowns in the final 10 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — An unprecedented winner of the 90-and 70-meter individual events, Matti Nykanen becomes the Winter Olympics' first triple gold medalist in Nordic skiing when Finland wins the new 90-meter team ski jumping event.</p><p xmlns="">1993 — Steve Yzerman of the Detroit Red Wings scores his 1,000th career point with two goals and two assists in a 10-7 loss to Buffalo Sabres.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Lipscomb's John Pierce becomes college basketball's career scoring leader with 33 points in his regular-season finale, a 119-102 win over Cumberland. Pierce's 4,110 points break former roommate Phil Hutcheson's record of 4,106.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Svetlana Feofanova breaks the pole vault indoor world record for the fourth time this month, clearing 15 feet, 6 1/2 inches at the Gaz de France meet.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — Joe Sakic scores two goals, including the game-winner, and two assists, and Jarome Iginla scores twice as Canada beat the United States 5-2 for the gold medal at the Winter Olympics. It's the seventh time Canada has won the gold in its national sport, but the first since 1952.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Julia Mancuso earns a stunning victory in the giant slalom to salvage a disappointing Olympics for the U.S. women in their final Alpine event of the Turin Games. Mancuso gives the American women their first Olympic Alpine medal since Picabo Street's gold in the super-G at the 1998 Nagano Games.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Tiger Woods wins the Accenture Match Play Championship, his fifth straight tournament victory. Woods overwhelms Stewart Cink with 14 birdies in 29 holes for an 8-and-7 victory, the largest margin in the final in the 10-year history of this tournament.</p><p xmlns="">2009 — Syracuse beats St. John's 87-58 to give coach Jim Boeheim his record 31st 20-win season. Boeheim breaks the tie with former North Carolina coach Dean Smith for the Division I record for 20-win seasons.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Missy Parkin becomes the first woman to reach the match play finals in the 69th U.S Open at Brunswick Zone-Carolier. Shafer, a 25-year Professional Bowlers Association Tour veteran, completes the 26-game qualifying portion of the U.S. Open with a total of 5,825 pins - averaging at a 224.04 pace.</p><p xmlns="">___</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>