<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c63d9fbf-ed41-9c5f-3b1e-74d7a6e922a0" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Rob Nikolewski</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AUTO-SALES:SD — business (700 words)</title><summary>For the third straight year, sales for new cars and trucks in California exceeded 2 million and the forecast for 2018 anticipates the number to top 2 million again — but just barely, as the rate of growth is slowing.New vehicle registrations...</summary><sourceId>c5798ef8-5853-1959-959d-6a0f51f92996</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K6479%kniht%r%BC-AUTO-SALES:SD — business (700 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">California vehicle sales exceed 2 million for third straight year</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Rob Nikolewski</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">For the third straight year, sales for new cars and trucks in California exceeded 2 million and the forecast for 2018 anticipates the number to top 2 million again — but just barely, as the rate of growth is slowing.</p><p xmlns="">New vehicle registrations reached 2.047 million units in 2017, down from 2.088 million in 2015, which was one of the strongest years ever recorded by the California New Car Dealers Association (CNCDA), which releases sales figures each quarter.</p><p xmlns="">About 2.01 million cars and trucks are expected to be sold this year.</p><p xmlns="">“That’s the California new vehicle market — it’s 2 million a year, pretty stable,” said Brian Maas, the CNCDA president. “That seems to be the place where the market is sitting when it’s healthy.”</p><p xmlns="">The new car market has plateaued after seven straight years of significant increases. Registrations in the final three months of 2017 were down 1.2 percent over the fourth quarter of 2016, marking the third straight quarter of slight declines.</p><p xmlns="">While the numbers dipped last year, they were still nearly twice as large compared to the lowest point of the Great Recession in 2009 when 1.04 million registrations were recorded in the Golden State.</p><p xmlns="">The 2017 sales figures underscored a trend — consumers are buying fewer cars and more pickup trucks and SUVs.</p><p xmlns="">Light truck sales were up 10.3 percent across the state while car sales dipped 7.4 percent. Dealers and auto analysts say the combination of relatively low gasoline prices in the past three years, better fuel efficiency for trucks and SUVs plus the desire for roomier vehicles account for the shift.</p><p xmlns="">“Unemployment is low and you look at survey research that indicates people feel fairly good relatively speaking about their economic situation and when they do, they tend to buy more light trucks or bigger vehicles,” Maas said.</p><p xmlns="">The top four-selling vehicles in the state were cars but five of the remaining six in the top 10 were light trucks and SUVs.</p><p xmlns="">Among three selected regional markets, San Diego County experienced the biggest drop in car sales — down 13.2 percent — while light truck registrations were up 7.1 percent for the year.</p><p xmlns="">Even the San Francisco area saw a 9.2 percent increase in pickup trucks and SUVs and a 5.8 percent drop in car registrations.</p><p xmlns="">Los Angeles/Orange County experienced a 12.2 percent drop in sales of cars and a 7.3 percent bump in light trucks.</p><p xmlns="">The market for alternative vehicles experienced a solid 2017. The market share for electric, plug-in hybrids and hybrid vehicles in 2017 reached 9.4 percent.</p><p xmlns="">Chevrolet in 2017 rolled out the Bolt, an electric vehicle (EV) boasting a range of 238 miles between charges and a price tag — after federal and state incentives — of about $30,000.</p><p xmlns="">Dealers sold or leased 13,487 Bolts last year, making it the top-selling sub-compact in the CNCDA report.</p><p xmlns="">“I think more significant is the broader market for EVs is maturing,” Maas said. “Many more manufacturers than even a year ago have some kind of plug-in or EV product in the space. If you’re interested in those types of vehicles you have a lot more choice than you did before.”</p><p xmlns="">Tesla is not a member of the CNCDA but the electric car maker was included in the quarterly report detailing sales figures by brand. Telsa recorded a 36.1 percent increase in the fourth quarter of last year compared to 2016.</p><p xmlns="">That number may grow in 2018, considering that Tesla is beginning to deliver — albeit with some delays — its Model 3, which has a stripped-down price of $35,000 and is aimed at attracting middle-class buyers.</p><p xmlns="">About 13,000 more electric vehicles were sold in the fourth quarter of 2017 compared to the final three months of 2016. That’s a healthy increase but to put things in perspective, the best selling full-size pickup truck in the state — the Ford F Series — outsold all EVs combined in 2017 (55,249 units to 53,549).</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">Best Selling Vehicles in California, 2017</p><p xmlns="">1. Honda Civic 94,525</p><p xmlns="">2. Honda Accord 72,037</p><p xmlns="">3. Toyota Camry 65,671</p><p xmlns="">4. Toyota Corolla 55,738</p><p xmlns="">5. Ford F Series 55,249</p><p xmlns="">6. Toyota RAV4 51,054</p><p xmlns="">7. Chevy Silverado 42,724</p><p xmlns="">8. Honda CR-V 42,449</p><p xmlns="">9. Toyota Prius 40,735</p><p xmlns="">10. Toyota Tacoma 37,478</p><p xmlns="">Source: IHS Markit</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000047103,t000002537,t000047405,t000002676,t000132082,t000032262,t000046807,g000065558,g000362661,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>