<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="81281701-70fa-4842-8e65-36e3c0852b2a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-EU--Europe-Latvia Corruption-The Latest</title><summary>LONDON (AP) — The Latest on the bribery investigation on the Latvian central bank chief (all times local):6:05 p.m.Latvian state TV reports that the country's central bank chief has been released from detention on bail pending an investigation...</summary><sourceId>1a72c2c3-e679-4cae-cae8-4fa66bd1e492</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:W1479%asian%u%BC-EU--Europe-Latvia Corruption-The Latest;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">The Latest: Latvian central bank chief is released on bail</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: With AP Photos.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">LONDON (AP) — The Latest on the bribery investigation on the Latvian central bank chief (all times local):</p><p xmlns="">6:05 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Latvian state TV reports that the country's central bank chief has been released from detention on bail pending an investigation into suspected bribery.</p><p xmlns="">The channel showed Ilmars Rimsevics speaking to reporters Monday evening and saying that he "rejects everything" that has been alleged about him. An Associated Press investigation found that a Latvian bank is accusing Rimsevics of seeking bribes for years, abusing his power and being connected to individuals involved in money laundering from Russia.</p><p xmlns="">Rimsevics was detained on Saturday evening after questioned by Latvia's anti-corruption authorities.</p><p xmlns="">The state TV quoted Rimsevics' lawyer, Saulvedis Varpins, as saying that more information on the case will be provided Tuesday.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">4:20 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Executives at Latvian bank Norvik say the nation's central bank chief, who was detained Saturday without charges, sought to extort money from their firm for years.</p><p xmlns="">Latvia Central bank chief Ilmars Rimsevics faces a criminal investigation for bribery but is not charged so far.</p><p xmlns="">Norvik has filed an international complaint against Latvia in which it claims a "Senior Latvian Official" sought bribes from the bank and abused his power. Norvik's CEO, Oliver Bramwell, told The Associated Press: "The high-level official mentioned in our request for arbitration is Rimsevics."</p><p xmlns="">Norvik's chairman, Grigory Guselnikov, also told the AP how individuals connected to Rimsevics had asked his bank to launder money from Russia.</p><p xmlns="">Rimsevics is also on the highest policymaking council of the European Central Bank, which sets monetary policy for the 19 euro countries.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>