<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="23733bc6-23d9-488e-a179-ac1b78328dd6" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0497</summary><sourceId>855371b6-0f8c-40b2-0b28-2aad495f49e1</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6843%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0497</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 13</hl2><p xmlns="">1923 — The New York Renaissance, the first all-black pro basketball team, is organized. Rens become one of the dominant basketball teams of the 1920s and 1930s.</p><p xmlns="">1937 — Maribel Vinson wins her ninth and final U.S. figure skating singles championship. Robin Lee wins his third straight men's title.</p><p xmlns="">1937 — The NFL Redskins move from Boston to Washington.</p><p xmlns="">1948 — Dick Button, the Olympic gold medalist, beats Hans Gerschwiler again to win the men's World Figure Skating championship in Davos, Switzerland.</p><p xmlns="">1954 — Furman's Frank Selvey scores 100 points in a 149-95 victory over Newberry. Selvey breaks the record of 73 points set by Temple's Bill Mlkvy in 1951. He makes 41 field goals and 18 free throws.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — Frank Mahovlich of the Montreal Canadiens scores his 1,000th career point with an assist in a 7-6 loss to the Philadelphia Flyers.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Julius Erving, playing in his first NBA All-Star Game, is voted MVP after finishing with 30 points and 12 rebounds. His East team loses 125-124.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Bryan Trottier of the New York Islanders becomes the 15th NHL player to reach 500 goals, scoring in the second period of a 4-2 loss to the Calgary Flames.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Tommy Moe wins the downhill over local hero Kjetil Andre Aamodt at the Winter Olympics in Lillehammer, Norway. Moe wins by 0.04 seconds, the closest Alpine race in Olympic history. Norwegian speedskater Johann Olav Koss sets a world record in the 5,000 meters, winning gold in 6 minutes, 34.96 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">1995 — Connecticut's men's basketball team is ranked No. 1 in the AP poll, joining the school's women's team. It is the first time a school's men's and women's basketball teams were simultaneously No. 1.</p><p xmlns="">1999 — Steve Jaros rolls the 13th televised 300 game in PBA history en route to winning the Chattanooga Open.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — In St. Anton, Austria, Fritz Strobl and Werner Franz finish with identical times of 1 minute, 20.72 seconds to win an icy and treacherous super-G, the second tie in World Cup history.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Teresa Phillips of Tennessee State becomes the first woman to coach in men's Division I, but her team loses its 17th straight game — 71-56 at Austin Peay.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Ted Ligety wins the giant slalom at world championships held at Beaver Creek, Colo. Ligety defeats Austrian rival Marcel Hirscher by 0.45 seconds for his third straight world giant slalom title.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Gabby Williams scores a career-high 26 points and Napheesa Collier adds 18 to help top-ranked UConn to its 100th consecutive victory with a 66-55 win over No. 6 South Carolina.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Kawhi Leonard scores 32 points and San Antonio clinches its NBA-record 20th consecutive winning season with a 110-106 victory over Indiana. The Spurs improve to 42-13 in the season following Tim Duncan's retirement.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>