<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f6d767cc-6ba1-46a7-a23b-b899f24db8c2" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0472</summary><sourceId>9ae827c9-6c12-492c-92ca-6b0fcdae9d09</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z9992%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0472</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Named Adam Esselman coordinator of baseball information.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Named Dave Duncan pitching consultant. Agreed to terms with LHP Xavier Cedeno, INF Jake Elmore and RHPs Jeanmar Gomez and Bruce Rondon on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with RHP Stephen Fife on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Tyler Cloyd, Jumbo Diaz, Javy Guerra, Drew Rucinski, Jacob Turner, and Alex Wimmers; LHP Mike Kickham; C Bryan Holaday; INFs Cristhian Adames, Johnny Giavotella, Yadiel Rivera, and Jonathan Rodriguez, and OFs Rafael Ortega, JB Shuck, and Scott Van Slyke on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Renewed their player development contract with Columbia (SAL) through the 2020 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed LHP Andrew Barbosa.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BULLS — Acquired C Willie Reed and the right to swap 2022 second-round draft picks from Detroit for G Jameer Nelson and them waived Reed.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND CAVALIERS — Acquired G Jordan Clarkson and F Larry Nance Jr. from the Los Angeles Lakers for G Isaiah Thomas, F Channing Frye and a 2018 protected first-round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA DREAM — Signed F Angel McCoughtry to a multiyear contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Placed Fs Marcus Kruger and Josh Jooris on waivers.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Recalled F Jimmy Hayes from his conditioning loan to Binghamton (AHL). Acquired Fs Christoph Bertschy and Mario Lucia from Minnesota for D Viktor Loov.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled D Neal Pionk from Hartford (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed D Desmond Bergin to a PTO agreement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Announced Fs Alex Krushelnyski and Steven Swavely have been recalled to Lehigh Valley (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Traded G Andrew Dykstra to Colorado for a 2020 second-round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ARMADA FC — Loaned MF Jack Blake to Tampa Bay (USL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">USL — Named Brad Baker vice president of broadcasting, effective Feb. 13.</p><p xmlns="">OTTAWA FURY FC — Signed MF Cristian Portilla and D Kyle Porter.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">METRO ATLANTIC ATHLETIC CONFERENCE_Named Joe Ruggiero director of new media/video.</p><p xmlns="">ALBANY (NY) — Signed football coach Greg Gattuso to a five-year contract extension through the 2022 season.</p><p xmlns="">EASTERN MICHIGAN — Named Ben Needham assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">IOWA — Named Kammy Powell football athletic trainer.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>