<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2aed8c0f-79c1-42dd-8e5b-3101133d854f" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0647</summary><sourceId>719ee8ee-fe79-4cd7-cd7a-bb2ad45dcb2c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8501%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0647</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB PLAYERS ASSOCIATION — Announced the resignation of director of communications Greg Bouris.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agreed to terms with RHP Kevin Gausman on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY RAYS — Agreed to terms with RHP Sergio Romo on a one-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Agreed to terms with LHP Craig Breslow on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO CUBS — Agreed to terms with RHP Yu Darvish on a six-year contract and OF Peter Bourjos on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Agreed to terms with OF Quintin Berry on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Traded 3B Matt Reynolds to Washington for cash.</p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO PADRES — Placed LHP Jose Torres on the restricted list.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON NATIONALS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Brady Dragmire, David Goforth, Edwin Jackson, Jaron Long, Roman Mendez, Chris Smith and Cesar Vargas; LHPs Tim Collins, Ismael Guillon, Bryan Harper and Tommy Milone; Cs Miguel Montero and Jhonatan Solano; INFs Reid Brignac and Chris Dominguez; and OFs Ryan Raburn and Moises Sierra.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">GARY SOUTHSHORE RAILCATS — Released INF Kris Goodman and RHP Drasen Johnson.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Traded LHP Anthony Pacillo to Fargo-Moorhead for a player to be named.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY T-BONES — Signed INF JC Rodriguez. Released OF Chantz Mack.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Signed LHP Bo Hellquist and RHPs Nicco Blank and Ryan Fritze.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed 1B David Washington.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA CHAMPIONS — Released RHP Garrett Cortright.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed 1B/OF Kurtis Kloke.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed OF Marcus Guzman.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Named Greg Cadaret pitching coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE TITANS — Named Matt Edwards assistant special teams coach, Scott Booker and Ryan Crow defensive assistants and Matt Pees quality control coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Re-signed LB Adam Komar to a two-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Agreed to terms with WR Nic Demski and RB Kienan LaFrance on one-year contracts and DB Chandler Fenner to a two-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Recalled D Marcus Pettersson from San Diego (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Reassigned D Andrei Mironov to San Antonio (AHL). Recalled D Duncan Siemens from San Antonio.</p><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS BLUE JACKETS — Loaned D Andre Benoit to Bridgeport (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Recalled F Dylan Sadowy from Toledo (ECHL) to Grand Rapids (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Placed F Trevor Lewis on injured reserve, retroactive to Feb. 9.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Recalled F Oskar Sundqvist from San Antonio (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Bridgeport F Steve Bernier one game and Bakersfield F Mitch Callahan 20 games.</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled F J.C. Beaudin from Colorado (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Signed Fs Jake Trask and Daniel Gentzler from Macon (SPHL).</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Traded the ECHL playing rights to D Adam Comrie to Manchester for G Branden Komm.</p><p xmlns="">UTAH GRIZZLIES — Traded F Todd Skirving to Atlanta for future considerations.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">D.C. UNITED — Traded the rights to M Yamil Asad to Atlanta for general and targeted allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">SEATTLE SOUNDERS — Signed M Alex Roldan and D Jordan McCrary.</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Traded a 2018 international roster spot to Colorado for general allocation money.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Premier Development League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND ROUGH RIDERS — Named Stephen Roche coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">HAMPTON — Named Brian White offensive coordinator and Marcus Dixon defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">OHIO STATE — Named Taver Johnson cornerbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">SUNY OLD WESTBURY — Named Michael Cardino assistant baseball coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>