<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="eb9424c3-a824-44bd-9a1a-f50f9b2a8356" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0600</summary><sourceId>1eeec1c2-bb5d-4425-4259-e7b737dca06e</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z3096%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0600</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">COMMISSIONER'S OFFICE — Suspended Cincinnati RHP Jake Ehret (Louisville-IL) 50 games and Cleveland OF Carlos Ventura (DSL Indians) 72 games for violations of the Minor League Drug Prevention and Treatment Program.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Placed LHP Zach Britton on the 60-day DL.</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Agreed to terms with RHP Edinson Volquez on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO CUBS — Agreed to terms with RHP Shae Simmons on a one-year contract. Placed LHP Drew Smyly on the 60-da DL.</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE BREWERS — Agreed to terms with SS Nick Franklin and LHP Wade Miley on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA PHILLIES — Agreed to terms with RHP Drew Hutchison on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS CARDINALS — Designated RHP Rowan Wick for assignment. Agreed to terms with RHP Bud Norris on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Released C JJ Fernandez.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">NBA G League</hl2><p xmlns="">DELAWARE 87ERS — Acquired G Kyle Randall from the available player pool.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA PANTHERS — Reinstated general manager Marty Hurney.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT LIONS — Named Hank Fraley assistant offensive line coach and Evan Rothstein research and analytics assistant.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Signed DE Craig Roh to a two-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Assigned F Julien Nantel from San Antonio (AHL) to Colorado (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Recalled F Jason Dickinson from Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Recalled F Spencer Watson from Manchester (ECHL) to Ontario (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA WILD — Assigned G Steve Michalek from Iowa (AHL) to Rapid City (ECHL). Recalled G Adam Vay from Rapids City to Iowa.</p><p xmlns="">MONTREAL CANADIENS — Assigned G Zachary Fucale from Laval (AHL) to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Placed F John Quenneville on injured reserve, retroactive to Feb. 10.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Assigned F Vinni Lettieri to Hartford (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND MONSTERS — Returned F Michael Kirkpatrick on loan to Florida (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">ROCKFORD ICEHOGS — Assigned F Alex Wideman to Indy (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Assigned F Brady Shaw to Colorado (ECHL) and F Jake Marchment to Utah (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TUCSON ROADRUNNERS — Assigned F Artur Tyanulin to Fort Wayne (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended Worcester G Eamon McAdam two games.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Signed F Garrett Milan.</p><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI CYCLONES — Signed D Eric Diodati to an amateur tryout agreement.</p><p xmlns="">UTAH GRIZZLIES — Released F Nate Mitton.</p><p xmlns="">WHEELING NAILERS — Signed Fs Bryan Arneson and Ryan Marcuz.</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Signed D Chris Saracino. Added G Chris Habazin as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA UNITED — Traded the discovery rights to M Alejandro Romero Gamarra to the N.Y. Red Bulls for general allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">D.C. UNITED — Signed D Chris Odoi-Atsem to a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CHATTANOOGA — Named Jeremiah Wilson cornerbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">DUKE — Promoted Ben Albert and Matt Guerrieri to co-defensive coordinators. Named Lanier Goethie assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">LA SALLE — Announced the resignation of field hockey coach Michelle Marks Salmi.</p><p xmlns="">MEMPHIS — Named Scott Symons inside linebackers coach.</p><p xmlns="">MICHIGAN STATE — Signed football coach Mark Dantonio to a one-year contract extension through the 2023 season.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>