<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5a486ec0-baee-8407-4552-d2b62601b45e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jonathan M. Alexander</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKC-LOUISVILLE-DUKE:RA — sports (250 words)</title><summary>DURHAM, N.C. — Even with Duke’s best scorer on the bench, Louisville had no real answers on how to stop the Blue Devils.Duke freshman Marvin Bagley III missed his fourth consecutive game with a “mild knee sprain.” And for the fourth time, Duke...</summary><sourceId>f0906dc7-1ec6-aed2-ed26-7c270ff2d650</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7238%knihr%r%BC-BKC-LOUISVILLE-DUKE:RA — sports (250 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">No. 5 Duke cruises past Louisville at home; picks up fourth win without Bagley</h2><byline xmlns="">By Jonathan M. Alexander</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">DURHAM, N.C. — Even with Duke’s best scorer on the bench, Louisville had no real answers on how to stop the Blue Devils.</p><p xmlns="">Duke freshman Marvin Bagley III missed his fourth consecutive game with a “mild knee sprain.” And for the fourth time, Duke won again in convincing fashion at Cameron Indoor Stadium.</p><p xmlns="">Senior guard Grayson Allen knocked down some big shots. He led all scorers with 28 points. He was 10-for-20 for the game as the Blue Devils cruised to a 82-56 win.</p><p xmlns="">After losing two straight games, Duke (23-5, 11-4 ACC) has now won four straight. The Blue Devils currently sit at second in the ACC standings, half a game ahead of UNC, which Duke will play one final time at home in two weeks.</p><p xmlns="">The Blue Devils got out to a fast start early in the first half. With a little more than two minutes left in the first half, Duke led by 21 points. Louisville cut the lead to 17 points at halftime.</p><p xmlns="">Louisville would eventually trim the lead to 13 points, but never got closer than that. Louisville junior Ray Spalding scored 17 points and grabbed 10 rebounds for the Cardinals.</p><p xmlns="">Duke primarily used a zone defense, as it has done in the previous four games. Louisville struggled to hit quality shots and finished shooting 36 percent from the floor.</p><p xmlns="">Freshman forward Wendell Carter Jr. recorded 18 points, 9 rebounds and 6 assists. Freshman guard Gary Trent Jr. had 11 points.</p><p xmlns="">Duke will play Syracuse at home on Saturday.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000008058,t000008056,t000003183,g000065650,g000220400,g000362661,g000066164,g000221059,g000065627</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>