<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="0623a733-895d-425d-9a2b-fe0b101d5658" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jim Salter</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Missouri Governor-Indicted,2nd Ld-Writethru</title><summary>ST. LOUIS (AP) — A St. Louis grand jury has indicted Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens on a felony invasion of privacy charge for allegedly taking a compromising photo of a woman with whom he had an affair in 2015, the city circuit attorney's office...</summary><sourceId>1854901b-3d2c-49b1-9b1a-f6302684399e</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL0782%limit%u%BC-US--Missouri Governor-Indicted,2nd Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Grand jury indicts Missouri governor who admitted affair</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Updates to show Greitens was taken into custody but released, and add comment from spokeswoman for the circuit attorney. Adds byline.</p><byline xmlns="">By JIM SALTER</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS (AP) — A St. Louis grand jury has indicted Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens on a felony invasion of privacy charge for allegedly taking a compromising photo of a woman with whom he had an affair in 2015, the city circuit attorney's office said Thursday.</p><p xmlns="">St. Louis Circuit Attorney Kim Gardner launched an investigation in January after Greitens admitted to an affair with his St. Louis hairdresser that began in March 2015. He was elected governor in November 2016.</p><p xmlns="">Gardner declined comment beyond a brief news release, but spokeswoman Susan Ryan confirmed the indictment stemmed from a photo Greitens allegedly took of the woman.</p><p xmlns="">Greitens was taken into custody in St. Louis and released on his own recognizance, Ryan said.</p><p xmlns="">The woman told her husband, who was secretly taping the conversation, that Greitens took the compromising photo of her at his home and threatened to use it as blackmail if she spoke about the affair. A news release from Gardner says it is a felony if a person transmits an image "in a manner that allows access to that image via a computer."</p><p xmlns="">Messages seeking comment from Greitens and his attorney were not immediately returned.</p><p xmlns="">Greitens has repeatedly denied blackmailing the woman, but has repeatedly refused to answer questions about whether he took a photo.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>