<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e22c2879-1c69-488e-bba3-0b13fc661d35" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TN--Tennessee Governor-Black,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Republican U.S. Rep. Diane Black on Thursday defended her efforts to extend an emissions control loophole that benefits a trucking company associated with $225,000 in donations to her campaign for governor.The New York...</summary><sourceId>375b00cb-ba73-4b62-b62a-8fcd577a2861</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:e2675%tntn-%r%BC-TN--Tennessee Governor-Black,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Black defends campaign checks, trucking emissions loophole</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Adds detail, background, quotes.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Republican U.S. Rep. Diane Black on Thursday defended her efforts to extend an emissions control loophole that benefits a trucking company associated with $225,000 in donations to her campaign for governor.</p><p xmlns="">The New York Times reported this week that Black asked U.S. Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt to continue the emissions exemptions for rebuilt diesel engines, which trucks from Byrdstown-based Fitzgerald Glider Kits use. "Glider kits" include a truck chassis and cab assembly without a new engine.</p><p xmlns="">According to the Times, Black approached Pruitt with a Tennessee Technological University study funded by Fitzgerald that downplays the trucks' pollution problems. Fitzgerald also promised to build the university a new research center on land owned by the company, the report says.</p><p xmlns="">Black's campaign spokesman Chris Hartline said the congresswoman fights to support the few companies trying to keep rural Tennessee manufacturing jobs. Hartline says Black has fought a President Barack Obama-era diesel emissions rule since 2014, and she believes "sensible regulators can promote safety and American manufacturing at the same time."</p><p xmlns="">"Diane does her best to help all constituents that walk through her door, regardless of their politics — that's her job," Hartline said in a statement.</p><p xmlns="">Black also sponsored a bill in 2015 that sought to block the Obama administration's push to close the loophole, but the effort failed.</p><p xmlns="">Black received the $225,000 from entities, executives and relatives associated with Fitzgerald in the six weeks before Pruitt announced he would allow the exemption. The donations represent about 13 percent of more than $1.7 million Black raised from donors from August, when she entered the race, through mid-January.</p><p xmlns="">Tennessee Democratic Party chairwoman Mary Mancini called Black's behavior "pay to play."</p><p xmlns="">"Every Tennessean needs to know the air they breathe is safe and clean," Mancini said in a statement. "It is extremely disturbing that Rep. Black would put families at higher risk of lung cancer and asthma in exchange for campaign contributions."</p><p xmlns="">Tommy Fitzgerald, one of the company's owners, told The Times that it was good public policy, not special favors, that Black and Pruitt displayed.</p><p xmlns="">Black is one of four leading Republicans in the governor's race.</p><p xmlns="">Businessman and former state economic development chief Randy Boyd's campaign received $16,000 from a Fitzgerald family member and an affiliate in October and January, well after he left his state job last February. House Speaker Beth Harwell and businessman Bill Lee are also running.</p><p xmlns="">The main Democrats running are former Nashville Mayor Karl Dean and House Minority Leader Craig Fitzhugh.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>