<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c68fe3fa-2b83-4bb4-8592-fed9f930921d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Not Real News-Dog Meat</title><summary>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A Los Angeles restaurant doesn't have permission to kill as many as three dogs a day and serve the meat to customers, despite claims in a widely shared false story this week. Health officials say the restaurant doesn't exist.A...</summary><sourceId>4684aa97-d8ab-44f8-4f89-d4ee50a878ff</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:k8079%caca-%r%BC-Not Real News-Dog Meat;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Officials: No dog meat on the menu at Los Angeles restaurant</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES (AP) — A Los Angeles restaurant doesn't have permission to kill as many as three dogs a day and serve the meat to customers, despite claims in a widely shared false story this week. Health officials say the restaurant doesn't exist.</p><p xmlns="">A post that has appeared online in various forms since at least 2014 surfaced again recently on the site quotes-news. The Los Angeles County Health Department said it has no record of any restaurant named Puchow de Manila Eatery and Fine Dining. Even if there were such a place, the department said the sale of dog meat for human consumption is illegal in California.</p><p xmlns="">The false story quotes World Animal Protection as being "shocked" about the restaurant but a spokeswoman for that group said it was never asked to comment. A photo linked to the story is from a 2014 New York Times story about a dog meat festival in China.</p><p xmlns="">____</p><p xmlns="">This is part of The Associated Press' ongoing effort to fact-check misinformation that is shared widely online, including work with Facebook to identify and reduce the circulation of false stories on the platform.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>