<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8f827081-236f-821e-27ca-d8b314d0e809" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Mark Zeigler</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-OLY-FIG-PAIRS-KNIERIMS:SD — sports, itop (550 words)</title><summary>GANGNEUNG, South Korea — Chris Knierim and wife Alexa ended their Olympic figure skating odyssey with a thud. It’s hard to jump with a heavy heart.The U.S. pairs team was in the warm-up room before the free program at Gangneung Ice Arena and...</summary><sourceId>b5cb9136-7f1c-a82e-82e8-8631a6cfc6dd</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7365%kniht%r%BC-OLY-FIG-PAIRS-KNIERIMS:SD — sports, itop (550 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Knierims finish Olympics with a heavy heart</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Mark Zeigler</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">GANGNEUNG, South Korea — Chris Knierim and wife Alexa ended their Olympic figure skating odyssey with a thud. It’s hard to jump with a heavy heart.</p><p xmlns="">The U.S. pairs team was in the warm-up room before the free program at Gangneung Ice Arena and glanced at the television in the corner. CNN happened to be on, reporting on the school shooting in Florida that killed 17.</p><p xmlns="">Moments later, they were on Olympic ice.</p><p xmlns="">They executed their signature move, a quad twist, but Chris fell on both side-by-side jumps and Alexa bobbled a landing on a throw triple Salchow. Their score of 120.27, six below their season best, dropped them from 14th after the short program to 15th overall.</p><p xmlns="">Germany’s Aljona Savchenko and Bruno Massot won the gold in one of the closest pairs competitions in Olympic history, their 235.90 points just .43 ahead of China’s Sui Wenjing and Han Cong. Canada’s Meagan Duhamel and Eric Radford were third, and Russia’s Evgenia Tarasova and Vladimir Morozov fourth.</p><p xmlns="">“I kind of put pressure on myself today,” a tearful Alexa said, “because I wanted to honor those who were lost and skate really well for them and have somewhat of a happy moment for our country. Unfortunately, we had too many mistakes today and it was one of our lowest scores. I’m maybe being too tough on myself, but I wanted to lift the spirits of those who are probably mourning right now.</p><p xmlns="">“I told Chris today that the world is so much bigger than us … Even though we’re here in Pyeongchang, our hearts are with them. We may be living in a different world over here with the Olympic hype, but we’re hurting for them.”</p><p xmlns="">It’s been an emotional but fulfilling week for the Knierims, whose primary job as the only U.S. pairs in Korea was in the team competition. Their highlight came in the short program of the three-day event, when they skated next after gold-medal favorite Nathan Chen had bombed but propped up U.S. medal hopes with an inspired performance.</p><p xmlns="">Two days later, they had a bronze medal around their necks.</p><p xmlns="">As the only U.S. pairs team, they skated both short and free programs in the team event (the men’s and ladies rotated athletes to save legs) and the fatigue seemed to catch up with them in the regular pairs competition. They weren’t expected to contend for a medal, but they also had finished ninth, seventh, ninth and 10th in four trips to the World Championships.</p><p xmlns="">But at least they executed a clean quad twist, where Alexa completes four horizontal revolutions high above the ice before Chris catches her. They returned it to their program last month after Alexa missed most of last season with an intestinal disorder that required three abdominal surgeries, and the difficult element came to symbolize the completion of her recovery.</p><p xmlns="">They bobbled it at the U.S. Championships last month in San Jose, and U.S. coaches asked them to play it safe in the team free program and downgrade it to a triple twist. This, then, was a small measure of redemption.</p><p xmlns="">“It felt great,” Chris said. “It was the highlight of our program, unfortunately. But it was nice we got it out on Olympic ice.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000136672,t000003385,t000003183</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>