<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ccf8ae87-8e7e-40c0-96d5-f4b98aee4f8a" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0516</summary><sourceId>ac19cfcb-a257-4783-7839-a5c8b85b498c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2010%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0516</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Friday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Agreed to terms with RHP Jake Petricka on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA PHILLIES — Agreed to terms with 2B Ryan Flaherty and OF Collin Cowgill on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Agreed to terms with OF Daniel Nava on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Waived G/F Marco Belinelli.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BULLS — Waived G/F Tony Allen.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's NBA</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK LIBERTY — Re-signed G Bria Hartley and C Kia Vaughn.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">DETROIT LIONS — Signed general manager Bob Quinn to a contract extension. Named Bo Davis defensive line coach.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Named John DeFilippo offensive coordinator.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Signed LB J.C.Sherritt to a contract extension through the 2019 season.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Agreed to terms with WR Adarius Bowman on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Assigned G Mason McDonald from Stockton (AHL) to Kansas City (ECHL) and G Tyler Parsons from Kansas City to Stockton.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Assigned Fs Marcus Kruger and Josh Jooris to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Placed D Jan Rutta on injured reserve, retroactive to Tuesday. Recalled D Carl Dahlstrom from Rockford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA WILD — Recalled Fs Pavel Jenys and Chase Lang from Rapid City (ECHL) to Iowa (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Traded F Joe Whitney and RW Adam Chapie to Washington for F John Albert and D Hubert Labrie. Assigned D Brendan Smith to Hartford (AHL). Recalled D John Gilmour from Hartford. Reassigned D Sergey Zborovskiy from Greenville (ECHL) to Hartford.</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Recalled D Chris Butler from San Antonio (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND MONSTERS — Returned RW Sam Kurker on loan to Manchester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">GRAND RAPIDS GRIFFINS — Assigned D Kevin Tansey to Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LEHIGH VALLEY PHANTOMS — Recalled D James De Haas from Reading (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">ROCKFORD ICEHOGS — Assigned G Matt Tomkins to Indy (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SYRACUSE CRUNCH — Assigned F Shane Conacher to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MARLIES — Assigned D Jeff King to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">TUCSON ROADRUNNERS — Assigned D Ryan Culkin to Fort Wayne (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ECHL — Suspended D Kevin Gibson one game.</p><p xmlns="">ADIRONDACK THUNDER — Loaned D Desmond Bergin to Hartford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">FLORIDA EVERBLADES — Loaned F Dave Dziurzynski to Utica (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Claimed G Greg Dodds off waivers from Indy.</p><p xmlns="">KALAMAZOO WINGS — Loaned F Justin Taylor to Utica (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">TULSA OILERS — Added G Jordan Neamonitis as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Acquired F Samuel Armenteros on loan from Benevento Calcio (Serie A-Italy).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">NCAA — Granted a sixth season of eligibility to Iowa State QB Kyle Kempt.</p><p xmlns="">ILLINOIS — Named Austin Clark defensive line coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>