<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="e849f283-ece7-4aa2-8079-7bfc7749be0c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Manuel Gamiz Jr.</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-FLA-SCHOOLSHOOTING-PA-THREAT:AA — national (200 words)</title><summary>ALLENTOWN, Pa. — Like many schools across the country likely did on Thursday, a Dieruff High School class in Allentown, Pa., discussed the mass shooting in Florida that claimed the lives of 17 high school students and staff.Teacher Reina Garcia...</summary><sourceId>0c4dc78f-ccfd-ee7d-e7dc-c810d08e7c63</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K5805%knihw%r%BC-FLA-SCHOOLSHOOTING-PA-THREAT:AA — national (200 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">During discussion on Florida mass shooting, Pennsylvania student threatens to kill classmates, police say</h2><byline xmlns="">By Manuel Gamiz Jr.</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">ALLENTOWN, Pa. — Like many schools across the country likely did on Thursday, a Dieruff High School class in Allentown, Pa., discussed the mass shooting in Florida that claimed the lives of 17 high school students and staff.</p><p xmlns="">Teacher Reina Garcia asked her Dieruff students how the shooting made them feel, and they took turns expressing their emotions.</p><p xmlns="">When it came time for student Emiliano T. Gil to speak, his answer frightened his classmates and teacher, Allentown police said.</p><p xmlns="">Gil, 19, of Allentown threatened that “he was going to kill all the people in the school and was going to start with the class he was in,” Allentown Detective Benjamin Iobst wrote in a criminal complaint.</p><p xmlns="">Gil’s words caused fear and alarm, and he was reported to school administrators and the school resource officer, according to the complaint. The resource officer placed Gil in investigative detention to preserve the safety of the school, the complaint says.</p><p xmlns="">Further investigation led to charges of terroristic threats, a first-degree misdemeanor, and disorderly conduct, a third-degree misdemeanor.</p><p xmlns="">Gil was arraigned by District Judge Michael D’Amore and released on $10,000 unsecured bail.</p><p xmlns="">Allentown Superintendent Thomas Parker said Gil has been suspended indefinitely. Pending a review, the district and school board will decide whether to expel him.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">(Reporter Jacqueline Palochko contributed to this story.)</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Morning Call (Allentown, Pa.) at www.mcall.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000027855,t000394143,g000065577,g000362661,g000066164,g000065564</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>