<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6d926106-af94-414d-9de3-0b1644fdef35" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0494</summary><sourceId>d1a78b81-475a-4759-759b-289898a020a3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5391%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0494</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 12</hl2><p xmlns="">1937 — Cleveland is granted an NFL franchise. The Rams play in Cleveland for nine years before moving to Los Angeles. After the 1994 season, the Rams move to St. Louis.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Boston's Bill Russell scores 18 points and grabs 41 rebounds to lead the Celtics to a 119-101 victory over the Syracuse Nationals.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Jean-Claude Killy of France wins the men's giant slalom in the Winter Olympics at Grenoble, his second gold medal en route to the Alpine triple crown.</p><p xmlns="">1972 — The Soviet Union ice hockey team wins the gold medal with a 5-2 victory over Czechoslovakia at the Winter Olympics. The United States is awarded the silver because it had beaten and tied Czechoslovakia.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Loy Allen Jr. becomes the first Winston Cup rookie to win a pole in the Daytona 500. Allen is .031 seconds quicker than six-time NASCAR Winston Cup champion Dale Earnhardt.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Morocco's Hicham el Guerrouj breaks indoor track's oldest record, winning the mile in 3 minutes, 48.45 at the Flanders meet held in Ghent, Belgium. Ireland's Eamonn Coghlan ran 3:49.78 in 1983 in New York.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Allen Iverson scores 60 points, a career high, to lead the Philadelphia 76ers to a 112-99 victory over the Orlando Magic.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Duke, saddled by its first four-game losing skid in 11 years, falls out of The Associated Press men's poll for the first time since the end of the 1995-96 season. The Blue Devils had been in the media poll for 200 straight weeks — the second longest streak behind UCLA's record 221 weeks.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — American Hannah Kearney wins her 15th straight World Cup moguls event at the World Cup event in Beida Lake, China. Kearney breaks downhill great Ingemar Stenmark's all-discipline record for consecutive FIS World Cup victories. Stenmark won 14 straight giant slaloms in 1978-80. Kearney's streak began in Lake Placid, N.Y., on Jan. 22, 2011.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — LeBron James becomes the first player in NBA history to score 30 points and shoot at least 60 percent in six straight games as the Miami Heat hold off the Portland Trail Blazers 117-104. James scores 30 points on 11 for 15 shooting.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Tina Maze of Slovenia and Dominique Gisin of Switzerland tie for gold in the Olympic women's downhill. Both speed down the Rosa Khutor course in 1:41.57 seconds for the first gold-medal tie in Olympic alpine skiing history.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>