<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="18c3dbca-f4bc-4dd9-a017-9eff9e03ad0e" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Bill Cosby</title><summary>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Bill Cosby's defense team says it wrongly accused prosecutors of hiding evidence from his suburban Philadelphia criminal sexual-assault case.Cosby's lawyers acknowledged in a court filing Monday they made the headline-grabbing...</summary><sourceId>5f1169df-5a29-476b-76bb-bae00d3ae7b4</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL6018%limit%r%BC-US--Bill Cosby;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Cosby's lawyers: We were wrong about hidden-evidence claim</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Will be updated.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Bill Cosby's defense team says it wrongly accused prosecutors of hiding evidence from his suburban Philadelphia criminal sexual-assault case.</p><p xmlns="">Cosby's lawyers acknowledged in a court filing Monday they made the headline-grabbing claim without realizing prosecutors had told Cosby's former lawyer about interviewing a woman who cast doubt on his accuser.</p><p xmlns="">The former lawyer says he knew about prosecutors last year interviewing a woman who said accuser Andrea Constand told her she wasn't sexually assaulted but could make up allegations to get money.</p><p xmlns="">Prosecutors have blasted the allegations of hiding evidence as "outrageous and reckless." They say Cosby's lawyers seemed more interested in shifting the narrative than in uncovering the truth.</p><p xmlns="">Constand told jurors Cosby gave her pills and molested her, which Cosby denies.</p><p xmlns="">Cosby's first trial ended in a hung jury last June. A retrial is scheduled for April.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>