<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="1c2d952b-cb68-4524-95e2-04b20d9039dd" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0870</summary><sourceId>ca30b754-da7c-45bc-5bcb-e87c33d1920d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7315%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0870</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BOSTON RED SOX — Promoted Mike Roose to athletic performance coordinator/strength and conditioning coach, Walter Miranda to Latin American pitching and rehabilitation coordinator, Devin Pearson assistant/amateur scouting, Greg Rybarczyk senior analyst/baseball research and development and Dan Madsen, Jim Robinson, Quincy Boyd and Fred Peterson national scouting supervisors. Named Adan Severino and Daniel Abroms mental skills coordinators, Kevin Avilla minor league physical therapist, Humberto Sanchez DSL pitching coach and RJ Warner minor league clubhouse assistant, Reed Gragnani Mid-Atlantic area scout, Carl Moesche Northwest area scout, J.J. Altobelli part-time Southern California scout, Mike Ganley director/baseball systems, Bill Letson data architect/baseball systems, Dan Meyer analyst/baseball research and development, Aneko Knowles Bahamas scout and Alfredo Castellon Colombia scout.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Named Chip Bowers president of business operations.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">GARY SOUTHSHORE RAILCATS — Signed RHP Daniel Minor.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed LHP Josh Blanco and INF Jake Wark.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG GOLDEYES — Signed LHP Mitch Lambson and RHP Victor Capellan.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Traded OF Johnny Bladel to Southern Maryland (Atlantic) for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">SUSSEX COUNTY MINERS — Signed C Brian Mayer.</p><p xmlns="">TROIS-RIVIERES AIGLES — Signed INFs Taylor Oldham and Taylor Brennan.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">EVANSVILLE OTTERS — Signed RHP Sean Johnson.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Traded OF Connor Oliver to River City for a player to be named.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Signed LHP Seth Brenner and OF Jason Heinrich.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TIMBERWOLVES — Recalled C Justin Patton from Iowa (NBAGL).</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA 76ERS — Signed G Marco Belinelli.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA CARDINALS — Signed CB Lou Young to a one-year contract and general manager Steve Keim to a contract extension through 2022.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA VIKINGS — Signed G Josh Andrews.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG BLUE BOMBERS — Re-signed DB Kevin Fogg to a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Placed F Troy Brouwer on injured reserve, retroactive to Thursday. Recalled G Jon Gillies from Stockton (AHL) and G Mason McDonald from Kansas City (ECHL) to Stockton.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Recalled F Dylan Sadowy from Toledo (ECHL) to Grand Rapids (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Placed G Cory Schneider on injured reserve, retroactive to Jan. 23. Recalled F Nick Lappin from Binghamton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled D Ryan Sproul from Hartford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">OTTAWA SENATORS — Assigned G Chris Driedger from Belleville (AHL) to Brampton (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended Belleville F Mike Blunden two games.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND MONSTERS — Recalled D Scott Savage from Jacksonville (ECHL) and G Ivan Kulbakov from Quad City (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">LEHIGH VALLEY PHANTOMS — Assigned Fs Steve Swavely and Alex Krushelnyski to Reading (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE ADMIRALS — Loaned D Rick Pinkston to Atlanta (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled D Nolan DeJong from Colorado (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Agreed to terms with D Drew Baker.</p><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Released G Carmine Guerriero. Signed G Daniel Spence.</p><p xmlns="">FLORIDA EVERBLADES — Released F Nolan LaPorte. Loaned F Michael Kirkpatrick to Cleveland (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Claimed G Greg Dodds off waivers from Indy. Loaned F Caleb Herbert to San Jose (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">IDAHO STEELHEADS — Loaned F Henrik Samuelsson to Rockford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ICEMEN — Loaned G Austin Lotz to Manitoba (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Added G Nick Niedert as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">FC DALLAS — Signed M Santiago Mosquera from Millonarios FC (Primera A-Colombia).</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Waived D Rennico Clarke.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National Women's Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON SPIRIT — Named Jack Stefanowski goalkeeper coach.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA FURY — Signed G David Monsalve.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">SOUTHEASTERN CONFERENCE — Fined South Carolina men's basketball coach Frank Martin $25,000 for comments about an official that issued him a technical foul.</p><p xmlns="">ALBANY (NY) — Named Joe Davis passing game coordinator/quarterbacks coach and Jarred Holley safeties coach.</p><p xmlns="">HAMPTON — Named Hank Hughes defensive coordinator and Ataveus Cash quarterbacks coach and passing game coordinator.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA STATE — Agreed to terms with softball coach Lori Meyer on a five-year contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">MISSISSIPPI — Announced men's basketball coach Andy Kennedy will step down at the end of the season.</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE STATE — Announced the resignation of baseball coach Jason Hawkins.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTHERN CAL — Signed offensive coordinator Tee Martin and defensive coordinator Clancy Pendergast to contract extensions.</p><p xmlns="">WILLIAM PENN — Announced it will add men's and women's lacrosse and men's volleyball programs, to begin play in the 2019-20 academic year.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>