<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="9b4f59aa-6b71-4097-bfea-16a1b1a64bc7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-ML--Iran,CORRECTIVE</title><summary>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — In a story Feb. 4 about the Iran nuclear deal, The Associated Press reported erroneously that President Donald Trump re-certified the agreement in January. Trump did not re-certify the deal, but extended sanctions waivers, and...</summary><sourceId>d28f7103-98da-4171-171a-01177a5bfab0</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL5883%limit%r%BC-ML--Iran,CORRECTIVE;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Correction: Iran  story</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Editors who used BC-ML--Iran, sent Feb. 4 and datelined in Tehran, Iran, are asked to use the following story.</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — In a story Feb. 4 about the Iran nuclear deal, The Associated Press reported erroneously that President Donald Trump re-certified the agreement in January. Trump did not re-certify the deal, but extended sanctions waivers, and said he would not do so again the next time they come up for renewal, in May, unless his concerns are addressed.</p><p xmlns="">A corrected version of the story is below:</p><p xmlns="">Iran says Trump's hostility to nuclear deal scares investors</p><p xmlns="">Iran says President Donald Trump's hostility to the 2015 nuclear deal is dampening foreign investment in the energy sector despite the lifting of sanctions</p><p xmlns="">TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran says President Donald Trump's hostility to the 2015 nuclear deal is dampening foreign investment in the energy sector despite the lifting of sanctions.</p><p xmlns="">Oil Minister Bijan Zanganeh told reporters on Sunday that the uncertainty over the future of the agreement, which Trump has repeatedly threatened to scrap, is scaring off potential investors.</p><p xmlns="">Trump extended sanctions waivers in January but said he would not do so again when they come up for renewal in May unless his concerns are addressed.</p><p xmlns="">Iran hopes to attract more than $150 billion to rebuild its energy industry after years of sanctions. Last year it signed a $5 billion gas deal with France's Total SA and a Chinese oil company to develop a massive offshore gas field.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>