<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="b7dcbda7-1d75-4cd6-af4c-36843302bb49" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0581</summary><sourceId>e158aaeb-8328-49dd-9dd9-e19c270e1f86</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z7927%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0581</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 14</hl2><p xmlns="">1936 — Maribel Vinson wins her eighth U.S. figure skating singles championship and Robin Lee wins his second consecutive men's title.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Sugar Ray Robinson captures the middleweight title with a technical knockout in the 13th round over Jake LaMotta in Chicago.</p><p xmlns="">1953 — Bill Chambers of William &amp; Mary grabs 51 rebounds in a 105-84 victory over Virginia.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Philadelphia's Wilt Chamberlain scores 41 points in a 149-123 win over Detroit to become the NBA's all-time scoring leader, passing Bob Pettit (20,880 points).</p><p xmlns="">1975 — Julius Erving of the New York Nets scores 63 points in a 176-166 quadruple overtime loss to the San Diego Conquistadors. Erving sets an ABA record by shooting 25-for-46 from the field and the 342 points are an ABA record.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Philadelphia's Al Hill sets a record for most points in an NHL debut with five points — two goals and three assists — in a 6-4 victory over the St. Louis Blues.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Bobby Allison outduels 26-year-old son Davey to win the Daytona 500 and becomes the first 50-year-old to win NASCAR's premier event.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Bonnie Blair becomes the first American woman in 40 years to win two gold medals in the Winter Olympics when she takes the 1,000-meter speed skating event. Toni Nieminen, 16, becomes the youngest male Winter Olympic champion ever, leading Finland to the team ski jumping title. He's a day younger than American bobsledder Bill Fiske was in 1928.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Mississippi wins on Kentucky's homecourt for the first time since 1927 with a 73-64 victory. It's the Rebels' first win in 20 games in Rupp Arena and the second in 45 games at Kentucky.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Anaheim's Sergei Fedorov is the first Russian-born player to reach 1,000 points, assisting on Keith Carney's goal in the second period of the Ducks' 2-1 win over Vancouver.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Savannah State becomes the second NCAA Division I school in a half-century to go through an entire season without a win, losing to Florida A&amp;M 49-44 to finish 0-28.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — In Vancouver, British Columbia, an American breaks through the Nordic combined barrier, winning the first Olympic medal in the sport dominated since its inception by the Europeans. Jason Lamy Chappuis of France overtakes American Johnny Spillane on the final straightaway for the gold medal.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The East edges the West 141-139 in the NBA All-Star Game before the largest crowd to watch a basketball game — 108,713 at Cowboys Stadium. Dwyane Wade scores 28 points and takes MVP honors before Dallas-born Chris Bosh makes the winning free throws with 5.0 seconds left.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The America's Cup again belongs to America. Larry Ellison's space-age trimaran easily speeds ahead of two-time defending champion Alinghi of Switzerland to complete a two-race sweep in yachting's premier event.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Mikaela Shiffrin becomes the third woman to win back-to-back slalom titles at the world championships. She finishes in a combined time of 1:38.48, edging Frida Hansdotter of Sweden by 0.34 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — The first NBA All-Star Game outside the U.S. is the highest scoring. Kobe Bryant makes his All-Star farewell and the West wins 196-173 in Toronto. Russell Westbrook scores 31 points in his second straight All-Star MVP performance. Paul George finishes with 41 for the East.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>