<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="c5578650-540f-44b5-97f4-57a7b80531ae" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Missouri Governor-Indicted-The Latest</title><summary>ST. LOUIS (AP) — The Latest on a grand jury indictment of Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens (all times local):5 p.m.Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens' attorney says a felony invasion of privacy charge against the Republican is "baseless and unfounded."Lawyer...</summary><sourceId>d78cce69-ce8f-4577-5778-2c3d7b5f52ed</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:APL0797%limit%u%BC-US--Missouri Governor-Indicted-The Latest;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">The Latest: Greitens' lawyer says felony charge "baseless"</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS (AP) — The Latest on a grand jury indictment of Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens (all times local):</p><p xmlns="">5 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens' attorney says a felony invasion of privacy charge against the Republican is "baseless and unfounded."</p><p xmlns="">Lawyer Edward Dowd on Thursday said the governor is "absolutely innocent" in response to St. Louis Circuit Attorney Kim Gardner's announcement of a grand jury indictment against Greitens related to his affair with a woman in 2015.</p><p xmlns="">Dowd in a statement said Greitens will file a motion to dismiss the charges.</p><p xmlns="">Gardner launched an investigation in January after Greitens admitted to the affair with his St. Louis hairdresser that began in March 2015. He was elected governor in November 2016.</p><p xmlns="">The woman told her husband, who was secretly taping the conversation, that Greitens took a compromising photo of her at his home and threatened to use it as blackmail if she spoke about the affair.</p><p xmlns="">A news release from Gardner says it is a felony if a person transmits an image "in a manner that allows access to that image via a computer."</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">4:20 p.m.</p><p xmlns="">A St. Louis grand jury has indicted Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens on a felony invasion of privacy charge related to the Republican's affair with a woman in 2015.</p><p xmlns="">St. Louis Circuit Attorney Kim Gardner announced the indictment Thursday. She launched an investigation in January after Greitens admitted to an affair with his St. Louis hairdresser that began in March 2015. He was elected governor in November 2016.</p><p xmlns="">The woman told her husband, who was secretly taping the conversation, that Greitens took a compromising photo of her at his home and threatened to use it as blackmail if she spoke about the affair. A news release from Gardner says it is a felony if a person transmits an image "in a manner that allows access to that image via a computer."</p><p xmlns="">Messages seeking comment from Greitens and his attorney were not immediately returned.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>