<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6c7d14d7-8349-851e-edd2-b6eb264a0fa7" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Chip Alexander</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKC-UNC-NCSTATE:RA — sports (550 words)</title><summary>RALEIGH, N.C. — N.C. State coach Kevin Keatts had Wolfpack fans roaring Saturday, taking the court at PNC Arena with a bright red blazer.There’s never been any doubt North Carolina is the Pack’s biggest rival, and every game against the Tar Heels...</summary><sourceId>33c0bb83-cce5-8d1f-d1fe-7a9f6eb3d782</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K6748%knihr%r%BC-BKC-UNC-NCSTATE:RA — sports (550 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Maye powers North Carolina past NC State, 96-89</h2><byline xmlns="">By Chip Alexander</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">RALEIGH, N.C. — N.C. State coach Kevin Keatts had Wolfpack fans roaring Saturday, taking the court at PNC Arena with a bright red blazer.</p><p xmlns="">There’s never been any doubt North Carolina is the Pack’s biggest rival, and every game against the Tar Heels is a big game.</p><p xmlns="">And the two teams played it that way, trading baskets, trading runs, before No. 21 North Carolina emerged with a 96-89 victory.</p><p xmlns="">UNC junior forward Luke Maye was all but unstoppable in the second half, scoring 27 of his 33 points. Jumpers, put-backs, drives, 3-pointers … Maye did it all while finishing with 17 rebounds.</p><p xmlns="">If there was any leftover fatigue from UNC’s emotional 82-78 win over Duke on Thursday, it didn’t show. Not for Maye or the Heels (19-7, 8-5 ACC).</p><p xmlns="">The Tar Heels’ near-flawless offensive efficiency in the second half and work on the offensive boards was more than N.C. State (16-9, 6-6) could overcome. N.C. State had a 19-0 run in the first half and led by two points at the break, but the Pack could not handle the Tar Heels defensively in the second half.</p><p xmlns="">Every time the Pack made it a one-possession game, Maye would hit a shot, or Joel Berry II a drive, or Theo Pinson would score.</p><p xmlns="">A three-point play by the Pack senior forward Abdul-Malik Abu with 1:34 left in regulation — Abu with a big dunk — pulled N.C. State within 85-83 and the place was loud. But UNC’s Kenny Williams then nailed a 3-pointer from the key at 1:11 and that was that.</p><p xmlns="">Junior guard Torin Dorn had 22 points and graduate guard Allerik Freeman scored 17 for the Wolfpack, which has dropped its last two games after a 10-point loss earlier in the week at Virginia Tech.</p><p xmlns="">The Pack was looking for its first sweep of the Tar Heels since the 2002-2003 season after beating UNC in a 95-91 overtime thriller on Jan. 27 in Chapel Hill. Adding a little extra motivation was Berry, a senior guard, saying Duke was the Tar Heels’ only rival.</p><p xmlns="">“N.C. State, I just don’t consider that as being a rival,” Berry said. “We just don’t like them.”</p><p xmlns="">The first half was filled with ebbs and flows, ending with the Pack ahead 37-35.</p><p xmlns="">The Tar Heels had a 12-2 run to take a 28-18 lead midway through the half, beginning it with a Berry 3-pointer and capping it with a Brandon Robinson 3.</p><p xmlns="">Keatts called a timeout and his message was heard. Freshman forward Braxton Beverly quickly hit a 3-pointer and the Pack was off on its 19-0 surge fueled by seven straight points by Dorn.</p><p xmlns="">When sophomore center Omer Yurtseven hit a short hook, the Wolfpack led 37-28 and the crowd was really howling. But there was no timeout from UNC coach Roy Williams.</p><p xmlns="">A put-back by Maye ended the UNC drought as the Tar Heels reeled off seven straight points and the Pack, with poor shot selection, went scoreless the last 3:45 of the half.</p><p xmlns="">Yurtseven, who’s 7-0 and 245 pounds, looked hopeless defensively against Maye early in the second half as the Heels’ 6-8, 240-pound junior scored on three straight possessions, then added a 3-pointer. After Maye had scored 11 points in the first 3:33 of the second half, Keatts was forced to pull Yurtseven from the game.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002776,t000049144,t000142162,t000002786,t000161539,g000362661,g000065598,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>