<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="36aa88e3-785e-4652-b8aa-db6b1cf294a4" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0490</summary><sourceId>4c58c447-998b-41e4-1e4a-e656016d4f8d</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0265%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0490</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Suspended free agent minor league RHP Landon Hughes 68 games and Boston C Jacob Romanski (Pawtucket-IL) 100 games, both without pay, for their violations of the Minor League Drug Prevention and Treatment Program.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Named Adam Esselman coordinator of baseball information.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Named Dave Duncan pitching consultant. Agreed to terms with LHP Xavier Cedeno, INF Jake Elmore and RHPs Jeanmar Gomez and Bruce Rondon on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with RHP Stephen Fife on a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">MIAMI MARLINS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Tyler Cloyd, Jumbo Diaz, Javy Guerra, Drew Rucinski, Jacob Turner, and Alex Wimmers; LHP Mike Kickham; C Bryan Holaday; INFs Cristhian Adames, Johnny Giavotella, Yadiel Rivera, and Jonathan Rodriguez, and OFs Rafael Ortega, JB Shuck, and Scott Van Slyke on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Renewed their player development contract with Columbia (SAL) through the 2020 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed LHP Andrew Barbosa.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">JOLIET SLAMMERS — Signed RHP Skylar Janisse.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed RHP Jensen Kirch and RHP Billy Roth.</p><p xmlns="">TRAVERSE CITY BEACH BUMS — Signed RHP Adam Cornwell and OF Donald Glover, Jr.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Acquired F Okaro White from Miami for F Luke Babbitt and then waived White.</p><p xmlns="">BOSTON CELTICS — Signed C Greg Monroe.</p><p xmlns="">BROOKLYN NETS — Acquired F Dante Cunningham from New Orleans for G Rashad Vaughn.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BULLS — Acquired C Willie Reed and the right to swap 2022 second-round draft picks from Detroit for G Jameer Nelson and then waived Reed. Acquired F Noah Vonleh and cash considerations from Portland for the draft rights to C Milovan Rakovic.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND CAVALIERS — Acquired G Jordan Clarkson and F Larry Nance Jr. from the Los Angeles Lakers for G Isaiah Thomas, F Channing Frye and a 2018 protected first-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">MIAMI HEAT — Acquired G Dwyane Wade from Cleveland for a protected 2024 second-round draft pick. Waived C AJ Hammons.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WIZARDS — Traded G-F Sheldon Mac and cash considerations to Atlanta for a protected 2019 second round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Women's National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA DREAM — Signed F Angel McCoughtry to a multiyear contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Placed Fs Marcus Kruger and Josh Jooris on waivers.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Recalled F Jimmy Hayes from his conditioning loan to Binghamton (AHL). Acquired Fs Christoph Bertschy and Mario Lucia from Minnesota for D Viktor Loov.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Recalled D Neal Pionk from Hartford (AHL). Waived D Brendan Smith.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Recalled F Matt Gaudreau from Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">GRAND RAPIDS GRIFFINS — Assigned D Kevin Tansey to Toledo (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed D Desmond Bergin to a PTO agreement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Announced Fs Alex Krushelnyski and Steven Swavely have been recalled to Lehigh Valley (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Traded G Andrew Dykstra to Colorado for a 2020 second-round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">JACKSONVILLE ARMADA FC — Loaned MF Jack Blake to Tampa Bay (USL). Signed F Conor Doyle and MF Javier Monsalvez.</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">USL — Named Brad Baker vice president of broadcasting, effective Feb. 13.</p><p xmlns="">OTTAWA FURY FC — Signed MF Cristian Portilla and D Kyle Porter.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">METRO ATLANTIC ATHLETIC CONFERENCE_Named Joe Ruggiero director of new media/video.</p><p xmlns="">ALBANY (NY) — Signed football coach Greg Gattuso to a five-year contract extension through the 2022 season.</p><p xmlns="">EASTERN MICHIGAN — Named Ben Needham assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">IOWA — Named Kammy Powell football athletic trainer.</p><p xmlns="">NEW MEXICO — Suspended football coach Bob Davie for 30 days without pay, following multiple investigations that examined whether he and coaching staff interfered with criminal investigations or misconduct cases involving players.</p><p xmlns="">TENNESSEE — Named Tyson Helton offensive coordinator, Kevin Sherrer defensive coordinator/inside linebackers coach, Terry Fair cornerbacks coach, Craig Fitzgerald strength coach, Will Friend offensive line coach, Robert Gillespie running backs coach, David Johnson receivers coach, Charles Kelly special teams coordinator, Brian Niedermeyer tight ends coach, Tracy Rocker defensive line coach, Chris Rumph co-defensive coordinator/outside linebackers coach, Drew Hughes director of player personnel and Todd Watson director of football operations.</p><p xmlns="">TCU — Pormoted Jeremy Modkins to cornerbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">UCONN — Reinstated F Eric Cobb to the men's basketball team.</p><p xmlns="">VANDERBILT — Named Jason Tarver defensive coordinator, Shawn Mennenga special teams coordinator, Aaron Moorehead wide receivers coach and Terrence Brown cornerbacks coach.</p><p xmlns="">WISCONSIN — Named Alando Tucker director for sudent-athlete engagement.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>