<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="3218b718-e562-4e5e-88ee-0f29169884be" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AL--Selma Mill Investment,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>SELMA, Ala. (AP) — International Paper, a Tennessee-based company, is investing millions more into a mill in central Alabama.Al.com reports that the pulp and paper company plans to invest $552.7 million in its Riverdale Mill to boost...</summary><sourceId>04773d91-f847-4928-928a-061e3760ea81</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:e2429%tntn-%r%BC-AL--Selma Mill Investment,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Company to increase investment to $522 million for mill</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: Updates with further details</p><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">SELMA, Ala. (AP) — International Paper, a Tennessee-based company, is investing millions more into a mill in central Alabama.</p><p xmlns="">Al.com reports that the pulp and paper company plans to invest $552.7 million in its Riverdale Mill to boost productivity. The company, located in Memphis, planned a $300 million conversion of its No. 15 paper machine at the mill.</p><p xmlns="">The initial conversion would have allowed the mill to produce high quality whitetop linerboard and containerboard, adding 450,000 tons of annual capacity. With the additional investment, the mill will convert a line making uncoated freesheet, or copy paper, to linerboard and containerboard.</p><p xmlns="">The products are important to the packing industry, the company said.</p><p xmlns="">"This project is another indication of International Paper's strong commitment to its Riverdale Mill and its workforce there," Commerce Secretary Greg Canfield said. "It's a great example of a company preserving its investment in a facility, and the jobs there, by pivoting output from one product to another that is in greater demand."</p><p xmlns="">Dallas County Economic Development Authority Executive Director Wayne Vardaman said the move is a "tremendous investment" in the community.</p><p xmlns="">"IP is Dallas County's largest employer with over 750 employees and numerous indirect jobs," Vardaman said. "These employees now know that the Riverdale Mill is here to stay."</p><p xmlns="">Vince Perez, a project manager at the Alabama Department of Commerce, said the project will be aided by the Alabama Reinvestment Act, a new version of the traditional abatement act used on projects.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>