<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2152d569-d256-4fe2-966d-e4161ca6bc79" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0423</summary><sourceId>11e7c9e9-81d4-47be-7be9-a1abe92d7d56</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6471%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0423</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><p xmlns="">Feb. 6</p><p xmlns="">1943 — Montreal's Ray Getliffe scores five goals to lead the Canadiens to an 8-3 triumph over the Boston Bruins.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Ted Williams signs a contract with the Boston Red Sox for $135,000, making him the highest paid player in major league history.</p><p xmlns="">1967 — Muhammad Ali successfully defends his world heavyweight title with a 15-round decision over Ernest Terrell in the Houston Astrodome.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — The NBA expands to 18 teams with the addition of franchises in Buffalo, Cleveland, Houston and Portland.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — The West beat the East, 123-111, in the ABA All-Star Game held in Salt Lake City. Willie Wise of the Utah Stars leads all scorers with 26.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Seventeen-year-old Dianne Roffe becomes the first U.S. woman to win a gold medal in a World Alpine Ski Championship race, capturing the giant slalom in 2:18.53.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Brett Hull of the St. Louis Blues scores his 50th goal, making him and his Hall of Famer father, Bobby Hull, the only father-son combination in NHL history to reach that milestone.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Randy Moss sets records with nine catches for 212 yards, and Mike Alstott scores three touchdowns in the NFC's 51-31 victory over the AFC, the highest-scoring Pro Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Pavel Bure records the 11th hat trick in All-Star history and goalie Olaf Kolzig plays a shutout third period as the World team routs North America 9-4 in the NHL's 50th All-Star game.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — The New England Patriots win their third Super Bowl in four years, 24-21 over the Philadelphia Eagles. It's their ninth straight postseason victory, equaling Vince Lombardi's Green Bay Packers.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — New England Patriots quarterback Tom Brady becomes the first unanimous choice for The Associated Press NFL Most Valuable Player Award. Brady gets all 50 votes since the AP began using a nationwide panel of media members who cover the league.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Aaron Rodgers throws three touchdown passes and Nick Collins returns an interception for another score, leading the Green Bay Packers to a 31-25 victory over the Pittsburgh Steelers in the Super Bowl.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Germany's Tobias Wendl and Tobias Arlt claim the record for the most Luge World Cup doubles wins in history. The Olympic champions clock a combined time of 1:40.368 to move onto 35 wins, one more than compatriots Patric Leitner and Alexander Resch, who retired in 2010.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>