<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The Island Packet (Hilton Head Island, S.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="19fc4ac0-965b-7192-ce9f-2beb3400c507" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Michael Olinger</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The Island Packet (Hilton Head Island, S.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-HOME-INSTAPOT-RECALL:HH — moms (250 words)</title><summary>Multi-purpose cookware company Instant Pot has issued a recall following reports of one its products overheating and melting, according to a post from the company in the Instant Pot Community Facebook group.The issue is with the Gem 65 8-in-1...</summary><sourceId>b7dcaec5-147e-d5bc-5bc4-576efcadcb05</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K7391%knihr%w%BC-HOME-INSTAPOT-RECALL:HH — moms (250 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Popular cooker recalled for overheating, melting. How to tell if yours is affected</h2><byline xmlns="">By Michael Olinger</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The Island Packet (Hilton Head Island, S.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">Multi-purpose cookware company Instant Pot has issued a recall following reports of one its products overheating and melting, according to a post from the company in the Instant Pot Community Facebook group.</p><p xmlns="">The issue is with the Gem 65 8-in-1 Multicooker, a device similar to a slow cooker, but with more functions, including roasting, stewing, baking, steaming, and searing, according to the company’s website.</p><p xmlns="">Instant Pot says, in their post, that the affected products have batch codes of 1728, 1730, 1731, 1734, and 1746. Batch codes can be found on a silver label on the underside of the cooker, on the bottom right side of the label, the post says.</p><p xmlns="">If your cooker has one of these codes on it, Instant Pot asks in their post that you stop using it.</p><p xmlns="">“We want you to know that we take any problem with our products extremely seriously as safety and quality are our primary concern, and we are working cooperatively with the US Consumer Product Safety Commission,” the post says in part. “We anticipate providing updated information and next steps regarding receiving a replacement Gem 65 8-in-1 Multicooker within the next few weeks.”</p><p xmlns="">Those with questions or concerns were directed in the post to call Instant Pot’s customer care line at 1-800-828-7280, extension 2.</p><p xmlns="">Instant Pot brand products are sold at several retailers across the U.S. according to the corporate website, including Amazon, Belk, Kroger, Target, and Walmart.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The Island Packet (Hilton Head, S.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The Island Packet (Hilton Head, S.C.) at www.islandpacket.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>