<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="3fc362a9-f3f8-46dd-919e-bfecafe7858d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0540</summary><sourceId>12fd8e60-6241-4a69-a699-8a9c0eb05e9b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z8089%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0540</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Saturday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WHITE SOX — Agreed to terms with 1B Diego Goris and LHP Matt Tomshaw on minor league contracts.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Miguel Almonte and Trevor Oaks; LHP Eric Skoglund; C Cam Gallagher; INFs Cheslor Cuthbert, Adalberto Mondesi and Ramon Torres; and OFs Jorge Bonifacio, Billy Burns, Paulo Orlando and Bubba Starling on one-year contracts and OF Michael Saunders on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with SS Erick Aybar on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Clayton Blackburn, Matt Bush, Jonathan Hernandez, Ronald Herrera, Ariel Jurado, Jose Leclerc, Ricky Rodriguez and Connor Sadzeck; LHPs Brett Martin and Yohander Mendez; C Brett Nicholas and Jose Trevino; INFs Joey Gallo, Ronald Guzman, Isiah Kiner-Falefa, and Drew Robinson; and OFs Willie Calhoun, Delino DeShields, Nomar Mazara and Carlos Tocci on one-year contracts.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI REDS — Agreed to terms with LHP Oliver Perez on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO ROCKIES — Agreed to terms with RHP Junior Franco on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PIRATES — Agreed to terms with LHP Kevin Siegrist on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Transferred G Josh Magette and F Andrew White III to Erie (NBAGL).</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES LAKERS — Assigned C Thomas Bryant to South Bay (NBAGL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Recalled C Kalle Kossila from San Diego (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Recalled F Laurent Dauphin from Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Assigned F Ryan Lomberg to Stockton (AHL). Placed G Mike Smith on injured reserve. Recalled Fs Tanner Glass and Andrew Mangiapane from Stockton.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Recalled D Tyler Ganly from Greenville (ECHL) to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">EDMONTON OILERS — Traded D Brandon Davidson to the N.Y. Islanders for a 2019 third-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES KINGS — Assigned F Jonny Brodzinski and G Scott Wedgewood to Ontario (AHL). Recalled D Paul LaDue to Ontario.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned F Blake Pietila to Binghamton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Reassigned F Samuel Blais and D Chris Butler to San Antonio (AHL). Recalled D Jordan Schmaltz and F Tage Thompson from San Antonio.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BINGHAMTON DEVILS — Returned LW Kevin Morris to Manchester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Assigned Fs Matt Gaudreau and Kellen Jones to Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND MONSTERS — Assigned G Ivan Kulbakov to Quad City (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SPRINGFIELD THUNDERBIRDS — Assigned G Evan Cowley to Manchester (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI CYCLONES — Loaned F Brandon McNally to Chicago (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO EAGLES — Claimed F Nick Miglio off waivers from Kansas City.</p><p xmlns="">QUAD CITY MALLARDS — Loaned G C.J. Motte to Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Released F Ryan Penny from his professional tryout agreement.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">COLORADO RAPIDS — Signed D Sam Vines to a three-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">PURDUE — Named Mark Tommerdahl special teams and tight ends coach.</p><p xmlns=""></p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>