<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8ffe6be4-462c-4b26-a857-6e087b65a5d6" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0557</summary><sourceId>47f823ba-2bf6-4b6b-b6ba-c44e00fa866c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6883%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0557</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">March 3</hl2><p xmlns="">1920 — The Montreal Canadiens set an NHL record for most goals in a game with a 16-3 rout of the Quebec Bulldogs.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Temple's Bill Mlkvy scores an NCAA-record 73 points in a 99-69 rout over Wilkes.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Buckpasser wins the Flamingo Stakes by a nose, under the guidance of Bill Shoemaker. The colt is such a prohibitive favorite among the field of nine that the race is declared a non-wagering contest. The race is known as "The Chicken Flamingo."</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Montreal's Jean Beliveau becomes the second NHL player to score 1,000 career points with a goal in a 5-2 loss to the Detroit Red Wings.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Peter Ueberroth, president of the Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee, is elected commissioner of baseball by major league team owners.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Willie Shoemaker becomes the first jockey to win $100 million in career purses after riding Lord at War to victory at the Santa Anita Handicap in Arcadia, Calif.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Mike Tyson adds the WBA heavyweight crown to his WBC heavyweight crown with a unanimous 12-round decision over James "Bonecrusher" Smith in Las Vegas.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Edward Fryatt ties a PGA Tour record with eight consecutive birdies in the second round of the Doral-Ryder Open. Fuzzy Zoeller did it in the 1976 Quad Cities Open, and Bob Goalby in the 1961 St. Petersburg Open.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Maurice Greene equals his world record in the 60-meter dash, running 6.39 seconds in a semifinal heat at the USA Indoor Championships in Atlanta. Greene matches the time he set Feb. 9, 1998, at Madrid, Spain.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — A bloodied John Ruiz becomes the first Hispanic heavyweight champion by knocking Evander Holyfield down with a huge right hand in the 11th round to win a unanimous 12-round decision for the WBA heavyweight title.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Brittney Griner punches an opponent in the face and is ejected from No. 14 Baylor's 69-60 win over Texas Tech. Officials toss the freshman with 9:01 remaining after she strikes Texas Tech sophomore forward Jordan Barncastle. Griner later receives a two-game suspension.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Orlando, down by 24 in the third quarter, goes on an unbelievable 40-9 run over the next 15 minutes and shocks the Miami Heat 99-96. The comeback is the second-largest comeback in Orlando franchise history.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — LeBron James scores a career-high 61 points, breaking Glen Rice's franchise record, and the Miami Heat defeat the Charlotte Bobcats 124-107.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Frank Mason III caps one of the biggest comebacks in Allen Fieldhouse history by scoring the last eight points in overtime to lead No. 9 Kansas past No. 20 West Virginia 76-69. It's the 11th consecutive Big 12 championship for Kansas. Mason ends with 19 points for the Jayhawks, whose 11 straight conference titles trail only the 13 in a row UCLA won in the John Wooden era.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — No. 1 Kentucky overcomes a nine-point deficit in the second half to keep its perfect season (30-0) intact, beating Georgia 72-64.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Kyrie Irving scores 43 points, LeBron James has 38 and the Cleveland Cavaliers set the NBA regular-season record with 25 3-pointers as they turned back Atlanta's late rally to beat the Hawks 135-130.</p><p xmlns="">___</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>