<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="efeba15f-dfb6-4c83-b638-b22974a59dec" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions</title><summary>BC-Transactions,0370</summary><sourceId>0c6b75e4-b182-40cf-0cfa-c28e33b375b3</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2706%-----%r%BC-Transactions;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions,0370</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">DETROIT TIGERS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Johnny Barbato, Buck Farmer, Artie Lewicki and Drew VerHagen; LHP Daniel Norris; Cs Grayson Greiner and John Hicks; INFs Sergio Alcantara and Jeimer Candelario and OFs Mikie Mahtook and Victor Reyes.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY RAYS — Traded INF Ryan Schimpf to Atlanta Braves in for a player to be named or cash.</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS CARDINALS — Agreed to terms with INF Paul DeJong on a six-year contract through 2023. Signed OF Tommy Pham. Agreed to terms with RHPs Matt Bowman, John Brebbia, Jack Flaherty, John Gant, Derian Gonzalez, Conner Greene, Dominic Leone, Josh Lucas, Mike Mayers, Alex Reyes, Sam Tuivailala and Luke Weaver; LHPs Austin Gomber and Ryan Sherriff; C Carson Kelly; INFs Greg Garcia, Jose Martinez, Yario Munoz, Edmundo Sosa, Breyvic Valera, Luke Voit and OFs Harrison Bader, Oscar Mercado and Tyler O'Neill. Re-assigned RHPs Hector Mendoza, Daniel Poncedeleon and Jake Woodford; LHP Jordan Schafer; Cs Jeremy Martinez and Dennis Ortega and INF Max Schrock to their minor league camp.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY JACKALS — Signed INF Kevin Whatley.</p><p xmlns="">QUEBEC CAPITALES — Signed INF Shao-Pin Ho.</p><p xmlns="">ROCKLAND BOULDERS — Signed RHP Ryan Deemes.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Called up G Josh Magette and F Andrew White III from Erie (NBAGL).</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WIZARDS — Signed G Ramon Sessions to a 10-day contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Recalled F Roope Hintz from Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">EDMONTON OILERS — Signed F Colin Larkin to a one-year NHL entry level contract beginning in 2018-19.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BAKERSFIELD CONDORS — Signed F Colin Larkin and D Logan Day to amateur tryout contracts for the remainder of the 2017-18 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Announced D Taylor Doherty and F Lindsay Sparks were recalled by Providence (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Traded F Ashton Rome to Manchester for D Justin Agosta.</p><hl2 xmlns="">OLYMPIC SPORTS</hl2><p xmlns="">IAAF — Announced the resignation of chief executive officer Olivier Gers.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>