<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="563da1d8-ec41-eea6-3311-dfd8212f66fe" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Gary Robbins</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-CMP-SANDIEGOSTATE-TRUMP:SD — national, itop (500 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — San Diego State University on Wednesday changed the name of one of its courses after the school was criticized by the public for implying that President Donald Trump should be impeached or removed from office.The one-unit course,...</summary><sourceId>67286316-86ee-8d33-d33f-774d4d58ba78</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3421%kniht%r%BC-CMP-SANDIEGOSTATE-TRUMP:SD — national, itop (500 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">San Diego State changes course title that implied that Trump should be impeached</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Gary Robbins</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — San Diego State University on Wednesday changed the name of one of its courses after the school was criticized by the public for implying that President Donald Trump should be impeached or removed from office.</p><p xmlns="">The one-unit course, which begins Friday, was titled “Trump: Impeachment, Removal or Conviction?”</p><p xmlns="">Following the outcry, the name Trump was dropped from the title.</p><p xmlns="">“In retrospect, we realize the title of the course, “Trump: Impeachment, Removal or Conviction?” is inconsistent with the course content described,” SDSU said in a statement. “As a result, the title will be amended to accurately reflect this course offered now and for future offerings of this course.</p><p xmlns="">“The course presents an overall framework of impeachment, removal or criminal investigation of a president and rather than focusing on President Trump, reviews all 19 impeachments in U.S. history. The one-unit, weekend class is not a requirement for graduation and is not paid for by state funds.”</p><p xmlns="">The course is offered through SDSU’s extended studies program and is meant for the general public. However, students can take the course and earn credit toward graduation.”</p><p xmlns="">The course description says the class will focus “on the two constitutional grounds: impeachment and removal (25th Amendment), and the possible charges of the independent counsel, the powers of the president, a history of the creation of that office and the comparison of divine right and rule of law leadership, presidential impeachments, including Nixon’s de facto impeachment, practically limitless grounds for impeachment, presidential immunity from indictment, and grounds for impeachment, removal, or indictment covering: conflict of interests, foreign emoluments, climate change, racism, religious bias, improper influence, nepotism, and a host of crimes, including conspiracy, false statements, and obstruction of justice.”</p><p xmlns="">The required textbook for the course is “The Case for Impeachment,” by Allan J. Lichtman, a history professor at American University in Washington, D.C.</p><p xmlns="">In late 2016, Lichtman predicted that Trump would win the presidency. He has correctly predicted the winning presidential candidate in every election since 1984.</p><p xmlns="">Lichtman published “The Case for Impeachment” in April 2017. The book examines the circumstances under which Trump could be impeached or removed from office. It also explores impeachment efforts that have been waged throughout American history.</p><p xmlns="">Lichtman is deeply familiar with the electoral process. In 2006, he ran for the U.S. Senate in Maryland, running as a Democrat.</p><p xmlns="">The SDSU course is being taught by John Joseph Cleary, a lecturer who could not immediately be reached for comment.</p><p xmlns="">Brandon Jones, an SDSU student who chairs the school’s College Republicans group, told Fox News on Wednesday, “San Diego State seems to sending a very clear message … They’re making a very strong claim that the president has sort of committed crimes of treason or bribery and that he has allegedly been accused of violating Article 2, Section 4 of the Constitution …</p><p xmlns="">“We see this all the time. College campuses, especially San Diego State University, there’s tons of liberal bias.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194): TRUMP-SANDIEGOSTATE-TRUMP</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002953,t000002996</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>