<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4d6638f2-fbf8-d16e-e3f0-0767c74daf12" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kevin Acee</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-PADRES-LOPEZ:SD — sports (950 words)</title><summary>There are people who let life’s cruel vagaries crush them, and then there are successful people.Raffy Lopez has been run over, stayed down and nearly destroyed. And then he decided to become who he is now.He’s the long shot who doesn’t care...</summary><sourceId>cf40a4ba-ac3f-f029-0294-9cab03cc2e6f</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1334%kniht%r%BC-BBN-PADRES-LOPEZ:SD — sports (950 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Padres catcher Raffy Lopez gained perspective from tragedy, struggle</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Kevin Acee</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">There are people who let life’s cruel vagaries crush them, and then there are successful people.</p><p xmlns="">Raffy Lopez has been run over, stayed down and nearly destroyed. And then he decided to become who he is now.</p><p xmlns="">He’s the long shot who doesn’t care because he’s learned that sometimes there is absolutely nothing a person can do except take a fastball to the facemask and shake it off.</p><p xmlns="">In the last four seasons, Lopez played for four major-league organizations and, briefly, for the Bridgeport Bluefish of the independent Atlantic League.</p><p xmlns="">He signed a minor-league deal with the Padres this winter in hopes of earning their backup catcher spot, and it looked like a decent proposition until spring training started.</p><p xmlns="">His task got much more difficult a few days into camp when the team signed 10-year veteran A.J. Ellis.</p><p xmlns="">“You roll with everything,” Lopez said the day after Ellis arrived. “It doesn’t change anything.”</p><p xmlns="">And before anyone rolls their eyes at a platitude as well-worn as sandlot catchers gear, they should know that in Lopez’s case some cliches are truer than others.</p><p xmlns="">“For me,” he said, “the way my career has gone, and with some things off the field I’ve dealt with, I just gained a perspective. … I learned you get to go home at the end of the day and take a deep breath.”</p><p xmlns="">Two years ago, on the eve of Lopez’s wedding, two hours before the rehearsal dinner, his mother suffered a brain aneurysm. She was in a coma while her son recited his vows, and she died a short while later.</p><p xmlns="">“It was the worst thing that ever happened to me, but it turned into the best thing,” Lopez said. “It just changed my outlook on things.”</p><p xmlns="">Lopez, 30, maintains the intensity and drive to play at this level. He isn’t seen sitting still very often, hustling to the batting cage between catching live batting practice and bullpens, working early and late on blocking balls in the dirt. Catchers are the busiest players in spring training.</p><p xmlns="">He has simply gained the perspective that what is going to happen is going to happen.</p><p xmlns="">“Am I going to be upset if I do poorly? Yes,” he said. “But I’m going to go home tonight and feel differently than I used to.”</p><p xmlns="">It took a year of severe struggles to absorb that into his identity.</p><p xmlns="">Lopez spent part of the 2016 season that followed his mother’s death with the Cincinnati Reds’ Triple-A affiliate and also a month in the Atlantic League. He hit .213/.262/.297 with one home run in 155 at-bats in Triple-A.</p><p xmlns="">“I had a hard time dealing with it,” he said. “There were other deaths in the family that happened in that span too. There was a lot of bitterness, anger. I had the worst year of my life.”</p><p xmlns="">The game he loved turned into something he despised.</p><p xmlns="">“It became my enemy in a sense,” Lopez said. “If I lined out, I was upset. I was thinking, ‘I should have good luck now.’ … I remember going through that year hating showing up to the field, hating everything.”</p><p xmlns="">He drove home to St. Louis at the end of that season, on his 29th birthday. His wife was asleep when he arrived. He spent the next day as he had on the drive home — contemplating his situation, the past and future and how it all might be different.</p><p xmlns="">His wife, an OB-GYN resident, arrived home from work and joined him and their dog on the couch.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t want to have another year like this,” Lopez eventually told her.</p><p xmlns="">“Neither do I,” she replied.</p><p xmlns="">Now, Lopez remembers it simply as a decision to stop wallowing.</p><p xmlns="">“Something went off in me that said, ‘You can’t live this way,’ ” he recalled. “I just decided to kind of appreciate things more. … We just decided we can’t live angry, pissed, feeling unlucky.”</p><p xmlns="">He hit .293/.368/.551 with 12 homers in Triple-A last year and homered four times in 54 at-bats for the Toronto Blue Jays. He said he made some “swing changes” but that the real difference was the change in mentality.</p><p xmlns="">“It’s just a different outlook that allows me to be me, allows me to play a little more relaxed,” he said. “Obviously, the game is important and there is a lot of livelihoods the line, a lot of money on the line. But you also realize the other side.”</p><p xmlns="">It would be difficult for the Padres to cast aside Ellis, who is a solid defender and has already established himself as a clubhouse leader. That sort of presence is something the Padres have purposefully sought in multiple additions to their roster.</p><p xmlns="">But Lopez is doing what he can with the deep-seated conviction that is all he can do.</p><p xmlns="">A home run and a single Tuesday against the Mariners were exactly what the Padres would want from his left-handed bat off the bench.</p><p xmlns="">His time in the majors — 83 plate appearances in 39 games over parts of three summers — has been spent with the Cubs, Reds and Blue Jays. He also was at Triple-A with the Angels organization for a time in 2015.</p><p xmlns="">In all, between the minor and major leagues, this is his 15th clubhouse since being drafted by the Cubs in the 16th round in 2011 out of Florida State.</p><p xmlns="">“I feel that’s what makes me attractive,” he said. “Just plug me in. I’m like a chameleon. I blend in.”</p><p xmlns="">He gets it, too. He brings perspective.</p><p xmlns="">“It’s a difficult lifestyle,” he said. “But you can only play for so long.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>