<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-SPORTSWATCH' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="5bf9b040-3e1f-4ee1-a11a-0418ace9fa54" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TV SportsWatch,ADV03-04</title><summary>BC-TV SportsWatch,ADV03-04,2786</summary><sourceId>4cd70652-8b30-4ac7-ac7a-c7ff90a9b881</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6665%-----%r%BC-TV SportsWatch,ADV03-04;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-TV SportsWatch,ADV03-04</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-TV SportsWatch,ADV03-04,2786</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Sports on TV</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Eds: For release weekend editions March 03-04</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv03</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">(All times Eastern)</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Schedule subject to change and/or blackouts</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday, March 5</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">6 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — CAA Tournament, first semifinal, at North Charleston, S.C.</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — MAAC Tournament, final, at Albany, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Horizon League Tournament, first semifinal, at Detroit</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — CAA Tournament, second semifinal, at North Charleston, S.C.</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — West Coast Tournament, first semifinal, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — SoCon Tournament, final, at Asheville, N.C.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Horizon League Tournament, second semifinal, at Detroit</p><hl2 xmlns="">11:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — West Coast Tournament, second semifinal, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Minnesota vs. Philadelphia, at Clearwater, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Arizona vs. San Diego, at Peoria, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Detroit at Cleveland</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Portland at L.A. Lakers</p><hl2 xmlns="">NHL HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Toronto at Buffalo</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2:55 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, Crystal Palace vs. Manchester United</p><hl2 xmlns="">WOMEN'S COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — MAAC Tournament, final, at Albany, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, first semifinal, at Chicago</p><hl2 xmlns="">4:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, first semifinal, at Uncasville, Conn.</p><hl2 xmlns="">6:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, second semifinal, at Chicago</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — AAC Tournament, second semifinal, at Uncasville, Conn.</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big 12 Tournament, final, at Oklahoma City ---</p><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday, March 6</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — ACC Tournament, first round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — ACC Tournament, first round, team TBA vs. Pittsburgh, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — CAA Tournament, final, at North Charleston, S.C.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — Horizon League Tournament, final, at Detroit</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Northeast Conference Tournament, final, at higher-seeded school</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — ACC Tournament, first round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — West Coast Tournament, final, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Summit League Tournament, final, at Sioux Falls, S.D.</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Houston (ss) vs. N.Y. Mets, at Port St. Lucie, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Colorado vs. Seattle, at Peoria, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">TNT — Houston at Oklahoma City</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">TNT — New Orleans at L.A. Clippers</p><hl2 xmlns="">NHL HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Detroit at Boston</p><hl2 xmlns="">10 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Washington at Anaheim</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — UEFA Champions League, Round of 16, 2nd Leg, Paris Saint-Germain vs. Real Madrid</p><p xmlns="">FS2 — UEFA Champions League, Round of 16, 2nd Leg, Liverpool vs. Porto</p><hl2 xmlns="">WOMEN'S COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Horizon League Tournament, final, at Detroit</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Summit League Tournament, final, at Sioux Falls, S.D.</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — West Coast Tournament, final, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — AAC Tournament, final, at Uncasville, Conn.</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, final, at Chicago ---</p><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday, March 7</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, second round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, second round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — ACC Tournament, second round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Big 12 Tournament, first round, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, first round, at New York</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, first round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">7:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Patriot League Tournament, final, at higher-seeded school</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — ACC Tournament, second round, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Big 12 Tournament, first round, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, first round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">9:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, first round, at New York</p><hl2 xmlns="">GOLF</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 a.m. (Thursday)</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — European PGA Tour, Hero Indian Open, first round, at New Delhi</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Chicago Cubs vs. Cleveland, at Goodyear, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — Toronto at Detroit</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — Cleveland at Denver</p><hl2 xmlns="">NHL HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Pittsburgh at Philadelphia</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — UEFA Champions League, Round of 16, 2nd Leg, Tottenham vs. Juventus</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — UEFA Champions League, Round of 16, 2nd Leg, Manchester City vs. Basel</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNEWS — Women, She Believes Cup, United States vs. England, at Orlando, Fla. ---</p><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday, March 8</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, first quarterfinal, Virginia vs. team TBA, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, first round, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, first quarterfinal, at New York</p><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second round, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, first quarterfinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, second round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, second quarterfinal, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, first round, at Orlando, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, second quarterfinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, second quarterfinal, at New York</p><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second round, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, first quarterfinal, Nevada vs. team TBA, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, second round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">5:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, second quarterfinal, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">6 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second round, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, third quarterfinal, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, third quarterfinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, first round, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, third quarterfinal, at New York</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, second round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second round, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, third quarterfinal, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, first round, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, second round, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">9:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at New York</p><hl2 xmlns="">11:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, team TBA vs. San Jose St., at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Pac-12 Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">GOLF</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, first round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 a.m. (Friday)</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — European PGA Tour, Hero Indian Open, second round, at New Delhi</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Detroit vs. Pittsburgh, at Bradenton, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, San Francisco vs. Seattle, at Peoria, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">TNT — Boston at Minnesota</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">TNT — San Antonio at Golden State</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — UEFA Europa League, Round of 16, 1st Leg, AC Milan vs. Arsenal</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — UEFA Europa League, Round of 16, 1st Leg, Leipzig vs. Zenit St. Petersburg ---</p><hl2 xmlns="">Friday, March 9</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AUTO RACING</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Monster Energy Cup Series, TicketGuardian 500, practice, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Xfinity Series, DC Solar 200, practice, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Xfinity Series, DC Solar 200, final practice, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Monster Energy Cup Series, TicketGuardian 500, qualifying, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BOXING</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Midnight</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Ronny Rios vs. Azat Hovhannisyan, junior featherweights, at Costa Mesa, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — AAC Tournament, first quarterfinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, first quarterfinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — SEC Tournament, first quarterfinal, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">1:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Conference USA Tournament, first semifinal, at Frisco, Texas</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — AAC Tournament, second quarterfinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second quarterfinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — SEC Tournament, second quarterfinal, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Conference USA Tournament, second semifinal, at Frisco, Texas</p><hl2 xmlns="">6 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, third quarterfinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">6:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — MAC Tournament, first semifinal, at Cleveland</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, first semifinal, at New York</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, first semifinal, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, first semifinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, third quarterfinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, third quarterfinal, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, first semifinal, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, second semifinal, at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big 12 Tournament, second semifinal, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><p xmlns="">ESPNU — AAC Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Big East Tournament, second semifinal, at New York</p><p xmlns="">SEC — SEC Tournament, fourth quarterfinal, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">11:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Mountain West Tournament, second semifinal, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Pac-12 Tournament, second semifinal, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">Midnight</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Big West Tournament, first semifinal, at Anaheim, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">GOLF</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, second round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">6 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — Champions Tour, Toshiba Classic, first round, at Newport Beach, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 a.m. (Saturday)</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — European PGA Tour, Hero Indian Open, third round, at New Delhi</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Pittsburgh vs. Philadelphia, at Clearwater, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Washington at New Orleans</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBA — Cleveland at L.A. Clippers</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — Bundesliga, Mainz vs Schalke</p><hl2 xmlns="">WINTER SPORTS</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">6 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — 2018 Winter Paralympics, Opening Ceremony, at Pyeongchang, South Korea</p><hl2 xmlns="">11 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — 2018 Winter Paralympics, Biathlon and Alpine Skiing, at Pyeongchang, South Korea</p><hl2 xmlns="">WOMEN'S COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — America East Tournament, final, at higher-seeded school ----</p><hl2 xmlns="">Saturday, March 10</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AUTO RACING</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Monster Energy Cup Series, TicketGuardian 500, practice, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Xfinity Series: DC Solar 200, qualifying, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">2:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — NASCAR, Monster Energy Cup Series, TicketGuardian 500, final practice, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FOX — NASCAR, Xfinity Series, DC Solar 200, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BOXING</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">10:15 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">SHO — Sergey Lipinets vs. Mikey Garcia, for Lipinets's IBF junior welterweight title; Rances Barthelemy vs. Kiryl Relikh, for the vacant WBA World super lightweight title, at San Antonio</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — Oscar Valdez vs. Scott Quigg, for Valdez's WBO featherweight title; Andy Vences vs. Erick DeLeon, junior lightweights, at Carson, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">11 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — America East Championship, at higher-seeded school</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Ivy League Tournament, first semifinal, at Philadelphia</p><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBS — American Athletic Tournament, first semifinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — SEC Tournament, first semifinal, at St. Louis</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — MEAC Tournament, final at Norfolk, Va.</p><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, first semifinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — SEC Tournament, second semifinal, at St. Louis</p><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Ivy League Tournament, second semifinal, at Philadelphia</p><hl2 xmlns="">3:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBS — American Athletic Tournament, second semifinal, at Orlando, Fla.</p><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Atlantic 10 Tournament, second semifinal, at Washington</p><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — SWAC Tournament, final, at Houston</p><hl2 xmlns="">6 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBS — Mountain West Tournament, final, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — Big 12 Tournament, final, at Kansas City, Mo.</p><hl2 xmlns="">6:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FOX — Big East Tournament, final, at New York</p><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — MAC Tournament, final, at Cleveland</p><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Big Sky Tournament, final, at Reno, Nev.</p><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Conference USA Tournament, final, at Frisco, Texas</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — ACC Tournament, final at Brooklyn, N.Y.</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Southland Tournament, final, at Katy, Texas</p><hl2 xmlns="">10 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — WAC Tournament, final, at Las Vegas</p><p xmlns="">FS1 — Pac-12 Tournament, final, at Las Vegas</p><hl2 xmlns="">Midnight</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Big West Tournament, final, at Anaheim, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">GOLF</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, third round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBC — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, third round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">5:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — Champions Tour, Toshiba Classic, second round, at Newport Beach, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Midnight</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — European PGA Tour, Hero Indian Open, final round, at New Delhi</p><hl2 xmlns="">MOTOR SPORTS</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — AMA Monster Energy Supercross, at Daytona Beach, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, N.Y. Mets vs. N.Y. Yankees, at Tampa, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">8 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Seattle vs. Cincinnati, at Goodyear, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">8:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ABC — San Antonio at Oklahoma City</p><hl2 xmlns="">RUGBY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Six Nations Championship, Ireland vs. Scotland, at Dublin</p><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Six Nations Championship, France vs. England, at Saint-Denis, France</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7:25 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, Manchester United vs. Liverpool</p><hl2 xmlns="">9:20 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — Bundesliga, Hannover vs. Augsburg</p><hl2 xmlns="">9:30 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Bundesliga, Bayern Munich vs. Hamburg</p><hl2 xmlns="">10 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, teams TBA</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:20 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — Bundesliga, Bayer Leverkusen vs. Borussia Monchengladbach</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:25 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, Chelsea vs. Crystal Palace</p><hl2 xmlns="">WINTER SPORTS</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBC — 2018 Winter Paralympics, Biathlon and Alpine Skiing, at Pyeongchang, South Korea (same-day tape)</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — FIS World Cup, Women's Slalom, at Ofterschwang, Germany (same-day tape)</p><hl2 xmlns="">10 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — 2018 Winter Paralympics, Sled Hockey: United States vs. Japan; Wheelchair Curling, at Pyeongchang, South Korea ---</p><hl2 xmlns="">Sunday, March 11</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AUTO RACING</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ABC — IndyCar, Firestone Grand Prix of St. Petersburg (Fla.)</p><hl2 xmlns="">3:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FOX — NASCAR, Monster Energy Cup Series, TicketGuardian 500, at Avondale, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Noon</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Ivy League Tournament, final, at Philadelphia</p><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBS — Atlantic 10 Tournament, final, at Washington</p><p xmlns="">ESPN — SEC Tournament, final, at St. Louis</p><hl2 xmlns="">2 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Sun Belt Tournament, final, at New Orleans</p><hl2 xmlns="">3:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBS — AAC Tournament, final, at Orlando, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">TBS — NCAA Tournament Selection Show, at Atlanta</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE SOFTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">5 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — Auburn at LSU</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE TRACK &amp; FIELD</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">7 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN2 — NCAA, Men's &amp; Women's Indoor Championships, finals, at College Station, Texas</p><hl2 xmlns="">GOLF</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, final round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBC — PGA Tour, Valspar Championship, final round, at Palm Harbor, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">5:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">GOLF — Champions Tour, Toshiba Classic, final round, at Newport Beach, Calif.</p><hl2 xmlns="">MLB BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Pittsburgh vs. Toronto, at Dunedin, Fla.</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">MLB — Spring training, Cincinnati vs. Seattle, at Peoria, Ariz.</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">3:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ABC — Golden State at Minnesota</p><hl2 xmlns="">9 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — Cleveland at L.A. Lakers</p><hl2 xmlns="">NHL HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">12:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBC — Boston at Chicago</p><hl2 xmlns="">7:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Dallas at Pittsburgh</p><hl2 xmlns="">RUGBY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Six Nations Championship, Wales vs. Italy, at Cardiff, Wales</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">9:25 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, Arsenal vs. Watford</p><hl2 xmlns="">10:30 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS1 — Bundesliga, Stuttgart vs. Leipzig</p><hl2 xmlns="">11:55 a.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — Premier League, Bournemouth vs. Tottenham</p><hl2 xmlns="">12:50 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">FS2 — Bundesliga, Borussia Dortmund vs. Eintracht Frankfurt</p><hl2 xmlns="">3 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPN — MLS, D.C. United at Atlanta United</p><hl2 xmlns="">WINTER SPORTS</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">11:30 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">NBCSN — 2018 Winter Paralympics, Snowboarding; Cross-Country Skiing: Women's Standing/VI 15km Free; Sled Hockey, at Pyeongchang, South Korea</p><hl2 xmlns="">WOMEN'S COLLEGE BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">1 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">CBSSN — Southland Tournament, final, at Katy, Texas</p><hl2 xmlns="">4 p.m.</hl2><p xmlns="">ESPNU — Ivy League Tournament, final, at Philadelphia</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-SPORTSWATCH</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>