<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Error importing an object from the XML generated by the XSL transformation associated with the object type 'story': 'Unable to connect to the database. Wrong connection parameters or server down. The connection parameters are specified in the Web.config file in the 'appSettings' section. Cannot open database "GN4Test" requested by the login. The login failed. (ERR0202)' (ERR0252)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ec1682f4-e5cb-4489-ba77-0cf65c38b630" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKN--Cavaliers-Love's Battle,1st Ld</title><summary>BC-BKN--Cavaliers-Love's Battle, 1st Ld,146</summary><sourceId>8f903f5b-b2fa-419d-19db-a67a455e58c2</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z3720%-----%r%BC-BKN--Cavaliers-Love's Battle,1st Ld;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-BKN--Cavaliers-Love's Battle,1st Ld</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-BKN--Cavaliers-Love's Battle, 1st Ld,146</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Cavs' Love discloses bouts with panic attacks, mental health</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Photo NY176, NY175</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Eds: Corrects title of essay. Adds photo. Will be updated. With AP Photos.</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Cavaliers All-Star forward Kevin Love has revealed suffering panic attacks, including one during a game this season. Love is currently sidelined with a broken left hand. He opened up about his mental health in an essay on the Players' Tribune. Love was overcome by anxiety during a Nov. 5 game against Atlanta and was briefly hospitalized. Love has long fought against seeking help, but said he drew courage following recent comments by Toronto's DeMar DeRozan, who has battled depression.</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By TOM WITHERS</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sports Writer</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND (AP) — Cavaliers All-Star Kevin Love has opened up about his panic attack this season and his struggles with mental health.</p><p xmlns="">The 29-year-old forward writes in an essay for the Players' Tribune on Tuesday that he was overcome by anxiety during a Nov. 5 home game against Atlanta. He was briefly hospitalized at the Cleveland Clinic and the episode left him shaken.</p><p xmlns="">Love is sidelined with a broken left hand. He says he has long been wary of the stigma of athletes being portrayed as weak if they speak about their psychological health. He says he drew courage after Toronto All-Star DeMar DeRozan disclosed he has dealt with depression.</p><p xmlns="">In his essay, titled "Everyone Is Going Through Something," Love says he has begun seeing a therapist. He encourages others who are suffering to seek help, saying "mental health isn't just an athlete thing. This is an everyone thing."</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>