<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="756ea81a-9085-4fd4-b604-07ce5b20ea5d" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0496</summary><sourceId>34914b00-77f7-43f0-3f0a-429fd780c86c</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z3471%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0496</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">March 1</hl2><p xmlns="">1934 — Primo Carnera retains his world heavyweight title with a unanimous 15-round decision over Tommy Laughren in Miami.</p><p xmlns="">1948 — Top-ranked NYU, the nation's only unbeaten basketball team, is upset by Notre Dame 64-59 at New York's Madison Square Garden. In a game with 17 lead changes, the Fighting Irish hold Dolph Schayes to nine points and Kevin O'Shea scores 18 for Notre Dame.</p><p xmlns="">1955 — Allen Fieldhouse, home of the Kansas Jayhawks, hosts its first basketball game and the Jayhawks beat rival Kansas State 77-66.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — Robyn Smith becomes the first woman jockey to win a stakes race when she rides North Sea to victory in the Paumonok Handicap at Aqueduct Race Track in New York.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Tuesdee Testa becomes the first female jockey to win a race at a major American Thoroughbred track when she rides Buz On to victory in the third race with at Santa Anita Park.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — Tamara McKinney becomes the first American woman skier to win the overall World Cup championship.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Wayne Gretzky of the Edmonton Oilers becomes the NHL's all-time assist leader, breaking the longtime mark of Gordie Howe. In his ninth season, Gretzky picks up assist No. 1,050 in a game against the Los Angeles Kings. Gretzky takes 681 games to surpass the record that took Howe 1,767 games to set.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Pat Day becomes the sixth jockey in history to earn $100 million in purses when he rides Wild Sierra to a second-place finish in the first race at Oaklawn Park.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — NBA referee Steve Javie ejects Portland radio analyst Mike Rice in the third quarter of the Pacers' 106-94 victory over the Portland Trail Blazers.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Atlanta's Lenny Wilkens becomes the first NBA coach to reach 1,000 career victories as the Hawks beat Cleveland 74-68.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — With 26-year-old rookie Dean Barker at Black Magic's helm, New Zealand sails into America's Cup history, becoming the first country other than the United States to defend the oldest trophy in sports.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Jackie Stiles of Southwest Missouri State becomes the NCAA career scoring leader in women's basketball, running her career total to 3,133 points with 30 in Southwest Missouri State's 94-59 victory over Creighton.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Roy Jones Jr. beats John Ruiz, becoming the second light heavyweight champion to win a piece of the heavyweight title. Jones wins a unanimous 12-round decision to take the WBA heavyweight crown.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — The Los Angeles Clippers hold New Orleans to one field goal over the final 20 minutes and an NBA record-low 16 points in the second half of an 89-67 victory.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Wichita State (31-0) rolls to a 68-45 victory over Missouri State to complete a perfect regular season. The Shockers are the first team since Saint Joseph's in 2004 to enter its league tournament unbeaten.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>