<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="f775d417-7b97-4b6c-b8f5-faebc8f84872" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-US--Treasury Bills</title><summary>WASHINGTON (AP) — The interest rate on three-month Treasury bills rose in Monday's auction to the highest level in more than nine years. The rate on six-month bills was unchanged at a continued high level.The Treasury Department auctioned $51...</summary><sourceId>1a7629f3-c09e-4c3a-c3aa-73f75ab04474</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:a1154%-----%r%BC-US--Treasury Bills;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Rate rises on 3-month US Treasury bills at weekly auction</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON (AP) — The interest rate on three-month Treasury bills rose in Monday's auction to the highest level in more than nine years. The rate on six-month bills was unchanged at a continued high level.</p><p xmlns="">The Treasury Department auctioned $51 billion in three-month bills at a discount rate of 1.660 percent, up from 1.645 percent last week. Another $45 billion in six-month bills was auctioned at a discount rate of 1.830 percent, steady from last week.</p><p xmlns="">The three-month rate was the highest since those bills averaged 1.690 percent on Sept. 8, 2008, at the height of the financial crisis. The six-month rate was the highest since those bills averaged 1.900 percent, also on Sept. 8, 2008.</p><p xmlns="">Interest rates generally have increased in recent weeks in response to higher levels of U.S. government debt and expectations of rising inflation.</p><p xmlns="">The discount rates on Treasury bills reflect that the bills sell for less than face value. For a $10,000 bill, the three-month price was $9,958.04 while a six-month bill sold for $9,907.48. That would equal an annualized rate of 1.690 percent for the three-month bills and 1.873 percent for the six-month bills.</p><p xmlns="">Separately, the Federal Reserve said Monday that the average yield for one-year Treasury bills, a popular index for making changes in adjustable-rate mortgages, rose to 2.05 percent last Thursday, compared with 2.03 percent on Monday, Feb. 26.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>