<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="cd38ab13-59a4-f6a6-214c-edf537ffd3ce" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Phillip Molnar</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TRUMP-TARIFFS-QANDA:SD — business (1200 words)</title><summary>President Donald Trump announced Thursday that his administration would pursue global tariffs of 10 percent for aluminum and 25 percent for steel. He promised during his campaign to revive U.S. steel and coal companies. We asked our panel of...</summary><sourceId>0fddffc4-92d9-df4a-f4ad-5dbc3c6912b2</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K6369%kniht%r%BC-TRUMP-TARIFFS-QANDA:SD — business (1200 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Are tariffs good for economic policy?</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Phillip Molnar</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">President Donald Trump announced Thursday that his administration would pursue global tariffs of 10 percent for aluminum and 25 percent for steel. He promised during his campaign to revive U.S. steel and coal companies. We asked our panel of experts earlier this week what they thought of tarriffs after Bloomberg reported the White House was thinking about it.</p><p xmlns="">Question: Are tariffs good for economic policy?</p><p xmlns="">Phil Blair, Manpower</p><p xmlns="">YES: When used appropriately and are justified by unfair pricing. Foreign dumping of any product, be it raw materials or manufactured goods is unfair competition. Tariffs on these selected goods are the only reasonable way to combat the situation. But tariffs should not be used without clear justification or in a retaliatory way since they clearly increase prices for American consumers.</p><p xmlns="">Kelly Cunningham, San Diego Institute for Economic Research</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs stifle competition by coercing special privileges for inefficient businesses at the expense of competent firms, and unambiguously raising prices on consumers. Protectionism cripples, hobbles, and destroys trade, while harming consumers and general prosperity. This is all done in order to confer special privileges on select groups of inefficient producers, making them comparatively larger, while making efficient producers smaller. The net effect reduces economic prosperity and the capacity of countries to otherwise trade more largely.</p><p xmlns="">David Ely, San Diego State University</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs can provoke retaliatory trade restrictions, drive up prices of imported goods, and limit choice. The U.S. Commerce Department’s proposed tariffs on imported steel and aluminum would benefit domestic manufacturers of these products. However, the tariffs will raise costs for domestic firms in construction, transportation and other industries that consume steel and aluminum as inputs and lower their competitiveness. The industries negatively impacted by tariffs employ far more workers than steel and aluminum manufacturers.</p><p xmlns="">Alan Gin, University of San Diego</p><p xmlns="">YES: Tariffs can protect some industries and the jobs associate with those industries. The industrial base of this country has been seriously impacted by the offshoring of production and jobs that resulted from free trade. That has devastated the communities where the former production facilities were located and affected the social fabric of this country. Yes, tariffs might invite retaliation against U.S. exporters, might raise prices, and might be too late to reverse the damage, but I think it is worth a try.</p><p xmlns="">Gina Champion-Cain, American National Investments</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariff policy designed politically as opposed to economically can trigger substantial negative consequences by inviting retaliation. Painstaking negotiation is required to prevent dumping without triggering a trade war. Steel and aluminum are commodities with deep roots in our manufacturing supply chain, the auto industry making up a large portion of demand. The proposed tariffs will increase U.S. consumer costs and make our manufactured goods less competitive. These tariffs suggest expedience over prudence.</p><p xmlns="">James Hamilton, UC San Diego</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs might benefit U.S. companies that produce steel, but would hurt the far larger number of U.S. companies that use steel, and would put companies like automakers at a competitive disadvantage. I’m also worried that other countries could retaliate with trade protections of their own, which would do serious damage to the U.S. and world economy. Reducing regulation and ensuring cheaper energy supplies are better ways to help the steel industry stay competitive.</p><p xmlns="">Gary London, London Group of Realty Advisors</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs are terrible for consumers, raising prices to us while mostly benefiting manufacturers. Those benefits aren’t worth it. Try buying a car in Brazil. Prepare to spend five to ten times more than that same automobile in the U.S. Why? High import tariffs. For what purpose? To protect inferior domestic products, or protect domestic jobs? Why bother? The market works better unfettered. When labor is too expensive here, things are built oversees. That is, until either labor goes up there, or robots take over the job. and then things are built here again. This isn’t America first. It is America stupid.</p><p xmlns="">Norm Miller, University of San Diego</p><p xmlns="">NO: Once the U.S. was dominant enough as the primary consumer of the world to be a dictator on trade issues, but those years are gone, just as our currency use for global trade has weakened. Recall the Canadians banning our meat exports based on faux mad cow concerns in response to our tariffs? Tariffs on steel raise construction and machine costs, temporarily protect a few industries, and hurt other innocent exporters, like our farmers who face retaliatory actions.</p><p xmlns="">Jamie Moraga, IntelliSolutions</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs aren’t usually good economic policy. It risks retaliation, could push up costs for domestic manufacturers, and increase costs to consumers. In the case of imposing tariffs on steel and aluminum imports, it’s in response to the recent memo regarding the risk being posed to our national security, which is supported by Secretary of Defense Jim Mattis. A tariff on steel and aluminum could protect U.S. metal producers from cheap imports, as China is the epicenter of global overproduction of steel. This may help correct unfair trade practices yet could have unintended negative consequences to our economy.</p><p xmlns="">Austin Neudecker, Rev</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs are used to protect domestic industries (increasing jobs in the short-term) but are stifling in the long-run. The world wins when we allow countries that make certain things efficiently to focus, and trade for things they do not. Levying tariffs increases prices for consumers, decreases investment and hinders innovation. Also, countries don’t go to war with countries they rely on economically. Invasion is costlier (in money and humans) than better trade policies.</p><p xmlns="">Bob Rauch, R.A. Rauch &amp; Associates</p><p xmlns="">NO: Low tariffs are best for the U.S. This proposed tariff is essentially a tax that raises the price of imported steel, making it more expensive than domestic steel. While this tariff would provide a source of revenue for the U.S. and help U.S. steel companies, retaliation by certain countries is possible. Additionally, we must weigh the potential threat that steel imports are to U.S. national security with the negative impacts of protectionism.</p><p xmlns="">Lynn Reaser, Point Loma Nazarene University</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs distort the efficient flow of resources across borders and stifle growth. A country’s imposition of tariffs to protect one industry can hurt other industries by provoking retaliatory measures. They also raise the costs of firms relying on inputs from the protected ones. For example, industries ranging from aircraft to autos will be affected by higher steel and aluminum tariffs and prices. Consumers will ultimately pay with higher prices on a number of goods and services.</p><p xmlns="">John Sarkisian, SKLZ</p><p xmlns="">NO: Tariffs are another form of tax imposed by governments that ultimately is paid by consumers in the form of higher prices for products. Tariffs can lead to less competition and create inefficient markets resulting in higher prices. It is unfortunate that governments impose tariffs which then leads to competing countries initiating a trade war by further imposing tariffs in response.</p><p xmlns="">Chris Van Gorder, Scripps Health</p><p xmlns="">NO: Imposing tariffs would be consistent with President Trump’s America First policy, but we now live in a global economy and protectionism policies should be used only as a last resort. While tariffs may help American steelmakers remain competitive, they will raise the cost of the many products that are made with steel. Ultimately, Americans and American businesses will pay the price, and that cost may escalate if other countries institute their own tariffs in retaliation.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002774,t000002537,t000040342,t000016748,t000181717,t000002771,t000038516,t000032262,t000016747</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>