<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="4fab8dc1-bc22-4a83-b510-ec9c9f6646b5" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0443</summary><sourceId>d6182997-370e-4011-0118-df3ca80d8e0b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0554%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0443</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Feb. 27</hl2><p xmlns="">1955 — Boston beats Milwaukee 62-57 at Providence, R.I., in a game that sets records for fewest points by one team and both teams since the introduction of the 24-second clock.</p><p xmlns="">1959 — The Boston Celtics defeat the Minneapolis Lakers 173-139. The Celtics set records for most points (173), most points in a half (90), most points in a quarter (52) and most field goals (72). Boston's Bob Cousy sets an NBA record with 28 assists to go with his 31 points. Teammate Tom Heinsohn scores 43 points.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Stan Mikita of the Chicago Black Hawks scores his 500th goal in a 4-3 loss to the Vancouver Canucks.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — Florida apprentice Mary Russ becomes the first female jockey to win a Grade I stakes in North America when she captures the Widener Handicap aboard Lord Darnley at Hialeah (Fla.) Park.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Prairie View sets an NCAA Division I record for most defeats in a season with a 112-79 loss to Mississippi Valley State in the first round of the Southwestern Athletic Conference tournament. Prairie View's 0-28 mark breaks the record of 27 losses shared by four teams.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Sweden wins its first hockey gold medal, defeating Canada 3-2 in the first shootout for a championship at the Winter Olympics in Lillehammer, Norway.</p><p xmlns="">1998 — Indiana's 124-59 victory over Portland marks the first time in the NBA's 51-year history one team scores more than twice as many points as the other.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — David Toms delivers the most dominant performance in the seven-year history of the Match Play Championship, winning eight out of nine holes to put away Chris DiMarco with the largest margin of victory in the 36-hole final. The score 6 and 5, could have been much worse as Toms was 9 up at one point.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Effa Manley is the first woman elected to baseball's Hall of Fame. The former Newark Eagles co-owner is among 17 people from the Negro Leagues and pre-Negro Leagues chosen by a special committee.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Steven Holcomb drives USA-1 to the Olympic gold medal in four-man bobsledding, ending a 62-year drought for the Americans in the event. Holcomb's four-run time was 3:24.46, with Justin Olsen, Steve Mesler and Curt Tomasevicz pushing for him.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Travis Kvapil's NASCAR Sprint Cup car is stolen from a hotel parking lot, forcing him to withdraw from a race at Atlanta Motor Speedway. The team didn't have a backup car in Atlanta, so it's forced to drop out when the car couldn't be found in time for NASCAR's mandatory inspection.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>