<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="58c6ea98-4e5b-4c1e-a4cc-7a4e8c4bc278" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0472</summary><sourceId>bb9fb137-4ad0-4022-0228-2fbb6e4e8605</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z4098%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0472</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Wednesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Agreed to terms with 1B Mike Napoli on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">KANSAS CITY ROYALS — Designated OF Billy Burns for assignment. Agreed to terms with 1B Lucas Duda on a one-year contract. Traded RHP Domingo Pena to Texas for international slot compensation.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA TWINS — Agreed to terms with DH Logan Morrison on a one-year contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Assigned F Tyler Cavanaugh to Erie (NBAGL). Signed G Jaylen Morris to a 10-day contract.</p><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES LAKERS — Waived F Corey Brewer. Recalled C Thomas Bryant from South Bay (NBAGL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA PANTHERS — Released RB Jonathan Stewart.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BEARS — Released LB Willie Young.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK JETS — Released DE Muhammad Wilkerson. Announced the retirement of RB Matt Forte.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Signed DB Buddy Jackson.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">OTTAWA SENATORS — Recalled G Marcus Hogberg from Brampton (ECHL) to Belleville (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">ST. LOUIS BLUES — Recalled F Conner Bleackley from Tulsa (ECHL) to San Antonio (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">VANCOUVER CANUCKS — Signed D Alex Biega to a two-year contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON CAPITALS — Recalled F Tim McGauley from South Carolina (ECHL) to Hershey (AHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO WOLVES — returned F Brandon McNally to Cincinnati (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEE ADMIRALS — Assigned G Jake Paterson to Allen (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SPRINGFIELD THUNDERBIRDS — Returned D Rob Hamilton to Manchester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SYRACUSE CRUNCH — Assigned G Olivier Mantha to Adirondack (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ADIRONDACK THUNDER — Traded G Tomas Sholl to Idaho for future considerations.</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Signed G Brad Barone and F Josh Henke.</p><p xmlns="">INDY FUEL — Loaned G Etienne Marcoux to Wilkes-Barre/Scranton.</p><p xmlns="">SOUTH CAROLINA STINGRAYS — Signed F Tad Kozun.</p><p xmlns="">WHEELING NAILERS — Released F Dylan Vander Esch. Signed D Ayrton Valente to an amateur tryout agreement.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">LACROSSE</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Lacrosse League</hl2><p xmlns="">BUFFALO BANDITS — Traded F Callum Crawford and a 2019 second-round draft pick to New England for F Shawn Evans and a 2019 fourth-round draft pick.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">OLYMPIC SPORTS</hl2><p xmlns="">USOC — Announced the resignation of CEO Scott Blackmun.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO FIRE — Acquired M Tony Tchani from Vancouver Whitecaps FC for $150,000 in targeted allocation money.</p><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA UNITED — Signed Ds Wyatt Omsberg and Carter Manley. Bought out the contract of D Vadim Demidov.</p><p xmlns="">MONTREAL IMPACT — Signed M Ken Krolicki to a one year deal with three option years.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK CITY FC — Signed G Jeff Caldwell.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA UNION — Acquired M Borek Dockal on loan from Henan Jianye (Super League-China). Traded a 2018 international roster spot to New York City FC for general allocation money.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO FC — Re-signed D Justin Morrow to a multi-year contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">United Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">USL — Announced El Paso, Texas, will be the next addition to the league for the 2019 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">CULVER-STOCKTON — Fired men's basketball coach Jack Schrader.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>