<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="28ffa121-a4f5-eac5-4754-531f63519aa0" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Kate Morrissey</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-IMMIGRANTS-DETENTION:SD — national, itop (900 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Many immigrants will spend the duration of their court proceedings in custody following a Supreme Court decision that on Tuesday reversed a Ninth Circuit ruling requiring periodic bond hearings.In a 5-3 ruling, the court’s...</summary><sourceId>f9189315-df58-40a2-0a20-fff07fd29abd</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K5446%kniht%r%BC-IMMIGRANTS-DETENTION:SD — national, itop (900 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Supreme Court decision means many immigrants will stay in detention for longer</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(HAS TRIM)</p><byline xmlns="">By Kate Morrissey</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Many immigrants will spend the duration of their court proceedings in custody following a Supreme Court decision that on Tuesday reversed a Ninth Circuit ruling requiring periodic bond hearings.</p><p xmlns="">In a 5-3 ruling, the court’s conservatives took issue with the way the Ninth Circuit had read immigration law relating to mandatory detention of certain groups of non-citizens. Justice Stephen Breyer wrote an impassioned dissent on behalf of the liberal side of the court. Justice Elena Kagan recused herself from the case.</p><p xmlns="">Immigration law requires mandatory detention of several groups of non-citizens including those who were convicted of certain crimes and those who were placed in the system when they arrived at the border. That second group includes many asylum seekers.</p><p xmlns="">Under the Ninth Circuit ruling, those going through immigration court proceedings were entitled to bond hearings after six months in detention and again at six month intervals after that. At those hearings, which became known as Rodriguez bonds, the federal government had to prove that the person was either dangerous to society or not likely to show up in court for an immigration hearing.</p><p xmlns="">Now that many of those going through the immigration court system in San Diego will no longer have bond hearings scheduled with judges, unless judges can move through cases more quickly, the number of people detained is likely to grow.</p><p xmlns="">Because of increased enforcement and policy changes under President Trump, the two detention facilities in the San Diego area have been so full in recent months that in December, it caused a backlog of asylum seekers at the border. Some have had to wait in Tijuana for weeks before there was room for them to ask for asylum.</p><p xmlns="">In Jennings v. Rodriguez, Justice Samuel Alito wrote in the court’s ruling that the Ninth Circuit had misapplied the “canon of constitutional avoidance,” which tells courts to opt for a way of reading a law that does not make it unconstitutional.</p><p xmlns="">In the decision, Alito said that immigration law about mandatory detention is straightforward and does not allow for an interpretation requiring bond hearings every six months.</p><p xmlns="">“Spotting a constitutional issue does not give a court the authority to rewrite a statute as it pleases,” Alito said.</p><p xmlns="">The case was based on Alejandro Rodriguez, a green card holder from Mexico who was convicted of joyriding and misdemeanor drug possession. After he’d been in immigration detention for three years fighting his case, the American Civil Liberties Union filed a lawsuit on his behalf arguing that he had a right to a bond hearing.</p><p xmlns="">Rodriguez eventually won his immigration case. The lawsuit arguing that he couldn’t be held in detention indefinitely became a class action and made its way up to the Supreme Court.</p><p xmlns="">In his dissent, Breyer argued that the majority opinion would likely make the mandatory detention part of immigration law unconstitutional.</p><p xmlns="">“We cannot here engage in this legal fiction,” Breyer wrote. “No one can claim, nor since the time of slavery has anyone to my knowledge successfully claimed, that persons held within the United States are totally without constitutional protection.”</p><p xmlns="">The Supreme Court did not decide whether immigration law concerning mandatory detention is constitutional. It sent that question back to the lower courts.</p><p xmlns="">Lauren Cusitello, founder and director of Crossroads Justice Center of San Diego, said attorneys are worried that until a court makes a decision on the constitutionality of the law, immigration judges may say they don’t have jurisdiction to grant bond to some detainees.</p><p xmlns="">“Even waiting six months to get a bond hearing — I think it’s hard for most people to understand just how difficult that is and how hard being detained can be for people,” Cusitello said.</p><p xmlns="">Officials with Immigration and Customs Enforcement have some discretion in deciding who will be placed in detention.</p><p xmlns="">Under the Trump administration’s immigration policies, ICE officers have generally kept people in detention until judges decide to release them on bond.</p><p xmlns="">“It is not common now,” Cusitello said of ICE choosing to release people. “It is in fact quite rare now in my experience.”</p><p xmlns="">(EDITORS: STORY CAN END HERE)</p><p xmlns="">Other court cases still require bond hearings for more specific groups of immigrant detainees, said Ahilan Arulanantham, legal director of the ACLU in Southern California and lead attorney in the Rodriguez case.</p><p xmlns="">A district court decision will still require bond hearings for many immigrants in the Los Angeles area as well, he said, but that will not apply to people in immigration detention in San Diego or Imperial counties.</p><p xmlns="">“In the short term, it will increase the number of people detained and further exacerbate all of the systemic problems that arise by worsening backlogs,” Arulanantham said.</p><p xmlns="">Arulanantham said he plans to push for lower courts to rule quickly on the constitutionality of the detention law.</p><p xmlns="">The Department of Justice hopes that this decision will allow immigration judges to put more time into working cases from the court’s backlog — currently over 650,000 cases.</p><p xmlns="">“We are aggressively working to implement common sense reforms to reduce that backlog, and today’s Supreme Court decision ensures that immigration judges in the Ninth Circuit can focus their valuable docket time on matters actually required by law,” said Devin O’Malley, a spokesman for the department.</p><p xmlns="">Some bond hearings that are already scheduled because of the previous Rodriguez ruling may still happen, an official from the DOJ said. The department has an internal coding system to help identify those cases.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000002953,t000138231,t000047681,t000047680,t000027855,t000392116,t000003137,t000002488,t000002458,t000190288,g000065558,g000362665,g000221937,g000362661,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>