<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="78e77083-4d1f-4a2d-9634-2fb5df27bc59" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0472</summary><sourceId>ca9279db-41d4-4bb4-bb4a-c578158f9786</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5632%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0472</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Thursday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Sign OF Daniel Fields.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed RHP Payton Lobdell to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed C Cody Erickson.</p><p xmlns="">SCHAUMBURG BOOMERS — Signed UTL Lucas Owens. Released RHP Brandon Quintero.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON WILD THINGS — Signed C Babe Thomas.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BULLS — Signed F Jarell Eddie to a 10-day contract.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND CAVALIERS — Suspended G J.R. Smith one game for detrimental conduct.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Canadian Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">EDMONTON ESKIMOS — Announced the retirement of OL D'Anthony Batiste.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Recalled F Laurent Dauphin from Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Reassigned D David Warsofsky to San Antonio (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned G Eddie Lack to Binghamton (AHL). Activated G Cory Schneider off injured reserve.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Signed F Alex Barre-Boulet to a three-year entry level contract. Recalled F Anthony Cirelli from Syracuse (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">AHL — Suspended San Diego D Korbinian Holzer one game for an illegal check to the head of an opponent in a Feb. 27 game against San Antonio.</p><p xmlns="">HARTFORD WOLF PACK — Signed G Charles Williams to a professional tryout agreement.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Signed D Kyle Chatham.</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Acquired G William King from the Brampton.</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">MINNESOTA UNITED — Promoted Stacey Hardin to athletic trainer.</p><p xmlns="">PORTLAND TIMBERS — Waived D Chance Myers.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">MUHLENBERG — Announced Corey Goff executive director of athletics and recreation will leave at the end of the 2017-18 school year.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY CITY — Announced the retirement of director of athletics Alice De Fazio. Named Ken Heaton interim director of athletics.</p><p xmlns="">NORTH CAROLINA — Named Henry Baker an assistant football coach.</p><p xmlns="">STOCKTON — Announced the retirement of women's basketball coach Joe Fussner, effective June 30.</p><p xmlns="">TUSCULUM — Announced the resignation of men's and women's golf coach Adam Buie. Announced director of athletic marketing and promotions Nick Forsberg, will serve as interim golf coach for the remainder of the spring season.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>