<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="6ad31d50-e0a6-41ab-9df9-c6c8cee7edfd" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jonathan Mattise</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>Associated Press</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-TN--Tennessee Governor-Forum</title><summary>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Tennessee's gubernatorial candidates are largely fine with proposed TennCare work requirements, with some concerns.At Tuesday's health care forum, Republican House Speaker Beth Harwell touted legislation seeking TennCare...</summary><sourceId>fecf7219-fc09-4220-2208-c37df8e46dd0</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:e2234%tntn-%r%BC-TN--Tennessee Governor-Forum;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Governor hopefuls largely OK with TennCare work requirements</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">Eds: APNewsNow. Will be updated.</p><byline xmlns="">By JONATHAN MATTISE</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">Associated Press</bycr></p><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Tennessee's gubernatorial candidates are largely fine with proposed TennCare work requirements, with some concerns.</p><p xmlns="">At Tuesday's health care forum, Republican House Speaker Beth Harwell touted legislation seeking TennCare work requirements on able-bodied patients without children under 6. Others expressed support for the concept but had questions.</p><p xmlns="">Democratic House Minority Leader Craig Fitzhugh said it wouldn't affect Tennessee much, citing limited eligibility.</p><p xmlns="">A fiscal analysis says Harwell's bill would impact 86,400 people and cost Tennessee $18.7 million annually.</p><p xmlns="">Ex-Democratic Nashville Mayor Karl Dean said he'd want assurances against too much bureaucracy.</p><p xmlns="">Republican businessman Randy Boyd said it must make economic sense for the state. Republican businessman Bill Lee said TennCare should also incentivize patients to help lower costs.</p><p xmlns="">Republican Congresswoman Diane Black, who instead attended an anti-abortion event, supports work requirements.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>