<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="a5803aac-757e-7da7-f73c-8b236f84c0ee" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Jonathan M. Alexander</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BKC-UNC-DUKE:RA — sports (450 words)</title><summary>DURHAM, N.C. — The game had all the makings of a great rivalry game.Duke and North Carolina both ranked in the top 10. One with many talented freshmen and one senior. The other, a veteran team, whose key players had won a national championship....</summary><sourceId>70aeca85-1dc0-aa93-a93e-fcb4dc7dfc64</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K4979%knihr%r%BC-BKC-UNC-DUKE:RA — sports (450 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Duke, down 10 at half, comes back to beat UNC; will be No. 2 seed in ACC tourney</h2><byline xmlns="">By Jonathan M. Alexander</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">DURHAM, N.C. — The game had all the makings of a great rivalry game.</p><p xmlns="">Duke and North Carolina both ranked in the top 10. One with many talented freshmen and one senior. The other, a veteran team, whose key players had won a national championship. Both with Hall-of-Fame coaches.</p><p xmlns="">It was the final game of the regular season and the second meeting between these two teams — No. 9 UNC won the first. After coming off heart-breaking loses, both needed a win to secure the No. 2 seed in the ACC tournament next week.</p><p xmlns="">But only one could come out on top.</p><p xmlns="">Here, late Saturday night, that team was No. 5 Duke.</p><p xmlns="">UNC led by 10 points at halftime, but the Blue Devils went on a furious run to win 74-64 at Cameron Indoor Stadium. With the win, Duke (25-6, 13-5 ACC) will be a No. 2 seed in the ACC tournament, while UNC (23-8, 12-6 ACC) will be a No. 6 seed.</p><p xmlns="">The Cameron Crazies roared and chanted. They had waited on this game. Some had camped out for six weeks to get a good seat, endured a flu outbreak four weeks in, and strong winds one day before the game, which destroyed some of their tents.</p><p xmlns="">But it must have paid off because Duke got the win. Duke senior guard Grayson Allen scored 15 points on his senior night.</p><p xmlns="">The first half of this game was ugly. But the second half, would make most people say ‘wow.’ The Tar Heels led by 10 points early.</p><p xmlns="">UNC’s Joel Berry and Theo Pinson, who had their senior night spoiled earlier this week on a game-winning 3-pointer at the buzzer, were hoping to spoil Allen’s. And after one half, it looked like that would happen. The game was tight during the first 15 minutes.</p><p xmlns="">Neither team had a lead larger than four points. But after Blue Devils scored to make the lead 24-23 with 5:38 left in the first half, the Tar Heels ended the half on an 11-2 run and led 35-25.</p><p xmlns="">Duke managed to get the score within seven points, 50-43, after nine minutes. Then the Blue Devils went on its big run.</p><p xmlns="">A 3-pointer by Marvin Bagley III started it off. After a UNC miss, Bagley scored on a layup and was fouled. The Tar Heels missed again, and Duke freshman guard Gary Trent Jr. knocked down a 3-pointer to put Duke up 52-50. Duke extended its lead to four points and kept the lead. Bagley led Duke with 21 points. UNC grad transfer Cam Johnson led the Tar Heels with 16 points.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.)</p><p xmlns="">Visit The News &amp; Observer (Raleigh, N.C.) at www.newsobserver.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000008058,t000008056,t000003183,g000221059,g000065627,g000362661,g000066164</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>