<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2cca25bb-e790-433d-9ef9-b4fe02ca6399" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0595</summary><sourceId>0fb3f232-dbcb-445c-45cb-99c14e58fb43</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2436%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0595</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">March 6</hl2><p xmlns="">1920 — Mickey Roach of Toronto scores five goals to lead the St. Patricks to an 11-2 rout of the Quebec Bulldogs.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Dorothy Hamill wins figure skating's world championships in Goteberg, Sweden.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Montclair State's Carol Blazejowski scores 52 points against Queens College, a college scoring record — for men or women — in the current Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — The San Antonio Spurs and Milwaukee Bucks combine for 337 points in the highest-scoring game in NBA history, to that point. The Spurs win 171-166 in three overtimes.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — The 12-team U.S. Football League begins its first season with five games.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Dale Hawerchuck of the Winnipeg Jets sets the NHL record for most assists in one period, with five in the second period of a 7-3 triumph over the Los Angeles Kings.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Julie Krone becomes the winningest female jockey with her 1,205th career victory. The milestone comes aboard the filly Squawter in the ninth race at Aqueduct.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Jay Sigel stages the biggest comeback in PGA and Senior tour history, rallying from 10 strokes behind to win the GTE West Seniors Classic in a four-hole playoff with Jim Colbert.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Detroit's Chris Osgood becomes the third goalie in NHL history to score a goal, firing the puck into an empty net with 11 seconds remaining in the Red Wings' 4-2 victory over Hartford.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Shaquille O'Neal of the Los Angeles Lakers scores an NBA season-high 61 points and had 23 rebounds in a 123-103 victory over the Los Angeles Clippers.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — George Mason beats North Carolina-Wilmington 35-33 in the second-lowest scoring game in the shot-clock era of NCAA basketball.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Devin Harris scores 31 points and the New Jersey Nets erase an early 16-point deficit to beat New York 113-93. The Knicks miss all 18 attempts in the most futile 3-point shooting night in league history.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Lindsey Vonn clinches her third discipline title in three days with a super-G victory in Tarvisio, Italy. She took the super-combined and downhill titles the previous two days.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The Los Angeles Clippers rout the Los Angeles Lakers 142-94. It's the most lopsided victory for the Clippers' franchise and the most one-sided loss in Lakers history.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim is suspended for nine games, with the school punished for ignoring the "most fundamental core values of the NCAA" for academic, drug and other violations committed primarily by the men's basketball program. The school is put on probation for five years and the team is forced to vacate 108 wins in which ineligible players participated.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Shane Walsh scores the winning goal in the fifth overtime to lead UMass to a 4-3 victory over Notre Dame in the longest game in NCAA Division I hockey game.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Katie Lou Samuelson scores 40 points, hitting all 10 of her 3-point shots to lead top-ranked UConn to a 100-44 rout of South Florida in the American Athletic Conference Tournament final. Samuelson sets a Division I record for consecutive 3-pointers in a game. The Huskies win their 107th straight game and extend their conference winning streak to 82 games.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Joe Thornton of the San Jose Sharks becomes the 13th NHL player to reach 1,000 assists when he sets up Joe Pavelski's empty-net goal with 26 seconds left in the third period of a 3-2 win against the Winnipeg Jets.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>