<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="ad54f40c-a3cc-44a5-89b0-84a1c8d495d3" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</summary><sourceId>dfabe9ae-819b-4d6f-d6fb-9543f3dc3a26</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z1233%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Monday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">BALTIMORE ORIOLES — Agreed to terms with DH Pedro Alvarez on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">BOSTON RED SOX — Agreed to terms with OF-DH J.D. Martinez on a five-year contract.</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO BLUE JAYS — Signed RHP Seung-Hwan Oh to a one year contract .</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI REDS — Agreed to terms with OF Ben Revere on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Signed RHP A.J. Griffin to a minor league contract.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Association</hl2><p xmlns="">GARY SOUTHSHORE RAILCATS — Traded OF Joey Havrilak to Washington in exchange for a player to be named.</p><p xmlns="">LINCOLN SALTDOGS — Signed RHP Austin Robichaux.</p><p xmlns="">SIOUX FALLS CANARIES — Signed OF Christopher Grayson and OF Burt Reynolds.</p><p xmlns="">ST. PAUL SAINTS — Signed OF Jordan Smith.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Can-Am League</hl2><p xmlns="">ROCKLAND BOULDERS — Traded INF Dylan Tice to Sugar Land for RHP Ryan Deemes.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">EVANSVILLE OTTERS — Signed OF Jeff Gardner to a contract extension.</p><p xmlns="">GATEWAY GRIZZLIES — Signed RHP Grant Black.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed RHP Alex Vargas.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed 1B/OF Derek Bauer and C Tanner Lubach.</p><p xmlns="">RIVER CITY RASCALS — Signed OF Mike Meyers.</p><p xmlns="">WINDY CITY THUNDERBOLTS — Signed C Kevin Reiher.</p><hl2 xmlns="">BASKETBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Basketball Association</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA HAWKS — Waived F Ersan Ilyasova. Called up G Josh Magette and F Andrew White III from Erie (NBAGL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">NBA Development League</hl2><p xmlns="">AGUA CALIENTE CLIPPERS — Acquired F Skylar Spencer from the G League available player pool.</p><p xmlns="">SANTA CRUZ WARRIORS — Acquired G Jeremy Pargo from the in-season waiver wire.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CAROLINA PANTHERS — Released S Kurt Coleman and DE Charles Johnson.</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BEARS — Released LB Pernell McPhee and DB Quintin Demps.</p><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND BROWNS — Claimed WR Larry Pinkard off waivers from Jacksonville.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Acquired F Jason Chimera from the New York Islanders for F Chris Wagner.</p><p xmlns="">ARIZONA COYOTES — Assigned F Laurent Dauphin to Tucson (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Claimed F Chris Stewart off waivers from Minnesota. Acquired F Nick Shore from Ottawa for a 2019 seventh-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">CAROLINA HURRICANES — Assigned C Greg McKegg to Charlotte (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS — Acquired 2018 first- and fourth-round draft picks and F Victor Ejdsell from Nashville for F Ryan Hartman and a 2018 fifth-round draft pick. Acquired a conditional 2019 fifth-round draft pick from Boston for F Tommy Wingels. Assigned F Lance Bouma to Rockford (AHL). Recalled F Matthew Highmore from Rockford.</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Acquired D Ryan Graves from the New York Rangers for D Chris Bigras.</p><p xmlns="">COLUMBUS BLUE JACKETS — Acquired D Ian Cole from Ottawa for C Nick Moutrey and a 2020 third-round draft pick. Acquired F Thomas Vanek from Vancouver for Fs Tyler Motte and Jussi Jokinen. Acquired F Ryan Kujawinski from Arizona for F Jordan Maletta.</p><p xmlns="">DALLAS STARS — Recalled F Jason Dickinson from Texas (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT RED WINGS — Acquired a 2018 first-round draft, a 2019 second-round draft pick and a 2021 third-round draft pick from Vegas for LW Tomas Tatar.</p><p xmlns="">MONTREAL CANADIENS — Acquired D Mike Reilly from Minnesota for a 2019 fifth-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">NASHVILLE PREDATORS — Signed C Mike Fisher to a one-year contract. Acquired F Brandon Bollig and G Troy Grosenick from San Jose for a 2018 sixth-round draft pick. Acquired F Tyler Gaudet and D John Ramage from Arizona for F PC Labrie and D Trevor Murphy.</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Acquired F Patrick Maroon from Edmonton for a 2019 third-round pick and the rights to F J.D. Dudek.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Traded D Ryan McDonagh and LW J.T. Miller to Tampa Bay for C Vladislav Namestnikov, D Libor Hajek, C Brett Howden, a 2018 first-round draft pick and a conditional 2019 first-round draft pick. Assigned F Vinni Lettieri to Hartford (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA FLYERS — Claimed D Johnny Oduya off waivers from Ottawa.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PENGUINS — Acquired F Josh Jooris from Carolina for C Greg McKegg and assigned him to Wilkes-Barre/Scranton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE SHARKS — Acquired F Evander Kane from Buffalo for F Danny O'Regan and conditional 2019 and 2020 draft picks.</p><p xmlns="">VANCOUVER CANUCKS — Acquired F Brendan Leipsic from Vegas for D Philip Holm.</p><p xmlns="">WINNIPEG JETS — Acquired F Paul Stastny from St. Louis for F Erik Foley, a 2018 first-round draft pick and a conditional 2020 fourth-round draft pick. Acquired D Joe Morrow from Montreal for a 2018 fourth-round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">MILWAUKEES ADMIRALS — Traded Derek Army to Tucson for future considerations.</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Signed D Ryan MacKinnon.</p><hl2 xmlns="">LACROSSE</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Lacrosse League</hl2><p xmlns="">VANCOUVER STEALTH — Signed T Andrew Suitor to a two-year contract extension through 2020.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">COLORADO STATE — Announced the resignation of men's basketball coach Larry Eustachy.</p><p xmlns="">CUMBERLAND — Announced the retirement men's basketball coach Lonnie Thompson.</p><p xmlns="">EASTERN KENTUCKY — Fired men's basketball coach Dan McHale. Named Reece Gaines men's basketball coach.</p><p xmlns=""></p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>