<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2b18e101-cd66-4b7e-8e54-5219fc8df001" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight,ADV03</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight, ADV03,3738</summary><sourceId>a97e022f-6736-469d-69d8-b6efadec2731</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z6887%-----%s%BC-AP Sportlight,ADV03;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,ADV03</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight, ADV03,3738</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Adv03</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">For release weekend editions March 3-4</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">March 4</hl2><p xmlns="">1960 — Phil Latrielle of Middlebury scores an NCAA-record 10 goals in a 13-2 victory over Colgate. Latrielle, a three time All-American, would score a record 250 goals in the 85 games of his collegiate ice hockey career.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Philadelphia Warriors registers his fifth straight 50-point game with 58 against the New York Knicks and sets a season scoring record with 3,921 points.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Joe Frazier wins the vacant New York world heavyweight title with an 11th-round TKO of Buster Mathis at Madison Square Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Guy LaFleur of the Montreal Canadiens scores his 1,000th point with a goal in a 9-3 rout over the Winnipeg Jets.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Hank Gathers, one of two Division I players to lead the nation in scoring and rebounding in the same season, dies after collapsing during Loyola Marymount's West Coast Conference tournament game against Portland. He was 23.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Mianne Bagger makes sports history at the Women's Australian Open as the first transsexual to play in a pro golf tournament.</p><p xmlns="">2006 — Rafael Nadal ends top-ranked Roger Federer's 56-match hardcourt winning streak with a 2-6, 6-4, 6-4 victory in the final of the Dubai Open.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Miikka Kiprusoff becomes the first goalie in 25 years to stop two penalty shots in a game and finishes with 37 saves, leading Calgary past Columbus 4-3.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Gonzaga, the small Northwest school that has delivered big NCAA tournament wins, is on top of The Associated Press' Top 25 for the first time. Riding the best record in Division I at 29-2, the Bulldogs become the 57th school to be ranked No. 1 since the AP poll began in January 1949.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Brittney Griner scores a Big 12 single-game record 50 points in her final regular-season game at Baylor and leads the Bears to a 98-50 win over Kansas State.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Russell Westbrook becomes the first player since Michael Jordan in 1989 to have four consecutive triple-doubles and the first since Jordan that year to have back-to-back triple-doubles with at least 40 points. Westbrook sets career highs with 49 points and 16 rebounds, and adds 10 assists, helping the Oklahoma City Thunder beat the Philadelphia 76ers 123-118 in overtime.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Marit Bjoergen wins world championship gold in the 30-kilometer classical race as Norway completes a sweep of women's cross-country ski titles at the world championships in Lahti, Finland. Bjoergen takes her record 18th career gold medal and fourth of the championships. No country had won all women's cross-country gold medals at a single world championships since Russia in 1997, when there were only five events, rather than the current six.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Austrian Marcel Hirscher stuns the world of Alpine skiing by locking up an unprecedented sixth straight overall World Cup He becomes the first male skier to win six overall titles. Hirscher's 44th career win also secures him the giant slalom title.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Napheesa Collier scores 24 points and top-ranked UConn routed Tulsa 105-57 in the American Athletic Conference quarterfinals. The Huskies (30-0) extend their NCAA-record winning streak to 105 games and reach the 30-victory mark for the 12th consecutive season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 5</hl2><p xmlns="">1924 — Frank Carauna, of Buffalo, N.Y., becomes the first to bowl two straight perfect 300 games. Carauna throws five strikes to open his third game, giving him 29 straight strikes.</p><p xmlns="">1931 — WGL radio broadcasts the first game of the American Basketball League championship series. The Brooklyn Visitations beat the Fort Wayne Hoosiers 14-10 in the first professional basketball game to be broadcast live on radio.</p><p xmlns="">1960 — Carol Heiss wins the ladies title at the World Figure Skating Championships in Vancouver.</p><p xmlns="">1965 — Ernest Terrell wins the world heavyweight title with a unanimous 15-round decision over Eddie Machen in Chicago.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Bob Seagren sets an indoor record in the pole vault with a 17-foot, ¼-inch vault in Albuquerque.</p><p xmlns="">1973 — New York Yankee pitchers Fritz Peterson and Mike Kekich announce that they've swapped wives and children.</p><p xmlns="">1981 — Scott Hamilton wins the men's title at the World Figure Skating Championships held in Hartford, Conn.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — Golden State's Joe Barry Carroll scores 52 points in a 127-121 Warrior victory over the Utah Jazz.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Mike Bossy of the New York Islanders scores his 50th goal, becoming the first NHL player to score 50 goals in eight consecutive seasons.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Ottawa and Philadelphia combine for an NHL-record 419 penalty minutes, with the Flyers setting a single-team mark with 213. There are five consecutive brawls in the final two minutes, including one involving both goalies. The previous record for penalty minutes was 406 by the Minnesota North Stars and Boston Bruins in 1981. The Flyers beat the Senators 5-3.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Makai Mason scores 22 points to lead Yale to a 71-55 victory over Columbia, clinching the Bulldogs' first NCAA Men's Tournament bid since 1962.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Clemson beats Boston College 66-50, completing the Eagles' winless regular season in Atlantic Coast Conference play. The Eagles (7-24, 0-18) are the first men's ACC team to go winless in their conference regular-season games since Maryland went 0-14 in 1986-87. Worse, BC's football team went 0-8 in league play, making the school the first in ACC history to go winless in both sports in the same academic year.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 6</hl2><p xmlns="">1920 — Mickey Roach of Toronto scores five goals to lead the St. Patricks to an 11-2 rout of the Quebec Bulldogs.</p><p xmlns="">1976 — Dorothy Hamill wins the World Figure Skating Championships in Goteberg, Sweden.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Montclair State's Carol Blazejowski scores 52 points against Queens College, setting a new collegiate scoring record (for men or women) in the current Madison Square Garden in New York.</p><p xmlns="">1982 — The San Antonio Spurs and Milwaukee Bucks combine for 337 points in the highest scoring game in NBA history, to that point. The Spurs win, 171-166, in three overtimes.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — The 12-team United States Football League begins its first season with five games.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Dale Hawerchuck of the Winnipeg Jets sets the NHL record for most assists in one period, with five in the second period of a 7-3 triumph over the Los Angeles Kings.</p><p xmlns="">1988 — Julie Krone becomes the winningest female jockey in history with her 1,205th career victory. Krone rides a filly named Squawter to victory in the ninth race at Aqueduct Racetrack.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Jay Sigel stages the biggest comeback in PGA and Senior tour history, rallying from 10 strokes behind to win the GTE West Seniors Classic in a four-hole playoff with Jim Colbert.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Detroit's Chris Osgood becomes the third goalie in NHL history to score a goal, firing the puck into an empty net with 11 seconds remaining in the Red Wings' 4-2 victory over Hartford.</p><p xmlns="">2000 — Shaquille O'Neal of the Los Angeles Lakers scores an NBA season-high 61 points and had 23 rebounds in a 123-103 victory over the Los Angeles Clippers.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — George Mason beats North Carolina-Wilmington 35-33 in the second-lowest scoring game in the shot-clock era of NCAA basketball.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — Devin Harris scores 31 points and the New Jersey Nets erased an early 16-point deficit to beat New York 113-93. The Knicks miss all 18 attempts in the most futile 3-point shooting night in league history.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Lindsey Vonn clinches her third discipline title in three days with a super-G victory to wrap up a memorable weekend of ski racing in Tarvisio, Italy. Vonn took the super-combined and downhill titles the previous two days.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The Los Angeles Clippers rout the rival Los Angeles Lakers 142-94. It's the most lopsided victory ever for the Clippers' franchise and the most one-sided loss in Lakers history.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim is suspended for nine games, with the school punished for ignoring the "most fundamental core values of the NCAA" for academic, drug and other violations committed primarily by the men's basketball program. The school is put on probation for five years and the basketball team is forced to vacate 108 wins in which ineligible players participated.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Shane Walsh scores the winning goal in the fifth overtime to lead UMass to a 4-3 victory over Notre Dame in the longest game in NCAA Division I ice hockey history.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Katie Lou Samuelson has a record-breaking night, scoring 40 points and hitting all 10 of her 3-point shots to lead top-ranked UConn to a 100-44 rout of South Florida in the American Athletic Conference Tournament final. Samuelson sets a Division I record for consecutive 3-pointers in a game. The Huskies win their 107th straight game and extends their conference winning streak to 82 games.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Joe Thornton of the San Jose Sharks becomes the 13th NHL player to reach 1,000 assists when he assists on Joe Pavelski's empty-net goal with 26 seconds left in the third period of a 3-2 win against the Winnipeg Jets.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 7</hl2><p xmlns="">1921 — Cy Denneny of the Ottawa Senators scores six goals in a 12-5 victory over the Hamilton Tigers.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — Ezzard Charles wins a unanimous 15-round decision over Jersey Joe Walcott to retain the world heavyweight title in Detroit.</p><p xmlns="">1954 — The Minneapolis Lakers and Milwaukee Hawks experiment with the baskets raised from 10 feet to 12 feet during an exhibition game. George Mikan and the Lakers win 65-63.</p><p xmlns="">1970 — Austin Carr scores an NCAA tournament record 61 points as Notre Dame routs Ohio University 112-82. Carr hits 25 of 44 field goals and 11 of 14 free throws.</p><p xmlns="">1974 — New Orleans is granted an NBA franchise.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Anthony Roberts of Oral Roberts scores 65 points in a 90-89 loss to Oregon in the first round of the National Invitation Tournament.</p><p xmlns="">1983 — Phil Mahre wins the Alpine World Cup championship for the third straight year to become the third person to win three consecutive titles.</p><p xmlns="">1987 — Thomas Hearns wins his third championship, the WBC light heavyweight title, with a 10-round TKO of Dennis Andries.</p><p xmlns="">1996 — Magic Johnson becomes the second NBA player to reach 10,000 career assists, getting the milestone on the go-ahead basket in Los Angeles' 102-90 victory over Sacramento.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Detroit becomes the first team in the NBA's shot-clock era to hold three consecutive opponents under 70 points with an 86-65 victory over Seattle. The Pistons beat Denver 97-66 and Portland 83-68.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — The Indianapolis Colts cut injured Peyton Manning, the only four-time MVP in NFL history. Manning, who missed the previous season with a neck injury, was due a $28 million bonus this week.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Kikkan Randall adds a World Cup crystal globe to her stash and carves out another slice of history for the U.S ski team. Randall is the first American in 30 years to win a cross country championship by clinching the overall sprint title. Randall's 11th-place finish at a race in Norway secures the championship with one race left in the season.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The U.S. women's soccer team's two-year unbeaten streak ends at 43 games with a 1-0 loss to Sweden at the Algarve Cup in Albufiera, Portugal. The U.S. had been 36-0-7 since a 1-0 loss to Japan at the Algarve Cup on March 5, 2012.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Kentucky (31-0) becomes the first men's basketball team from a major conference to go undefeated in the regular season since Indiana in 1976. Wichita State of the Missouri Valley Conference went undefeated in the regular season in 2014.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Stephen Curry scores 41 points and becomes the first player in NBA history to make 300 3-pointers in a season, and the Golden State Warriors set another record by holding off the Orlando Magic 119-113 for their 45th straight home victory.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Dirk Nowitzki scores the 20 points he needed for 30,000 in his career in barely more than a quarter, and the Dallas Mavericks post an easy home win over the Los Angeles Lakers, a 122-111 victory. The 7-foot German becomes the sixth NBA player and the first international one to reach the milestone, joining four Hall of Famers and a future one in Kobe Bryant.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 8</hl2><p xmlns="">1954 — The Milwaukee Hawks beat the Baltimore Bullets twice 64-54 and 65-54, in the only double-header in NBA history involving the same two teams.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — Silky Sullivan, ridden by Bill Shoemaker, wins the Santa Anita Derby by three lengths after trailing by 40 early in the race and by 20 entering the final turn.</p><p xmlns="">1971 — Joe Frazier wins the world heavyweight title with a unanimous 15-round decision over Muhammad Ali.</p><p xmlns="">1990 — Kurt Browning becomes the first Canadian to defend a title in the World Figure Skating Championships as he edges early leader Viktor Petrenko of the Soviet Union.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — Ray Floyd, 49, holds off Fred Couples for a two-stroke victory in the Doral Open and joins Sam Snead as the only men to win PGA Tour titles in four decades.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — In the World Indoor Championship in Paris, Kevin Little becomes the first white American sprinter in 41 years to win a major international competition, matching the U.S. 200 record of 20.40 seconds.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Air Force punctuates a record-setting season when it moved into The Associated Press men's basketball Top 25 for the first time in the program's 48-year history. Air Force (22-5) has a team record for wins, five more than previous record in 1957-58.</p><p xmlns="">2005 — Oakland (Mich.) upsets top-seeded Oral Roberts 61-60 to win the Mid-Continent Conference tournament and an automatic bid to the NCAAs. It's the fourth straight season a team with a losing record has made the men's NCAA tournament.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — At age 60, Saoul Mamby loses a unanimous 10-round decision to Anthony Osbourne in Grand Cayman. Mamby, a former super lightweight champion, becomes the oldest boxer in a sanctioned fight.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Kevin Garnett scores 17 points to reach the 20,000-point plateau in Boston's 119-89 victory over Memphis.</p><p xmlns="">2008 — Lindsey Vonn wins her 10th career World Cup downhill to break the U.S. record held by Picabo Street and Daron Rahlves. Vonn breaks the record with her fifth downhill of the season in 1:23.57 on the 1.4-mile Crans-Montana, Switzerland course.</p><p xmlns="">2010 — The top-ranked Connecticut Huskies set an NCAA women's record by winning their 71st straight game, a 59-44 victory over No. 6 Notre Dame in the semifinals of the Big East tournament. UConn surpasses its own mark set from Nov. 9, 2001, to March 11, 2003.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The Big East Conference announces the departure of DePaul, Georgetown, Marquette, Providence, St. John's, Seton Hall and Villanova, allowing them to separate from the football schools and create their own conference on July 1.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Deron Williams makes an NBA-record nine 3-pointers in the first half, finishes with 11 and scores a season-high 42 points to lead the Brooklyn Nets to a 95-78 victory over the Washington Wizards.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — The Chicago Blackhawks' record for the best start in NHL history ends at 24 games after a 6-2 loss to the Colorado Avalanche.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — Doug McDermott scores a career-high 45 points to become the eighth player in Division I history to go over 3,000 for a career and Creighton rolls past Providence 88-73.</p><p xmlns="">2015 — Leonardo Mayer defeats Joao Souza in the longest Davis Cup singles match ever, winning 7-6 (4), 7-6 (5), 5-7, 5-7, 15-13 to keep Argentina alive against Brazil in their first round series. Mayer needed 6 hours, 42 minutes to beat Souza, which is also longer than the record for a clay-court match on the ATP tour.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — Barcelona completes one of the most sensational comebacks in soccer by beating Paris Saint-Germain 6-1 to reach the Champions League quarterfinals, scoring the decisive goal of a 6-5 victory on aggregate in the fifth minute of stoppage time. Sergi Roberto's dramatic late goal sends the Nou Camp wild and makes Barcelona the first team to overturn a 4-0 first-leg defeat since the Champions League format started in the 1992-93 season.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — The San Antonio Spurs rally in the final quarter to win without Kawhi Leonard and overcomes a 28-point first quarter deficit. Manu Ginobili has 19 points, David Lee adds 18 points and 10 rebounds and the San Antonio Spurs rally to beat the Sacramento Kings 114-104. San Antonio (50-13) extends its league record for 50-win seasons to 18 straight.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 9</hl2><p xmlns="">1943 — Eddie Dancker banks in a desperation 25-foot hook shot from the corner to give Sheboygan a 30-29 win over Fort Wayne and the National Basketball League crown. The defeat of the Pistons is regarded as one of the biggest upsets in pro basketball history.</p><p xmlns="">1948 — NHL president Clarence Campbell expels Billy Taylor of the New York Rangers and Don Gallagher of the Boston Bruins because of gambling associations.</p><p xmlns="">1958 — George Yardley of the Detroit Pistons becomes the first NBA player to score 2,000 points in a season. Yardley averages 27.8 points per game in the 72-game season.</p><p xmlns="">1968 — Houston's Elvin Hayes scores 49 points and pulls down 27 rebounds in a 94-76 win over Loyola of Chicago in the first round of the NCAA tournament.</p><p xmlns="">1977 — Anthony Roberts of Oral Roberts sets an NIT record with 65 points in a 90-89 loss to Oregon in the first round.</p><p xmlns="">1979 — Detroit's Kevin Porter hands out a franchise-record 25 assists as the Pistons defeat the Boston Celtics 160-117.</p><p xmlns="">1984 — Tim Witherspoon wins the vacant WBC heavyweight title with a 12-round majority decision over Greg Page.</p><p xmlns="">1986 — Buffalo's Gilbert Perreault scores his 500th goal in a 4-3 win over the New Jersey Devils.</p><p xmlns="">1994 — Detroit's Dino Ciccarelli scores his 1,000th career point with a goal in a 5-1 win over Calgary.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — Ty Tryon, a 16-year-old high school sophomore, makes the cut in his first PGA Tour event. He's 1-over after the second round of the Honda Classic, making him the second-youngest player to make the cut in a PGA Tour event.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Kevin Love records his 52nd consecutive double-double to surpass Moses Malone for the longest such streak since the ABA and NBA merged in 1976 in the Minnesota Timberwolves' 101-75 over the Indiana Pacers.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Lindsey Vonn of the United States wins the World Cup giant slalom race in Are, Sweden to clinch her fourth overall title. Vonn won the overall title three times in a row from 2008-10. She missed out on the title last season, finishing three points behind Maria Hoefl-Riesch of Germany.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Liberty becomes the second 20-loss team to reach the NCAA tournament, beating Charleston Southern 87-76 to win the Big South Conference title. It joins Coppin State in 2008 as the only schools with 20 or more defeats in the field of 68.</p><p xmlns="">2013 — Bernard Hopkins becomes the oldest boxer to win a major title, scoring a 12-round unanimous decision over Tavoris Cloud to claim the IBF light heavyweight championship in New York. The 48-year-old Hopkins breaks the record he set by beating Jean Pascal for the WBC light heavyweight title on May 21, 2011.</p><p xmlns="">2016 — Russell Westbrook has 25 points, a career-high 20 assists and 11 rebounds to help the Oklahoma City Thunder beat the Los Angeles Clippers 120-108. It's the first triple-double with at least 20 points and 20 assists since Rod Strickland did it for the Washington Wizards in 1998.</p><p xmlns="">2017 — The second-ranked and top-seeded Villanova Wildcats shoot 63.2 percent (36 for 57) and commits just five turnovers in a record-setting 108-67 victory over St. John's in the Big East Tournament quarterfinals. Villanova shoots better than 50 percent from 3-point range (15 for 29). It's the most points and largest margin of victory in the tournament for Villanova and it's the worst loss the Red Storm ever endured.</p><hl2 xmlns="">March 10</hl2><p xmlns="">1913 — The Quebec Bulldogs win the Stanley Cup in two games over Sydney.</p><p xmlns="">1920 — Quebec's Joe Malone scores six goals to lead the Bulldogs to a 10-4 rout of the Ottawa Senators.</p><p xmlns="">1961 — Wilt Chamberlain of the Philadelphia Warriors becomes the first NBA player to score 3,000 points in a season. Chamberlain scores 32 points in a 120-103 loss to Detroit to bring his season total to 3,016.</p><p xmlns="">1985 — Dick Motta becomes the fourth NBA coach to record 700 victories as Dallas beats New Jersey 126-113.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Eddie Sutton of Oklahoma State becomes the first coach to lead four schools into the NCAA tournament. Sutton also coached Creighton, Arkansas and Kentucky in the tournament.</p><p xmlns="">1992 — New York Islanders coach Al Arbour becomes the second coach in NHL history to win 700 games with a 5-2 victory over Philadelphia.</p><p xmlns="">2001 — With Swedish great Ingemar Stenmark looking on, Hermann Maier wins the giant slalom for his 13th victory this season, equaling one of the mightiest alpine skiing records. Maier, winner of the overall World Cup title three of the last four years, ties the record Stenmark set in 1979.</p><p xmlns="">2002 — John Stockton, the NBA's career assist leader, has 13 assists in Utah's 95-92 loss at Houston to give him exactly 15,000 for his career.</p><p xmlns="">2004 — Orlando's Tracy McGrady scores a franchise record 62 points in a 108-99 win over Washington.</p><p xmlns="">2007 — Pittsburgh's Sidney Crosby, 19, becomes the youngest player in NHL history with two 100-point seasons after scoring a goal in a 3-2 overtime win over the New York Rangers.</p><p xmlns="">2011 — Veteran referees Jim Burr, Tim Higgins and Earl Walton, cited for two errors in the final seconds of the St. John's-Rutgers game, withdraw from the rest of the Big East tournament. The three officials missed two calls — a travel and stepping out of bounds — in the final 1.7 seconds of St. John's 65-63 win in the second-round of Big East tournament. The Big East acknowledged after the game the officials blew the calls.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Ashton Eaton of the United States sets a heptathlon world record and wins the gold at the world indoor championships in Istanbul. The American dominates the two-day competition, capping it with an overwhelming 1,000 meters. He breaks the record he set last year by 77 points with a total of 6,645.</p><p xmlns="">2014 — The game between Dallas and the Columbus Blue Jackets is postponed by the NHL after Stars forward Rich Peverley collapses on the bench during the first period.</p><p xmlns="">END ADV</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>