<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="2c1dea17-2c99-4880-a273-782158c48631" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</summary><sourceId>b09435a6-f1b7-456c-56cb-9b0b793b9dbf</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z0385%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Sunday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">American League</hl2><p xmlns="">CLEVELAND INDIANS — Placed RHP Cody Anderson on the 60-day DL. Claimed RHP Ben Taylor off waivers from Boston. Agreed to terms with RHP Matt Belisle on a minor league contract.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK YANKEES — Named Alex Rodriguez and Nick Swisher special advisers.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">TEXAS RANGERS — Agreed to terms with RHP Nick Gardewine and LHP's Alex Claudio and Joe Palumbo on one-year contracts.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">CINCINNATI REDS — Agreed to terms with C Tony Sanchez on a minor league contract.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BOSTON BRUINS — Signed RW Brian Gionta to a one-year contract. Waived D Paul Postma.</p><p xmlns="">CALGARY FLAMES — Signed D Cody Goloubef to a two-way contract for the remainder of the season and placed him on waivers for the purpose of assigning him to Stockton (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned F John Quenneville to Binghamton (AHL) and D Colton White from Binghamton to Adirondack (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK RANGERS — Traded F Rick Nash to Boston for Fs Ryan Spooner and Matt Beleskey, D Ryan Lindgren, a 2018 first-round draft pick and a 2019 seventh-round draft pick.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PENGUINS — Assigned F Vincent Dunn and F Frederik Tiffels from Wilkes-Barre/Scranton (AHL) to Brampton (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN JOSE SHARKS — Traded F Brandon Bollig and G Troy Grosenick to Nashville for a 2018 sixth-round draft pick.&lt;</p><p xmlns="">TORONTO MAPLE LEAFS — Acquired Fs Tomas Plekanec and Kyle Baun from Montreal for D Rinat Valiev, F Kerby Rychel and a 2018 second-round draft pick.</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BRIDGEPORT SOUND TIGERS — Recalled F Matt Gaudreau and Kellen Jones from Worcester (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">READING ROYALS — Returned F Ryan Penny to Reading (ECHL).</p><p xmlns="">STOCKTON HEAT — Signed G C.J. Motte to a professional tryout agreement.</p><p xmlns="">WILKES-BARRE/SCRANTON PENGUINS — Assigned Fs Cody Wydo and Troy Josephs to Wheeling (ECHL).&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ADIRONDACK THUNDER — Released F Tim Kielich.</p><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Released D Sean Escobedo.</p><p xmlns="">BRAMPTON BEAST — Released D Alex Vazquez.</p><p xmlns="">GREENVILLE SWAMP RABBITS — Added G Kent Nusbaum as emergency backup.</p><p xmlns="">MANCHESTER MONARCHS — Loaned D Colton Saucerman to Providence (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">WHEELING NAILERS — Added G Joe Spadaccini as emergency backup. Signed F Dylan Vander Esch and D Kyle Thacker to amateur tryout agreements.</p><p xmlns="">WORCESTER RAILERS — Released G Joe Spagnoli as emergency backup.&lt;</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">PURDUE — Announced wide receivers coach JaMarcus Shephard will also be co-offensive coordinator.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>