<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="943cf5b7-ef85-1392-dafa-778068fa99a6" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Tom Krasovic</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-KRASOVIC-COLUMN-SPORTSPLUS:SD — sports (1350 words)</title><summary>SAN DIEGO — Football was king in San Diego, and the king wore blue and gold, and the king reigned for nearly six decades.Yes, baseball had moments. There were All-Star games, World Series games, Hall of Fame players. However, the baseball Padres...</summary><sourceId>c79e5c4b-4677-00dd-0dd1-c5ef0bf95960</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K1091%kniht%r%BC-BBN-KRASOVIC-COLUMN-SPORTSPLUS:SD — sports (1350 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Tom Krasovic: As Chargers vibe recedes, Padres see big days ahead in San Diego</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Tom Krasovic</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">SAN DIEGO — Football was king in San Diego, and the king wore blue and gold, and the king reigned for nearly six decades.</p><p xmlns="">Yes, baseball had moments. There were All-Star games, World Series games, Hall of Fame players. However, the baseball Padres never crowded out the football Chargers for long. The NFL gobbled up too much ground, in San Diego, in the whole country, for the Chargers to stay in the shadows.</p><p xmlns="">“I think the Padres were always No. 2 to the Chargers here,” said longtime San Diego broadcaster Bob Chandler, a San Diego State graduate whose career dates to the early 1960s.</p><p xmlns="">Even after the announcement to relocate, the Chargers continued to cast a shadow over the little Pads. It took the football team six months to clear out of San Diego. By then the Pads were more than halfway through another low-watt season.</p><p xmlns="">Now comes a sea change. For the first time for a full year, the Chargers will be elsewhere than the big-league Pads.</p><p xmlns="">Don’t crown the Pads just yet. They’ve not joined a playoff race in any of the past seven years. They have the National League’s worst record over the past 10 years. They’ve not won a playoff game on San Diego soil since San Diegans voted them a new ballpark in November 1998. Oddsmakers peg the team for under 75 wins this year.</p><p xmlns="">Nor is San Diego entirely there for the taking, even with the Chargers out of the picture. The digital age has shredded the entertainment dollar into small pieces. Young adults are cutting the cord to cable TV, a main connector between the Pads and San Diegans. Baseball has become an often-tedious three-hour-plus game dominated by outcomes that don’t include putting the ball in play.</p><p xmlns="">Let’s just say the Pads have a great opportunity within their realm, here and now. They’re uniquely situated as the only Major League Baseball franchise of the 30 without an NFL, NBA or NHL team in its market.</p><p xmlns="">Before the Chargers planted themselves in San Diego in 1961, the Pads were a minor league team in the Pacific Coast League. A small Navy town then, San Diego now is the country’s eighth-largest city.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">Pads ownership, which took over in August 2012, says watch out for the team in 2020, give or take a year or two.</p><p xmlns="">The long-term forecast from Peter Seidler, managing partner, is for perennial success like the Pads never have maintained.</p><p xmlns="">“I really expect what we’re building now to lead us to 10 years of being in contention for the playoffs. We should make that happen,” Seidler said in an interview this week.</p><p xmlns="">The Pads have strung together four winning seasons just once, from the opening of Petco Park in 2004 through 2007.</p><p xmlns="">Seidler defined playoff contention in two parts. Going into baseball seasons, the Pads will be universally viewed as a top-eight team in the 15-member National League. “The second piece of that would be,” he said, “you get halfway through the season and you’re still there.”</p><p xmlns="">The Pads will hit .500 in these 10 at-bats, guesses their lead investor. “I would say this: Five years of being in the playoffs, at least, and maybe three or four other years of being close and maybe not making it, and one year a bunch of weird stuff happens. At least five years where we get in.”</p><p xmlns="">Well aware that San Diego’s weather is far easier to forecast than a baseball team’s fortunes, Seidler fed some slack into the line.</p><p xmlns="">“When I talk about 10 consecutive years of playoff contention,” he said, “I know there will be a year or two when we’re out of it by the end of August. But, (the perception will be that) we’re a still strong enough team or organization, that it was a weird year. Weird things happened.”</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">What Seidler is describing, the Chargers achieved. And then some.</p><p xmlns="">For the 10 seasons from 2004 through 2013, the Chargers won six playoff berths. Also, they tended to stay relevant when they fell short. In 2010, for instance, when their run of four division-winning seasons ended, they led the league in total offense and defense, only to miss the playoffs due largely to their poor special teams.</p><p xmlns="">In their favor, the Chargers had to get past only three teams to win the West, where the Pads have to surpass four.</p><p xmlns="">Yet, attaining a height Seidler didn’t forecast for his team, the Chargers won 60 percent of their games over the 10 years. Perhaps more remarkably, they never reached a Super Bowl and got to only one AFC Championship Game. And for all the on-field relevance within a sport that dominated the American sports landscape, team owner Dean Spanos never emerged as a popular figure in San Diego.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">While it stands to reason that entertainment dollars not spent on football would go to baseball, and vice-versa, a former Chargers executive didn’t see the San Diego sports scene as a zero-sum game.</p><p xmlns="">“I believed that a high tide raised all boats,” said Jim Steeg, the team’s chief operations officer from 2004 to 2010 and member of the mayoral panel that in 2015 recommended the Mission Valley site for a new Chargers stadium. “I wanted all local teams to do well to build enthusiasm for attending and watching games in the community. This included baseball, colleges, et cetera. I was a Padres season ticket holder.”</p><p xmlns="">Yet Pads owners and executives shed few tears, one guesses, when San Diego voters denied the Chargers a new football stadium downtown in November 2016.</p><p xmlns="">The building would’ve gone in the East Village, next to Petco Park.</p><p xmlns="">Although the Pads never came out against the Chargers’ facility measure, their neutral public stance was rather like a passive-aggressive thumbs down, or at least a finger pointing toward Mission Valley. And if the Pads were in fact opposed to Measure C, the Chargers were understanding of their position.</p><p xmlns="">“They didn’t want us in their hair downtown,” Chargers counsel Mark Fabiani told me last June, while saying he believed the football team’s proposal for Mission Valley had a better chance of success.</p><p xmlns="">At any rate, the Chargers are some 90 miles north, in Orange County, and their absence isn’t making many local hearts grown fonder. Threading the needle on the topic, Seidler sees opportunity for the Pads yet also doesn’t want them to be the only major-sports game in town for decades to come.</p><p xmlns="">“You could debate whether it’s good for business or bad for business to have another professional major sports franchise here, but we are the only one,” he said. “On the one hand we should take advantage of that from a business standpoint. On the other hand, it’s a responsibility (to fare well) from a community standpoint, and I think we do. It doesn’t impact the way we operate our business — but I would rather see another major professional sports franchise in town than not. Just because I think it’s good for the city.</p><p xmlns="">“It creates overall enthusiasm. The football team did what the football team did. We really feel an obligation to bring a winner here.”</p><p xmlns="">Coming off their seventh consecutive losing season and one that ended with the worst run differential in the big leagues, the Pads probably will have to walk before they can run.</p><p xmlns="">Seidler said his optimism begins with a highly ranked farm system that even Pads rivals have told me is legit.</p><p xmlns="">Naturally, ownership is touting its recent high-stakes investments, notably the $144-million pledge to first baseman Eric Hosmer and the contract extensions awarded last year to General Manager A.J. Preller and manager Andy Green.</p><p xmlns="">The former San Diego Chargers are the much better bet to qualify for the next postseason, but there’s a Pads fans in their midst: Philip Rivers.</p><p xmlns="">When Rivers moved to San Diego in 2004, the Pads were moving into the new ballpark and on the verge of drawing three million fans for the season.</p><p xmlns="">While Rivers still seeks a first Super Bowl, the Pads will look to just get back on the baseball map.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000007079,t000007065,t000046469,t000003194,t000424479,t000007121,t000003183,t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000007391</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>