<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'The multi-category attribute 'cats' references multiple times the category 'local' (id:1630) (ERR0325)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="63229fcd-daa8-4622-ba4e-41fe52be3359" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By The Associated Press</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Not Real News--California Voter Program,1st Ld-Writethru</title><summary>Immigrants living in the U.S. illegally will not automatically be registered to vote in California come April.At issue is a California law taking effect in April that will automatically register people to vote when they get a driver's license, an...</summary><sourceId>34ac9bf8-921d-49c3-9c39-9cafac999e7e</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:k9688%caca-%r%BC-Not Real News--California Voter Program,1st Ld-Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">System won't register to vote those living in US illegally</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(Eds: APNewsNow. Adds dropped letter to second graf in "ID card")</p><byline xmlns="">By The Associated Press</byline><p /><p xmlns="">Immigrants living in the U.S. illegally will not automatically be registered to vote in California come April.</p><p xmlns="">At issue is a California law taking effect in April that will automatically register people to vote when they get a driver's license, an ID card, or update their address with the Department of Motor Vehicles. California allows immigrants living in the country illegally to obtain drivers licenses, leading some online news websites to falsely claim they'll be automatically signed up to vote.</p><p xmlns="">California's new program has specific safeguards in place to ensure only U.S. citizens can go through the voter registration process. A DMV worker processing a drivers' license application for an undocumented immigrant, for example, will not be able to access the voter registration boxes, which will be greyed out.</p><p xmlns="">"To be eligible, you have to be a U.S. citizen," said Jessica Gonzalez, a DMV spokeswoman.</p><p xmlns="">___</p><p xmlns="">This is part of The Associated Press' ongoing effort to fact-check misinformation that is shared widely online, including work with Facebook to identify and reduce the circulation of false stories on the platform.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>