<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="02e609fb-7049-4b9b-92fb-34aaebd0ed9c" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-AP Sportlight</title><summary>BC-AP Sportlight,0487</summary><sourceId>30d4ef53-7bfd-4717-7179-09af61f49f47</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z5121%-----%r%BC-AP Sportlight;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-AP Sportlight,0487</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">AP Sportlight</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Compiled By PAUL MONTELLA</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">March 2</hl2><p xmlns="">1921 — Kentucky beats Georgia 20-19 in the Southern Intercollegiate men's basketball championship game in Atlanta. The 14-team conference does not keep formal regular season standings. It's college basketball's first tournament.</p><p xmlns="">1940 — Seabiscuit, ridden by Red Pollard, wins the Santa Anita Handicap in his final race. Beaten by a nose in both the 1937 and 1938 Santa Anita Handicaps, Seabiscuit beats Kayak II by one-half length to retire as the leading money-winning horse in the world.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — In the first NBA All-Star Game, Ed Macauley of the Celtics scores 20 points to lead the East to a 111-94 victory at Boston Garden.</p><p xmlns="">1951 — St. John's Bob Zawoluk scores 65 points to lead the Redmen to a 105-61 rout of St. Peters. It's the first time in its 43-year history that St. John's scores over 100 points in a game.</p><p xmlns="">1962 — Wilt Chamberlain scores an NBA-record 100 points to lead the Philadelphia Warriors to a 169-147 triumph over the New York Knicks. Chamberlain scores 59 second-half points and 28 points from the free-throw line for records. Both teams combine for 316 points to surpass the record of 312 set by Boston-Minneapolis on Feb. 27, 1959.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Kelso, Horse of the Year 1960-64, runs his last race, finishing fourth at Hialeah (Fla.) Park. Kelso leaves the track as racing's all-time leading money winner with lifetime earnings of $1,977,896. These earnings hold for a record 13 years.</p><p xmlns="">1966 — Chicago's Bobby Hull becomes the first NHL player to have two 50-goal seasons during the Black Hawks' 5-4 victory over the Detroit Red Wings.</p><p xmlns="">1969 — Boston's Phil Esposito becomes the first NHL player to score 100 points in a season, scoring a goal in the Bruins' 4-0 victory over the Pittsburgh Penguins.</p><p xmlns="">1991 — Del Ballard Jr. throws the most famous gutter ball in PBA Tour history in the finals of the Fair Lanes Open. Ballard, needing seven pins on his last roll to beat Pete Weber, gets none as his ball falls into the gutter. Weber wins 213-207, claiming the $30,000 first prize, while Ballard takes $15,500.</p><p xmlns="">1997 — Croatia's Goran Ivanisevic wins the quickest final in ATP Tour history, beating Spain's Sergi Bruguera 6-2, 6-2 in 47 minutes in the Italian Indoors.</p><p xmlns="">2003 — Alinghi takes the America's Cup with a five-race sweep over Team New Zealand, winning the race by 45 seconds. The Swiss team becomes the first European yacht to win the America's Cup in 152 years.</p><p xmlns="">2012 — Major League Baseball expands its playoff format to 10 teams, adding a second wild-card in each league. The decision establishes a one-game, wild-card round in each league between the teams with the best records who are not division winners, meaning a third-place team could win the World Series.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>