<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'Invalid value 'The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)' for story.credit: length out of the range 0..32 (ERR0307)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="bbc143df-e249-3deb-adde-6fc740e9f511" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><authors>By Bryce Miller</authors><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><credit>The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</credit><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-BBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words)</title><summary>PEORIA, Ariz. — The split second Clayton Richard spun to track the rocket in flight, the screaming baseball absolutely reeked of trouble. It sliced toward the gap in deep right-center — a double, for sure. Maybe a triple.Pitchers know these...</summary><sourceId>6822077c-ea6e-10c1-0c15-676951f5e278</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:K3287%kniht%r%BC-BBN-MILLER-COLUMN:SD — sports (900 words);</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">Bryce Miller: Bubble-blowing Margot embraces ‘superstar’ status chase</h2><p class="notes" xmlns="">(PHOTO)</p><byline xmlns="">By Bryce Miller</byline><p><bycr xmlns="">The San Diego Union-Tribune (TNS)</bycr></p><p xmlns="">PEORIA, Ariz. — The split second Clayton Richard spun to track the rocket in flight, the screaming baseball absolutely reeked of trouble. It sliced toward the gap in deep right-center — a double, for sure. Maybe a triple.</p><p xmlns="">Pitchers know these things. This was the kind of dagger that destroys innings and ushers the dinged-up, demoralized arm to the showers. This was the mistake; the one that got away. Except, it didn’t.</p><p xmlns="">Richard caught a glimpse of an effortless blur named Manny Margot — and something that left him slack-jawed.</p><p xmlns="">“I saw him blow a bubble after four or five steps,” Richard said. “Off the bat you think it’s extra bases. Then you see him do that and you’re like, ‘Whoa, he’s got it.’ He’s tracking it, he’s blowing a bubble and he got under it fairly easily.”</p><p xmlns="">That’s Margot, the smiling, 23-year-old face of the Padres’ youth movement. He’s more confident by the minute — and stride — down to his symbolic bubble-blowing choice, Big League Chew.</p><p xmlns="">He’s the first player to find concrete footing in the Padres’ green movement, an organizational about-face that stocked the farm system with about $90 million in international and draft talent while netting even more young blood like Margot through trades.</p><p xmlns="">When news leaked that the Padres had scooped up Royals first baseman Eric Hosmer and would shuffle veteran Wil Myers to the outfield, everyone questioned who would play the other corner spot. No one, though, wondered who would play center.</p><p xmlns="">That job belongs to Margot, a blossoming standout from a dusty village in the Dominican Republic known only as Kilometer 56, simply because of the nearest roadside marker.</p><p xmlns="">“It’s something I’ve dreamed of since I was a kid, making it here and being in this sort of position,” Margot said this week through an interpreter. “But I don’t think you can ever let up. You can’t let that get to your head.</p><p xmlns="">“We have a lot of other people coming, so I have to maintain focus.”</p><p xmlns="">If Oakland’s Dustin Fowler isn’t able to capture his spot after late-June knee surgery, Margot will become the youngest starting center fielder in baseball. Projected front-liners at the position in the NL West average 29.5 years old. Baseball-wide, it hovers just north of 27.6.</p><p xmlns="">ESPN’s Top 300 fantasy baseball list ranks no younger, full-time outfielders ahead of Margot. The sabermetric-sleuths at FanGraphs rate his speed index at 70 … on a scale that goes to 70.</p><p xmlns="">As the Padres aim to turn the corner, many of the franchise’s key pieces will be following Margot’s confident, gum-smacking lead.</p><p xmlns="">“I think last year might have been a little more tense and there might have been a little more pressure,” Margot said. “At the same time, there’s always competition. That doesn’t go away. If you don’t take care of business, it can all change.”</p><p xmlns="">Maturation evolves on the field and off, where Margot prepares to play his first full season as a father to his son named Diamond. That, however, is far from where it started.</p><p xmlns="">In the Dominican, Margot played on a bad-hop field with a sunken car tire anchoring the pitching mound and a random chicken or two roaming the outfield. In a place where it doesn’t take much, smiles come easily.</p><p xmlns="">“It gels the clubhouse together,” Andy Green, the Padres manager, said of Margot’s infectious approach. “He plays to win. He never stops competing. I look at his at-bats and his swing might not be great on a given day, but he never yields.</p><p xmlns="">“As much as I love the smile, I love that too — that tenacity he has when he gets in the batter’s box.”</p><p xmlns="">Green and Margot realize, however, that they’ll need even more from the team’s leadoff hitter. Margot’s .313 on-base percentage in 2017 ranked just sixth on the team.</p><p xmlns="">Margot scored 53 runs last season. Green has challenged him to make it 100. And oh yeah, keep working on that Gold Glove.</p><p xmlns="">“I don’t think it’s impossible,” said Margot, a 5-11, 180-pound right hander. “As a leadoff hitter, I know I have to score runs. Putting that out there as sort of a marker, maybe it’s less than 100 and maybe it’s more, but having that as a marker is good.”</p><p xmlns="">Bubble-blowing good?</p><p xmlns="">Richard’s a believer.</p><p xmlns="">“Just look at the pride he takes in his defense,” Richard said. “Sometimes, that’s one of the last things to come along in a player’s development. Right out of the gate, he wants to be the best center fielder out there. That’s pretty special.”</p><p xmlns="">The best, as they say and Green hinted at this week, seems yet to come.</p><p xmlns="">“He breaks in on the ball as well as anybody I’ve seen,” Green said. “I think he’s just scratching the surface of his potential in center field. He was very solid last year. The push will be to be spectacular.”</p><p xmlns="">At the end of last season, Margot said in a Union-Tribune interview that he wanted to be a “superstar.” Most players, especially younger ones clawing to gain big-league traction, avoid that type of self-assigned pressure.</p><p xmlns="">Margot embraces it.</p><p xmlns="">“If you’re ever going to achieve things, you have to think big,” he said. “So I’m not going to retract that word. I stand firm by it. I have the potential to be that type of player. I know I have to continue to work, but I have a commitment to turn myself into that type of player.</p><p xmlns="">“Right now, I’m not changing that word, because I believe it.”</p><p xmlns="">Then he smiled.</p><p xmlns="">No bubble necessary.</p><p xmlns="">———</p><p xmlns="">©2018 The San Diego Union-Tribune</p><p xmlns="">Visit The San Diego Union-Tribune at www.sandiegouniontribune.com</p><p xmlns="">Distributed by Tribune Content Agency, LLC.</p><p xmlns="">—————</p><p xmlns="">PHOTO (for help with images, contact 312-222-4194):</p><p xmlns="">_____</p><p xmlns="">Topics: t000003270,t000003271,t000007309,t000007333,t000424479,t000003183,t000007391</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>