<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><log event="ImportExportErr" loginGuid="0cfbf252-5b2d-4e47-acc4-079c41f2429a" userId="4" userName="Administrator" xmlns="http://www.teradp.com/schemas/GN4/1/Log.xsd"><description>XML import: object(s) input</description><error code="257" name="ImportError">Error importing XML: 'There is no XML format with name: 'XHTML-TRANSACTIONS' (ERR0206)' (ERR0257)</error><xml><story name="8a7777e1-3436-4cd8-a98c-2dff43190cf3" xmlns="urn:schemas-teradp-com:gn4tera" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt"><cats><ref weight="100" code="local" /></cats><folderRef><keyVal>/Wires/AP Stories</keyVal></folderRef><sourceRef><keyVal>AP (agate)</keyVal></sourceRef><title>BC-Transactions,Writethru</title><summary>BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</summary><sourceId>0ec795ae-adc9-4cc6-cc68-cef14eae9a3b</sourceId><sourceRef><keyVal>AP</keyVal></sourceRef><instructions>Legacy:z2827%-----%r%BC-Transactions,Writethru;</instructions><objs /><xmlText><h2 style="display:none" xmlns="">BC-Transactions,Writethru</h2><byline xmlns=""></byline><p /><hl2 xmlns="">BC-Transactions, Writethru,0381</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Tuesday's Sports Transactions</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">By The Associated Press</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">BASEBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National League</hl2><p xmlns="">NEW YORK METS — Agreed to terms with RHPs Tyler Bashlor, Gerson Bautista, Jamie Callahan, Chris Flexen, Robert Gsellman, Seth Lugo, Kevin McGowan, Marcos Molina, Rafael Montero, Corey Oswalt, Jacob Rhame and Paul Sewald; INFs Gavin Cecchini, Luis Guillorme, T.J. Rivera, Amed Rosario and Dominic Smith; OFs Michael Conforto and Brandon Nimmo; LHP Steven Matz and Cs Tomas Nido and Kevin Plawecki on one-year contracts.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Atlantic League</hl2><p xmlns="">LONG ISLAND DUCKS — Signed RHP Rob Rogers.</p><hl2 xmlns="">Frontier League</hl2><p xmlns="">EVANSVILLE OTTERS — Signed RHP Brian Bass and RHP Tyler Vail.</p><p xmlns="">FLORENCE FREEDOM — Signed 3B Xavier Turner.</p><p xmlns="">LAKE ERIE CRUSHERS — Signed C Karl Ellison, OF Cameron Newell and RHP Sean Renzi.</p><p xmlns="">NORMAL CORNBELTERS — Signed OF Andrew Godbold to a contract extension.</p><hl2 xmlns="">FOOTBALL</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Football League</hl2><p xmlns="">CHICAGO BEARS — Named Brad Childress offensive consultant.</p><p xmlns="">DETROIT LIONS — Designated DE Ziggy Ansah as their franchise player.</p><p xmlns="">INDIANAPOLIS COLTS — Named Tom Rathman running backs coach, Alan Williams secondary coach, Marcus Brady assistant quarterbacks coach, Bobby Johnson assistant offensive line coach, Tom Manning tight ends coach, Kevin Patullo wide receivers coach and Gunnard Twyner offensive quality control coach.</p><p xmlns="">PHILADELPHIA EAGLES — Announced the retirement of P Donnie Jones.</p><p xmlns="">SAN FRANCISCO 49ERS — Signed OL Garry Gilliam to a two-year contract extension through 2019.</p><hl2 xmlns="">HOCKEY</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">National Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">ANAHEIM DUCKS — Assigned C Kalle Kossila and G Reto Berra to San Diego (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">BUFFALO SABRES — Recalled F Seth Griffith from Rochester (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">COLORADO AVALANCHE — Recalled G Spencer Martin from San Antonio (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">NEW JERSEY DEVILS — Assigned G Cory Schneider to Binghamton (AHL) on a conditioning loan.</p><p xmlns="">PITTSBURGH PENGUINS — Signed F Patric Hornqvist to a five-year contract extension through the 2022-23 season.</p><p xmlns="">TAMPA BAY LIGHTNING — Recalled F Michael Bournival from Syracuse (AHL).</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON CAPITALS — Recalled F Travis Boyd from Hershey (AHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">American Hockey League</hl2><p xmlns="">BAKERSFIELD CONDORS — Announced D Ethan Bear was recalled by Edmonton (NHL).</p><p xmlns="">SAN ANTONIO RAMPAGE — Recalled G Joe Cannata and F Brady Shaw from Colorado (ECHL).</p><hl2 xmlns="">ECHL</hl2><p xmlns="">ATLANTA GLADIATORS — Traded F Colin Jacobs to Toledo for D Davis Vandane,</p><hl2 xmlns="">SOCCER</hl2><hl2 xmlns="">Major League Soccer</hl2><p xmlns="">LOS ANGELES FC — Signed M Eduard Atuesta from Independiente Medellin using Targeted Allocation Money.</p><p xmlns="">NEW YORK CITY FC — Transferred D Sebastien Ibeagha from San Antonio (USL).</p><p xmlns="">SPORTING KANSAS CITY — Signed G Tim Melia, D Ike Opara and F Daniel Salloi.</p><hl2 xmlns="">North American Soccer League</hl2><p xmlns="">NASL — Canceled the 2018 season.</p><hl2 xmlns="">COLLEGE</hl2><p xmlns="">BERKELEY (NJ) — Named Joanna Ciavarella men's and women's tennis coach.</p><p xmlns="">MIDLAND — Named Eric Crouch running backs and special teams coach.</p><p xmlns="">WASHINGTON STATE — Named Mason Miller offensive line coach, Matt Brock special teams coordinator, Steve Spurrier Jr. outside receivers coach and Tyson Brown strength and conditioning coach.</p></xmlText><xmlFormatRef><keyVal xmlns="">XHTML-TRANSACTIONS</keyVal></xmlFormatRef></story></xml></log>